<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv generator-info-name="TVMaze EPG Generator" generator-info-url="https://www.tvmaze.com/api">
  <channel id="CNN.US">
    <display-name>CNN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Fox News Channel.US">
    <display-name>Fox News Channel</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="MS NOW.US">
    <display-name>MS NOW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNBC.US">
    <display-name>CNBC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Newsmax.US">
    <display-name>Newsmax</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NewsNation.US">
    <display-name>NewsNation</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.US">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NBC.US">
    <display-name>NBC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CBS.US">
    <display-name>CBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL Network.US">
    <display-name>NFL Network</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Syndication.US">
    <display-name>Syndication</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ESPN.US">
    <display-name>ESPN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="FOX.US">
    <display-name>FOX</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Bravo.US">
    <display-name>Bravo</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="History.US">
    <display-name>History</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="National Geographic.US">
    <display-name>National Geographic</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery.US">
    <display-name>Discovery</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="A&amp;E.US">
    <display-name>A&amp;E</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Comedy Central.US">
    <display-name>Comedy Central</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="PBS.US">
    <display-name>PBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="The CW.US">
    <display-name>The CW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="STARZ.US">
    <display-name>STARZ</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="HBO.US">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ITV1.GB">
    <display-name>ITV1</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="5.GB">
    <display-name>5</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Channel 4.GB">
    <display-name>Channel 4</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC Two.GB">
    <display-name>BBC Two</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC Alba.GB">
    <display-name>BBC Alba</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Sky Arts.GB">
    <display-name>Sky Arts</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="National Geographic.GB">
    <display-name>National Geographic</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC One.GB">
    <display-name>BBC One</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Quest.GB">
    <display-name>Quest</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="E4.GB">
    <display-name>E4</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <display-name>TRUE CRIME</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CBC.CA">
    <display-name>CBC</display-name>
    <country>CA</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Citytv.CA">
    <display-name>Citytv</display-name>
    <country>CA</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CTV.CA">
    <display-name>CTV</display-name>
    <country>CA</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.AU">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>AU</country>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260331000000 -0400" stop="20260331020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401050000 -0400" stop="20260401060000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends First</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the day, FOX &amp;amp; Friends First delivers all the headlines viewers may have missed overnight, along with a preview of upcoming news events. Presented two hours before FOX &amp;amp; Friends, the first hour of the program is hosted by Todd Piro and Carley Shimkus</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401050000 -0400" stop="20260401060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401050000 -0400" stop="20260401060000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Early Start</title>
    <desc>The news you need, first thing. Rahel Solomon has you covered with the latest headlines.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401050000 -0400" stop="20260401060000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Morning Call</title>
    <desc>Morning Call, anchored by Morgan Brennan, delivers the essential market intelligence that drives the trading day ahead. The program captures breaking business news as it unfolds and tracks pre‑market equity moves, commodity swings, U.S. futures, and overnight action across global markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401060000 -0400" stop="20260401100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401060000 -0400" stop="20260401070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401060000 -0400" stop="20260401070000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Early</title>
    <desc>Wake up to reliable reporting that delivers the essential facts you need to start your day informed, along with expert commentary and thoughtful analysis. Get an early look at the top stories shaping national and global conversations. Whether it's politics, business, culture, or breaking news, you'll be prepared for whatever the day brings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401060000 -0400" stop="20260401090000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Morning in America</title>
    <desc>Morning in America is NewsNation's live national morning newscast hosted by Markie Martin.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401060000 -0400" stop="20260401090000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk Box</title>
    <desc>Squawk Box is a business news television program that airs at breakfast time on the CNBC network. The program is currently co-hosted by Joe Kernen, Rebecca Quick, and Andrew Ross Sorkin. Since debuting in 1995, the show has spawned a number of versions across CNBC's international channels, many of which employ a similar format. The program title originates from a term used in investment banks and stock brokerages for a permanent voice circuit or intercom used to communicate stock deals or sales priorities; it also may refer to the squawk of a bird, like a peacock, which is the logo of CNBC.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401070000 -0400" stop="20260401100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401070000 -0400" stop="20260401090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America</title>
    <desc>Start your day and weekend with real news and analysis from Rob Finnerty, Michael Grimm &amp;amp; Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401070000 -0400" stop="20260401090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401070000 -0400" stop="20260401090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401070000 -0400" stop="20260401090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401080000 -0400" stop="20260401100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401090000 -0400" stop="20260401110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401090000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>National Report</title>
    <desc>National Report with Shaun Kraisman and Emma Rechenberg for live breaking news from NY and Washington, on politics, health, finance, and lifestyle that impact you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401090000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes</title>
    <desc>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes brings you a fast-paced look at the latest from the border to Main Street to the White House and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401090000 -0400" stop="20260401100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401090000 -0400" stop="20260401100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401090000 -0400" stop="20260401110000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk on the Street</title>
    <desc>Squawk on the Street is headquartered live on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange. We are there when the all-important opening bell rings every day. With our exclusive "Eye on the Floor" wireless cameras at the NYSE we take the viewer onto the floor of the exchange, right to the posts where the biggest companies in the world trade. In addition, our exclusive "Tick by Tick" charts track the action of every trade of every stock. Our live market coverage doesn't stop on the corner of Wall and Broad Streets in lower Manhattan. We also have exclusive coverage from the floor of the CME Group in Chicago giving our viewers the treasury, currency and commodity action in real time. In addition, "Squawk on the Street" is also on the air when the closing bells ring throughout Europe. That final hour of European trading starting at 10:30am eastern has proven to be very volatile and has a major impact on all U.S. based markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401100000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401100000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401100000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401100000 -0400" stop="20260401110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401110000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Faulkner Focus</title>
    <desc>Emmy-winning journalist Harris Faulkner provides the latest news driving the day with insightful analysis and interviews with top newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401110000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401110000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Price is Right</title>
    <desc>The Price is Right, originally hosted by Bob Barker until 2007 and Drew Carey thereafter -- features a wide variety of games and contests with the same basic challenge: Guess the prices of everyday (or not-quite-everyday) retail items. Four contestants, all of whom are seated in one of the wildest audiences in daytime game-show history, are called to the stage to play a preliminary pricing round. That winner joins the host on stage for one of more than 70 different pricing games. After three such games, the contestants spin a big wheel -- hoping to get as close to $1 as possible -- in the "Showcase Showdown". The two highest winners of that round advance to the final, where prizes could be cars or roomsful of furniture. A trio of models presents the prizes.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401110000 -0400" stop="20260401120000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Money Movers</title>
    <desc>Money Movers provides investors with real-time analysis of the stories and the people attracting the attention of the markets each day. Capturing the energy of day's early trading, the program includes the breaking news and numbers driving stocks and sectors, helping investors make critical decisions. "Money Movers" anchors Carl Quintanilla and Sara Eisen speak with the CEOs, government decision-makers and newsmakers who play a relevant role in how money is moving.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401120000 -0400" stop="20260401130000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Outnumbered</title>
    <desc>Featuring an ensemble of four female panelists and one rotating male, Outnumbered examines the top news stories as well as the leading pop culture and relationship issues dominating the headlines. FNC's Harris Faulkner, Kayleigh McEnany and Emily Compagno lead the program's coverage, while alternating co-panelists weigh in with analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401120000 -0400" stop="20260401140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401120000 -0400" stop="20260401130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401120000 -0400" stop="20260401140000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Newsline</title>
    <desc>Bianca de la Garza tackles the big news from D.C., N.Y., across America, and around the world!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401120000 -0400" stop="20260401150000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Nichole Berlie</title>
    <desc>The day's top news headlines with reports from correspondents around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401120000 -0400" stop="20260401130000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Fast Money Halftime Report</title>
    <desc>The hot trades in the market from the floor of the New York Stock Exchange.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401123000 -0400" stop="20260401133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401130000 -0400" stop="20260401150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401130000 -0400" stop="20260401160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401130000 -0400" stop="20260401140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401130000 -0400" stop="20260401140000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>The Exchange</title>
    <desc>Anchor Kelly Evans reports on the most important stories to today's markets and investors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401133000 -0400" stop="20260401140000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Bold and the Beautiful</title>
    <desc>They created a dynasty where passion rules, they are the Forresters, the first name in Fashion. The Bold and the Beautiful, a world of fashion, glamor and romance. A place where power, money and success are there for the taking in a city where dreams really do come true. Follow the lives and loves of the Forresters on The Bold and the Beautiful...</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401140000 -0400" stop="20260401160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401140000 -0400" stop="20260401160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401140000 -0400" stop="20260401150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401140000 -0400" stop="20260401150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401140000 -0400" stop="20260401150000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Power Lunch</title>
    <desc>Power Lunch takes you through the heart of the business day, focusing on real-time market coverage, breaking news and up-to-the-instant stock information. The show delves into the economy, the markets, real estate, media and technology -- any place where there's money to be made. The program features daily contributions from the Nasdaq MarketSite's Times Square studio and coverage from CNBC's Post 9 position on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange, as well as from CNBC's bureaus around the world. "Power Lunch" showcases the best stories of the day from CNBC's roster of digital and television journalists.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401150000 -0400" stop="20260401160000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Story</title>
    <desc>The Story with Martha MacCallum, anchored by Martha MacCallum, focuses on the stories that are most important to Americans with insight from top newsmakers and analysts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401150000 -0400" stop="20260401180000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live With Connell McShane</title>
    <desc>Connell McShane presents reports and analysis of the day's national and international newsworthy events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401150000 -0400" stop="20260401160000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Let's Make a Deal</title>
    <desc>Let's Make a Deal is an updated version of the classic television game show, hosted by Emmy Award-winner Wayne Brady, where audience members try to win cash and prizes by making wacky deals.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401160000 -0400" stop="20260401180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401160000 -0400" stop="20260401170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Will Cain Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers from across politics, business, culture and sports, The Will Cain Show will offer a comprehensive look at the news of the day in a signature podcast style.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401160000 -0400" stop="20260401170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401160000 -0400" stop="20260401170000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Record with Greta Van Susteren</title>
    <desc>Award-winning journalist Greta Van Susteren digs into the top stories of the day with the focus on why they matter to the American people. Greta speaks with the top newsmakers on both sides of the aisle, creating a conversation and dialogue that is imperative for the nation's well-being.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401170000 -0400" stop="20260401180000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Five</title>
    <desc>The Five is an American news and talk show on Fox News Channel featuring a rotating panel who discuss current stories, political issues, and pop culture. The show premiered in July 2011, replacing the Glenn Beck program, and airs on weekdays at 5:00 p.m. ET with replays at 4:00 a.m. ET. On October 3, 2011, after successful ratings and high popularity, Fox News announced that The Five would become the permanent 5 p.m. series, as the program had previously been announced to last only during the summer. The Five is currently the second-most-watched program in all of cable news in the United States, placing only behind The O'Reilly Factor, also on the Fox News Channel. The program has occasionally been the number one rated cable news series in the key 25 to 54 viewing demographic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401170000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401170000 -0400" stop="20260401180000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Ed Henry the Big Take</title>
    <desc>Ed Henry offers his common-sense take on the news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401180000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401180000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Special Report</title>
    <desc>Special Report with Bret Baier (formerly Special Report with Brit Hume) is an American television news and political commentary program appearing on Fox News Channel, currently hosted by Bret Baier. It airs live each Monday through Friday at 6:00 PM ET. The show focuses on both reporting and analysis of the day's events, with a primary focus on national political news. The show has been a part of the Fox News program lineup since 1998 and is the number one cable news broadcast in its time slot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401180000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Carl Higbie Frontline</title>
    <desc>Carl Higbie Frontline focuses on providing commonsense news analysis, exposing big government overreach and the media's shortfalls — all while always fighting for American values. Produced from Newsmax's Manhattan studios covering breaking news and exploring key issues such as personal liberty, security, and government transparency.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401180000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hill on NewsNation combines the power of two trusted news sources into one must-watch hour. The Hill, the nation's #1 political website, and NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, team up to define today's most-pressing issues, and question Washington's power brokers on what matters most to the people they serve and what matters most to Americans.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401183000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401183000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401183000 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401190000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401190000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Ingraham Angle</title>
    <desc>The Ingraham Angle cuts through the Washington chatter to speak directly with unexpected voices and the actual people who are impacted by the news of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401190000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401190000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Rob Schmitt Tonight</title>
    <desc>Rob Schmitt Tonight locks in all the late-breaking stories that matter to you, and delivers the up-to-the-minute news you need to hear before turning in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401190000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Elizabeth Vargas Reports</title>
    <desc>In-depth coverage of the biggest news stories of the day; NewsNation's home for exclusive and enterprise reporting; hosted live by Elizabeth Vargas.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>An emotional thrill ride through the day-to-day chaos of the city's newest state-of-the-art trauma center and into the lives of the courageous doctors, nurses and staff who hold it all together. This is one of those days.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Survivor</title>
    <desc>Eighteen to twenty castaways will compete against each other on Survivor. All castaways will compete to outwit, outplay, outlast and ultimately be crowned Sole Survivor.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401203000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Scrubs</title>
    <desc>Old friends JD and Turk scrub in together for the first time in a long time, learning that medicine has changed; interns have changed; but their bromance has stood the test of time.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>The Masked Singer</title>
    <desc>Based on an international hit, which already is a viral phenomenon with more than half a billion fans worldwide, and the No. 1 top-trending video of 2017 on YouTube, The Masked Singer features celebrities facing off against one another with one major twist: each singer is shrouded from head to toe in an elaborate costume, complete with full face mask to conceal his or her identity. Ken Jeong, Jenny McCarthy, Nicole Scherzinger and Robin Thicke serve on the panel and play detective, alongside host Nick Cannon.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Valley</title>
    <desc>The Valley follows a group of close friends as they trade bottle service in West Hollywood for baby bottles in the Valley all while they navigate bustling businesses, rocky relationships and feisty friendships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Jesse Watters Primetime</title>
    <desc>Jesse Watters brings his fresh take to Primetime. Each night, he'll speak with newsmakers from across the country and give Americans a show where straight talk is the only talk, and the obvious will never be left unsaid.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401213400 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Swamp People</title>
    <desc>The Swamp People featured in this History series are the proud descendants of French Canadian refugees who settled in the swamp region of Louisiana in the 18th century. Cameras follow members of this fiercely independent group as they struggle to preserve their way of life in the Atchafalaya Basin during the most important time of the year for them: alligator-hunting season.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Finnerty</title>
    <desc>Finnerty will look to cut through the noise to bring unfiltered truth, sharp debates, and a focus on the most pressing issues facing America today while standing up for American values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Cuomo</title>
    <desc>Chris Cuomo hosts CUOMO, a no-nonsense show featuring the day's most important news from all perspectives. CUOMO airs weeknights at 8 p.m./7C on NewsNation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401203000 -0400" stop="20260401210200 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Abbott Elementary</title>
    <desc>In this workplace comedy, a group of dedicated, passionate teachers — and a slightly tone-deaf principal — are brought together in a Philadelphia public school where, despite the odds stacked against them, they are determined to help their students succeed in life. Though these incredible public servants may be outnumbered and underfunded, they love what they do — even if they don't love the school district's less-than-stellar attitude toward educating children.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220400 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>The Masked Singer</title>
    <desc>Based on an international hit, which already is a viral phenomenon with more than half a billion fans worldwide, and the No. 1 top-trending video of 2017 on YouTube, The Masked Singer features celebrities facing off against one another with one major twist: each singer is shrouded from head to toe in an elaborate costume, complete with full face mask to conceal his or her identity. Ken Jeong, Jenny McCarthy, Nicole Scherzinger and Robin Thicke serve on the panel and play detective, alongside host Nick Cannon.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="National Geographic.US">
    <title>To Catch a Smuggler</title>
    <desc>Stationed at JFK International Airport—one of the largest hubs for international travel in America—officers with U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) and U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) crack down on criminals attempting to smuggle illegal goods and drugs into the United States. It's a job where everything—the safety of their team, and the security of the nation—is at stake. But for these officers, it's just another day at JFK.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Hannity</title>
    <desc>Sean Hannity interviews political figures and newsmakers and offers his own perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Greg Kelly Reports</title>
    <desc>The hardest-hitting stories from coast to coast: We take you from the Beltway to the Rust Belt and beyond — never forgetting we're here to enlighten, expose, inform, and spotlight the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Expedition Files</title>
    <desc>In the all-new series Expedition Files, adventurer Josh Gates travels through history on a search to uncover new evidence and answers to the world's most captivating and unexplained mysteries.  Each episode of Expedition Files explores compelling true stories that defy explanation, offering stunning revelations and surprising new insights.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>On Balance with Leland Vittert</title>
    <desc>The day's hottest subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>K9 PD with Jim Belushi</title>
    <desc>K9 PD with Jim Belushi showcases intense moments caught on camera of officers and their K9 partners facing high-stakes calls, told through gripping footage from surveillance cameras, body and dash cams, drones and more. Actor and lifelong K9 advocate Jim Belushi returns to the world of heroic K9s—only this time, it's for real—serving as host of the series, which captures the courage, precision, and raw instinct behind one of law enforcement's most formidable partnerships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Southern Hospitality</title>
    <desc>The series follows "Southern Charm" resident boss-lady Leva Bonaparte as she manages Charleston's very own "it" crowd, otherwise known as her larger-than-life staff at Republic Garden &amp;amp; Lounge. Leva and husband Lamar own four restaurants along the city's famous King Street, but Republic is the crown jewel of their kingdom. The hottest nightclub and backdrop for Charleston's lively party scene, Republic is the place to go for pleasure, business or both.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401212000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS News Special Report</title>
    <desc>On CBS News Special Report, special events are covered by the CBS news team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401212000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC News Special Report</title>
    <desc>On the ABC News Specials, the stories that need to be covered in great detailed are featured.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401212000 -0400" stop="20260401222000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>No job is more stressful, dangerous or exhilarating than those of the Firefighters, Rescue Squad and Paramedics of Chicago Firehouse 51. These are the courageous men and women who forge headfirst into danger when everyone else is running the other way and whose actions make the difference between life and death. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401213000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>K9 PD with Jim Belushi</title>
    <desc>K9 PD with Jim Belushi showcases intense moments caught on camera of officers and their K9 partners facing high-stakes calls, told through gripping footage from surveillance cameras, body and dash cams, drones and more. Actor and lifelong K9 advocate Jim Belushi returns to the world of heroic K9s—only this time, it's for real—serving as host of the series, which captures the courage, precision, and raw instinct behind one of law enforcement's most formidable partnerships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401213400 -0400" stop="20260401223400 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Pawn Stars: Best Of</title>
    <desc>The very best episodes of Pawn Stars.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Gutfeld!</title>
    <desc>Late night show with author, comedian and television host and producer Greg Gutfeld, offering up satirical political and social commentary with a weekly panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>District 21 of the Chicago Police Department is made up of two distinctly different groups. There are the uniformed cops who patrol the beat and go head to head with the city's street crimes. And there's the Intelligence Unit, the team that combats the city's major offenses - organized crime, drug trafficking, high profile murders and beyond. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Chris Plante: The Right Squad</title>
    <desc>Chris Plante and his "THE RIGHT SQUAD" are the most interesting, informative and funny group of talking heads in the world! It's a big claim. But it's true!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Katie Pavlich Tonight</title>
    <desc>Katie Pavlich Tonight offers a conservative take on the day's events while welcoming all viewpoints. The goal: cutting through left-right bias in pursuit of plain facts and honest analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Conspiracies &amp; Coverups</title>
    <desc>Driven by a relentless hunt for the truth, Bustamante pulls back the curtain on modern-day mysteries that blur the line between fact and fiction. Using his unique perspective and insider techniques, he investigates, pressure-tests, and challenges prevailing narratives to reveal the hidden forces behind these events and the motives used to manipulate the truth.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401223000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Southern Law</title>
    <desc>Southern Law follows law enforcement officers across the South as they respond to calls, protect their communities, and face the realities of policing in one of the country's most dynamic regions.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401222000 -0400" stop="20260401232000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>America's Culinary Cup</title>
    <desc>America's Culinary Cup will feature a cast of the nation's most decorated chefs as they compete in the kitchen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401230000 -0400" stop="20260402000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401230000 -0400" stop="20260402000000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News @ Night</title>
    <desc>Fox News @ Night is a live hour of hard news and analysis of the most compelling stories from Washington and across the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401230000 -0400" stop="20260401233500 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401230000 -0400" stop="20260402000000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Jesse Weber Live</title>
    <desc>A fresh, fast-paced, and often unexpected take on the day's headlines, diving into the biggest stories through the lens of an expert in legal affairs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401230000 -0400" stop="20260402000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401230000 -0400" stop="20260402000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401235000 -0400" stop="20260402005000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Emmy Award and Grammy Award winner Jimmy Fallon brought NBC's "The Tonight Show" back to its New York origins when he launched The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from Rockefeller Center. Fallon puts his own stamp on the storied NBC late-night franchise with his unique comedic wit, on-point pop culture awareness, welcoming style and impeccable taste in music with the award-winning house band, The Roots.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401235000 -0400" stop="20260402005000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Late Show with Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert brings his signature satire and comedy to The Late Show with Stephen Colbert, the #1 show in late-night. Featuring bandleader Jon Batiste with his band Stay Human, the Emmy Award-nominated show broadcasts from the historic Ed Sullivan Theater. He talks with an eclectic mix of guests about what is new and relevant in the worlds of politics, entertainment, business, music, technology, and more. Stephen Colbert took over as host, executive producer, and writer of The Late Show on Sept. 8, 2015. Colbert is best known for his work as a television host, writer, actor, and producer, and lest known for his charity work teaching English as a second language on Tunisian date farms. Before joining the CBS family -- and being officially adopted by network president Les Moonves -- Colbert helmed The Colbert Report, which aired nearly 1,500 episodes and required Stephen to wear nearly 1,500 different neckties. The program received two Peabody Awards, two Grammy Awards, and several unwelcome shoulder massages. It won two Emmys for Outstanding Variety Series in 2013 and 2014, both of which appear to have been lost in the move. Colbert is pronounced koʊlˈbɛər, according to Wikipedia. His understudy is William Cavanaugh, who will be hosting The Late Show approximately one-third of the time. Good luck, Bill!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401000000 -0400" stop="20260401020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401000000 -0400" stop="20260401020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402050000 -0400" stop="20260402060000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends First</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the day, FOX &amp;amp; Friends First delivers all the headlines viewers may have missed overnight, along with a preview of upcoming news events. Presented two hours before FOX &amp;amp; Friends, the first hour of the program is hosted by Todd Piro and Carley Shimkus</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402050000 -0400" stop="20260402060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402050000 -0400" stop="20260402060000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Early Start</title>
    <desc>The news you need, first thing. Rahel Solomon has you covered with the latest headlines.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402050000 -0400" stop="20260402060000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Morning Call</title>
    <desc>Morning Call, anchored by Morgan Brennan, delivers the essential market intelligence that drives the trading day ahead. The program captures breaking business news as it unfolds and tracks pre‑market equity moves, commodity swings, U.S. futures, and overnight action across global markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402060000 -0400" stop="20260402100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402060000 -0400" stop="20260402070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402060000 -0400" stop="20260402070000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Early</title>
    <desc>Wake up to reliable reporting that delivers the essential facts you need to start your day informed, along with expert commentary and thoughtful analysis. Get an early look at the top stories shaping national and global conversations. Whether it's politics, business, culture, or breaking news, you'll be prepared for whatever the day brings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402060000 -0400" stop="20260402090000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Morning in America</title>
    <desc>Morning in America is NewsNation's live national morning newscast hosted by Markie Martin.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402060000 -0400" stop="20260402090000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk Box</title>
    <desc>Squawk Box is a business news television program that airs at breakfast time on the CNBC network. The program is currently co-hosted by Joe Kernen, Rebecca Quick, and Andrew Ross Sorkin. Since debuting in 1995, the show has spawned a number of versions across CNBC's international channels, many of which employ a similar format. The program title originates from a term used in investment banks and stock brokerages for a permanent voice circuit or intercom used to communicate stock deals or sales priorities; it also may refer to the squawk of a bird, like a peacock, which is the logo of CNBC.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402070000 -0400" stop="20260402100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402070000 -0400" stop="20260402090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America</title>
    <desc>Start your day and weekend with real news and analysis from Rob Finnerty, Michael Grimm &amp;amp; Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402070000 -0400" stop="20260402090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402070000 -0400" stop="20260402090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402070000 -0400" stop="20260402090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402080000 -0400" stop="20260402100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402090000 -0400" stop="20260402110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402090000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>National Report</title>
    <desc>National Report with Shaun Kraisman and Emma Rechenberg for live breaking news from NY and Washington, on politics, health, finance, and lifestyle that impact you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402090000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes</title>
    <desc>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes brings you a fast-paced look at the latest from the border to Main Street to the White House and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402090000 -0400" stop="20260402100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402090000 -0400" stop="20260402100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402090000 -0400" stop="20260402110000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk on the Street</title>
    <desc>Squawk on the Street is headquartered live on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange. We are there when the all-important opening bell rings every day. With our exclusive "Eye on the Floor" wireless cameras at the NYSE we take the viewer onto the floor of the exchange, right to the posts where the biggest companies in the world trade. In addition, our exclusive "Tick by Tick" charts track the action of every trade of every stock. Our live market coverage doesn't stop on the corner of Wall and Broad Streets in lower Manhattan. We also have exclusive coverage from the floor of the CME Group in Chicago giving our viewers the treasury, currency and commodity action in real time. In addition, "Squawk on the Street" is also on the air when the closing bells ring throughout Europe. That final hour of European trading starting at 10:30am eastern has proven to be very volatile and has a major impact on all U.S. based markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402100000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402100000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402100000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402100000 -0400" stop="20260402110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402110000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Faulkner Focus</title>
    <desc>Emmy-winning journalist Harris Faulkner provides the latest news driving the day with insightful analysis and interviews with top newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402110000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402110000 -0400" stop="20260402120000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Money Movers</title>
    <desc>Money Movers provides investors with real-time analysis of the stories and the people attracting the attention of the markets each day. Capturing the energy of day's early trading, the program includes the breaking news and numbers driving stocks and sectors, helping investors make critical decisions. "Money Movers" anchors Carl Quintanilla and Sara Eisen speak with the CEOs, government decision-makers and newsmakers who play a relevant role in how money is moving.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402120000 -0400" stop="20260402130000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Outnumbered</title>
    <desc>Featuring an ensemble of four female panelists and one rotating male, Outnumbered examines the top news stories as well as the leading pop culture and relationship issues dominating the headlines. FNC's Harris Faulkner, Kayleigh McEnany and Emily Compagno lead the program's coverage, while alternating co-panelists weigh in with analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402120000 -0400" stop="20260402140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402120000 -0400" stop="20260402130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402120000 -0400" stop="20260402140000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Newsline</title>
    <desc>Bianca de la Garza tackles the big news from D.C., N.Y., across America, and around the world!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402120000 -0400" stop="20260402150000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Nichole Berlie</title>
    <desc>The day's top news headlines with reports from correspondents around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402120000 -0400" stop="20260402130000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Fast Money Halftime Report</title>
    <desc>The hot trades in the market from the floor of the New York Stock Exchange.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402123000 -0400" stop="20260402133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402130000 -0400" stop="20260402150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402130000 -0400" stop="20260402160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402130000 -0400" stop="20260402140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402130000 -0400" stop="20260402140000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>The Exchange</title>
    <desc>Anchor Kelly Evans reports on the most important stories to today's markets and investors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402133000 -0400" stop="20260402140000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Bold and the Beautiful</title>
    <desc>They created a dynasty where passion rules, they are the Forresters, the first name in Fashion. The Bold and the Beautiful, a world of fashion, glamor and romance. A place where power, money and success are there for the taking in a city where dreams really do come true. Follow the lives and loves of the Forresters on The Bold and the Beautiful...</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402140000 -0400" stop="20260402160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402140000 -0400" stop="20260402160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402140000 -0400" stop="20260402150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402140000 -0400" stop="20260402150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402140000 -0400" stop="20260402150000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Power Lunch</title>
    <desc>Power Lunch takes you through the heart of the business day, focusing on real-time market coverage, breaking news and up-to-the-instant stock information. The show delves into the economy, the markets, real estate, media and technology -- any place where there's money to be made. The program features daily contributions from the Nasdaq MarketSite's Times Square studio and coverage from CNBC's Post 9 position on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange, as well as from CNBC's bureaus around the world. "Power Lunch" showcases the best stories of the day from CNBC's roster of digital and television journalists.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402150000 -0400" stop="20260402160000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Story</title>
    <desc>The Story with Martha MacCallum, anchored by Martha MacCallum, focuses on the stories that are most important to Americans with insight from top newsmakers and analysts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402150000 -0400" stop="20260402180000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live With Connell McShane</title>
    <desc>Connell McShane presents reports and analysis of the day's national and international newsworthy events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402150000 -0400" stop="20260402160000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Let's Make a Deal</title>
    <desc>Let's Make a Deal is an updated version of the classic television game show, hosted by Emmy Award-winner Wayne Brady, where audience members try to win cash and prizes by making wacky deals.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402160000 -0400" stop="20260402180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402160000 -0400" stop="20260402170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Will Cain Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers from across politics, business, culture and sports, The Will Cain Show will offer a comprehensive look at the news of the day in a signature podcast style.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402160000 -0400" stop="20260402170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402160000 -0400" stop="20260402170000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Record with Greta Van Susteren</title>
    <desc>Award-winning journalist Greta Van Susteren digs into the top stories of the day with the focus on why they matter to the American people. Greta speaks with the top newsmakers on both sides of the aisle, creating a conversation and dialogue that is imperative for the nation's well-being.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402170000 -0400" stop="20260402180000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Five</title>
    <desc>The Five is an American news and talk show on Fox News Channel featuring a rotating panel who discuss current stories, political issues, and pop culture. The show premiered in July 2011, replacing the Glenn Beck program, and airs on weekdays at 5:00 p.m. ET with replays at 4:00 a.m. ET. On October 3, 2011, after successful ratings and high popularity, Fox News announced that The Five would become the permanent 5 p.m. series, as the program had previously been announced to last only during the summer. The Five is currently the second-most-watched program in all of cable news in the United States, placing only behind The O'Reilly Factor, also on the Fox News Channel. The program has occasionally been the number one rated cable news series in the key 25 to 54 viewing demographic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402170000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402170000 -0400" stop="20260402180000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Ed Henry the Big Take</title>
    <desc>Ed Henry offers his common-sense take on the news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402180000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402180000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Special Report</title>
    <desc>Special Report with Bret Baier (formerly Special Report with Brit Hume) is an American television news and political commentary program appearing on Fox News Channel, currently hosted by Bret Baier. It airs live each Monday through Friday at 6:00 PM ET. The show focuses on both reporting and analysis of the day's events, with a primary focus on national political news. The show has been a part of the Fox News program lineup since 1998 and is the number one cable news broadcast in its time slot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402180000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Carl Higbie Frontline</title>
    <desc>Carl Higbie Frontline focuses on providing commonsense news analysis, exposing big government overreach and the media's shortfalls — all while always fighting for American values. Produced from Newsmax's Manhattan studios covering breaking news and exploring key issues such as personal liberty, security, and government transparency.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402180000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hill on NewsNation combines the power of two trusted news sources into one must-watch hour. The Hill, the nation's #1 political website, and NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, team up to define today's most-pressing issues, and question Washington's power brokers on what matters most to the people they serve and what matters most to Americans.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402183000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402183000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402183000 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Ingraham Angle</title>
    <desc>The Ingraham Angle cuts through the Washington chatter to speak directly with unexpected voices and the actual people who are impacted by the news of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>Ring of Honor Wrestling</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting pro-wrestling action from the stars of ROH.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Rob Schmitt Tonight</title>
    <desc>Rob Schmitt Tonight locks in all the late-breaking stories that matter to you, and delivers the up-to-the-minute news you need to hear before turning in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Elizabeth Vargas Reports</title>
    <desc>In-depth coverage of the biggest news stories of the day; NewsNation's home for exclusive and enterprise reporting; hosted live by Elizabeth Vargas.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210200 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>Chef Gordon Ramsay scours the country for the very best line cooks, home chefs, social media stars, food truck owners and everything in between, all competing against one another with the goal of finding the food world's newest superstar. Joined by two elite names in the food world, chefs Nyesha Arrington and Richard Blais, Ramsay and his co-mentors leave no stone unturned, as they each recruit a group of talented chefs and take them under their wings. Ramsay and his friends attempt to bring out the very best in their cooks, as they all try to find "the one." Ramsay firmly believes that as long as a chef has the drive, talent and perseverance, he or she can make that climb to the top. Creativity, consistency and cunning are the recipe for success to make it to the next level, as the competitors adapt to the challenges waiting for them. Chefs compete for a life-changing $250,000 grand prize and the title of "Next Level Chef."</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402203000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>This Old House</title>
    <desc>The mission of This Old House is to demystify the home improvement process and to celebrate the fusion of old world craftsmanship and modern technology. Each season features two renovation projects. Project One traditionally consists of eighteen or so episodes and is filmed in Massachusetts. Project Two is generally taped in a different region of the country to highlight the variety of American architectural styles and renovation issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Jesse Watters Primetime</title>
    <desc>Jesse Watters brings his fresh take to Primetime. Each night, he'll speak with newsmakers from across the country and give Americans a show where straight talk is the only talk, and the obvious will never be left unsaid.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>In the criminal justice system, the people are represented by two separate, yet equally important, groups: the police, who investigate crime; and the district attorneys, who prosecute the offenders. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>9-1-1</title>
    <desc>9-1-1 is a fast-paced exploration into the lives and careers of first responders – cops, paramedics, firefighters – the people who put their lives on the line to save others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402203000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Georgie &amp; Mandy's First Marriage</title>
    <desc>Georgie &amp;amp; Mandy's First Marriage follows Georgie and Mandy as they raise their young family in Texas while navigating the challenges of adulthood, parenting and marriage.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Finnerty</title>
    <desc>Finnerty will look to cut through the noise to bring unfiltered truth, sharp debates, and a focus on the most pressing issues facing America today while standing up for American values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Cuomo</title>
    <desc>Chris Cuomo hosts CUOMO, a no-nonsense show featuring the day's most important news from all perspectives. CUOMO airs weeknights at 8 p.m./7C on NewsNation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>Scrabble</title>
    <desc>Scrabble is a captivating, fast-paced take on the global board-game phenomenon. In each episode, wordsmiths battle it out playing a series of addictive, word-based games to win points and add words to a giant SCRABBLE board in the center of the set.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>The First 48</title>
    <desc>The First 48 follows detectives from around the country during these first critical hours as they race against time to find the suspect. Gritty and fast-paced, it takes viewers behind the scenes of real-life investigations with unprecedented access to crime scenes, autopsies, forensic processing, and interrogations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills</title>
    <desc>The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills offers a glimpse inside the world of luxurious wealth and pampered privilege, where being seen and who you know is everything. These women are in the center of it all and they have the mansions, the cars, and the diamonds to prove it. From heiresses to entrepreneurs to a family of child actresses - they deliver the star power and the drama.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402203000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Ask This Old House</title>
    <desc>The crew at This Old House take on some pretty big projects, which means they can only work on one or two houses a year. But homeowners have a virtual truckload of questions on smaller projects, and the TOH crew is ready to answer. Ask This Old House solves the steady stream of home improvement problems faced by viewers - and the crew even makes house calls!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402203000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Ghosts</title>
    <desc>Samantha and Jay throw caution to the wind when they convert their recently inherited country estate into a bed-and-breakfast. Call it mislaid plans. Not only is the place falling apart, but it's also inhabited by spirits of previous residents -- whom only Samantha can see and hear. Ghosts spins the funny, heartfelt story about a newfound dream that reveals connection and self-discovery aren't just for the living.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Matlock</title>
    <desc>After achieving success in her younger years, the brilliant septuagenarian Madeline Matlock rejoins the work force at a prestigious law firm where she uses her unassuming demeanor and wily tactics to win cases and expose corruption from within.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Rhode Island</title>
    <desc>They may live in the smallest state in the country, but their drama? Extra large. Bravo is expanding the distinguished franchise with The Real Housewives of Rhode Island, spotlighting a fresh, charismatic group of women whose lives intertwine across the storied coastline of New England luxury.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>9-1-1: Nashville</title>
    <desc>A high-octane procedural about heroic first responders, as well as their family saga of power and glamour set in one of America's most diverse and dynamic cities.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Hannity</title>
    <desc>Sean Hannity interviews political figures and newsmakers and offers his own perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>In the criminal justice system, sexually-based offenses are considered especially heinous. In New York City, the dedicated detectives who investigate these vicious felonies are members of an elite squad known as the Special Victims Unit. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Mysteries Unearthed with Danny Trejo</title>
    <desc>Mysteries Unearthed with Danny Trejo examines the fascinating stories surrounding buried artifacts and lost civilizations, shedding light, and offering new insight and information, on various mysteries of the past and present. Anchored by Trejo's affinity for history and his natural curiosity into exploring the unknown and coupled with captivating archival material, expert interviews, and compelling recreations, the series seeks to unearth what the human eye cannot easily detect, as objects, structures and creatures concealed under earth, ice and water are suddenly, and often accidentally, revealed. From ancient animals uncovered as permafrost melts to excavations that make international headlines, each episode explains the significance of these discoveries and offers surprising context to these amazing finds. What exciting revelations can these preserved objects expose about our history and the legends and myths that surround them?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Ladies of London</title>
    <desc>There are cultural differences between England and America in many respects. But that doesn't stop British socialites Annabelle Neilson and Caroline Stanbury from running in similar social circles with Americanexpats Juliet Angus, Caprice Bourret, Marissa Hermer and Noelle Reno, who all enjoy a posh London lifestyle in Ladies of London. The ladies adhere to the city's unwritten rules that one's reputation is everything and respect is not easily earned. Also featured on the docuseries is Julie Montagu, an Illinois native who is married to the heir to the Earl of Sandwich.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Greg Kelly Reports</title>
    <desc>The hardest-hitting stories from coast to coast: We take you from the Beltway to the Rust Belt and beyond — never forgetting we're here to enlighten, expose, inform, and spotlight the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>On Balance with Leland Vittert</title>
    <desc>The day's hottest subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>Trivial Pursuit</title>
    <desc>The all-time classic trivia game Trivial Pursuit is reimagined in a question-packed entertainment format. Gameplay takes place on a giant version of the iconic Trivial Pursuit game board, as contestants battle it out over a range of play-along question categories to win wedges and beat each other to the center. The victor then takes on a dramatic finale against the clock to claim the big money jackpot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Predator Hunters</title>
    <desc>Predator Hunters, following 30-year veteran investigator Detective Tony Godwin and his team within the North Texas-based Internet Crimes Against Children (ICAC) Task Force as they uncover online exploitation and bring perpetrators to justice before they harm any children. The series provides first-hand access to real investigations as Godwin - who has partnered with the FBI, Homeland Security, and the U.S. Secret Service - opens his case files for the first time.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210200 -0400" stop="20260402213200 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Animal Control</title>
    <desc>Animal Control is a workplace comedy following a group of Animal Control workers whose lives are complicated by the fact that animals are simple, but humans are not.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402213200 -0400" stop="20260402220100 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Going Dutch</title>
    <desc>In Going Dutch a decorated, hard-ass colonel is tasked with running the least important U.S. Army base in the world, located in the tulip-hugging, wine-chugging Netherlands.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Hunting Party</title>
    <desc>When a secret prison suffers a mysterious explosion that allows the nation's most violent serial killers to escape, a former profiler is thrust back into a thrilling game of cat and mouse. Alongside a team of soldiers, spies and special agents, she has no choice but to track down and recapture these dangerous criminals… before they kill again.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Gutfeld!</title>
    <desc>Late night show with author, comedian and television host and producer Greg Gutfeld, offering up satirical political and social commentary with a weekly panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
    <desc>The doctors of Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital deal with life-or-death consequences on a daily basis -- it's in one another that they find comfort, friendship and, at times, more than friendship. Together they're discovering that neither medicine nor relationships can be defined in black and white. Real life only comes in shades of grey.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Elsbeth</title>
    <desc>Elsbeth follows Elsbeth Tascioni, an astute but unconventional attorney who utilizes her singular point of view to make unique observations and corner brilliant criminals alongside the NYPD. After leaving her successful legal career in Chicago to tackle a new investigative role in New York City, Elsbeth finds herself jockeying with the toast of the NYPD, Captain C.W. Wagner, a charismatic and revered leader. Working alongside Elsbeth is Officer Kaya Blanke, a stoic and ethical officer who quickly develops an appreciation for Elsbeth's insightful and offbeat ways.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Chris Plante: The Right Squad</title>
    <desc>Chris Plante and his "THE RIGHT SQUAD" are the most interesting, informative and funny group of talking heads in the world! It's a big claim. But it's true!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Katie Pavlich Tonight</title>
    <desc>Katie Pavlich Tonight offers a conservative take on the day's events while welcoming all viewpoints. The goal: cutting through left-right bias in pursuit of plain facts and honest analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220300 -0400" stop="20260402230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Proof Is Out There: Alien Edition</title>
    <desc>In this special edition series of The Proof Is Out There, journalist Tony Harris will present compelling evidence of UFO sightings from around the globe. Are these videos proof that aliens exist? Tony and a team of experts will analyze the evidence and render a verdict.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402230000 -0400" stop="20260403000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402230000 -0400" stop="20260403000000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News @ Night</title>
    <desc>Fox News @ Night is a live hour of hard news and analysis of the most compelling stories from Washington and across the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402230000 -0400" stop="20260403000000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Jesse Weber Live</title>
    <desc>A fresh, fast-paced, and often unexpected take on the day's headlines, diving into the biggest stories through the lens of an expert in legal affairs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402230000 -0400" stop="20260403000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402230000 -0400" stop="20260403000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402231600 -0400" stop="20260402234600 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402233500 -0400" stop="20260403003500 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Late Show with Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert brings his signature satire and comedy to The Late Show with Stephen Colbert, the #1 show in late-night. Featuring bandleader Jon Batiste with his band Stay Human, the Emmy Award-nominated show broadcasts from the historic Ed Sullivan Theater. He talks with an eclectic mix of guests about what is new and relevant in the worlds of politics, entertainment, business, music, technology, and more. Stephen Colbert took over as host, executive producer, and writer of The Late Show on Sept. 8, 2015. Colbert is best known for his work as a television host, writer, actor, and producer, and lest known for his charity work teaching English as a second language on Tunisian date farms. Before joining the CBS family -- and being officially adopted by network president Les Moonves -- Colbert helmed The Colbert Report, which aired nearly 1,500 episodes and required Stephen to wear nearly 1,500 different neckties. The program received two Peabody Awards, two Grammy Awards, and several unwelcome shoulder massages. It won two Emmys for Outstanding Variety Series in 2013 and 2014, both of which appear to have been lost in the move. Colbert is pronounced koʊlˈbɛər, according to Wikipedia. His understudy is William Cavanaugh, who will be hosting The Late Show approximately one-third of the time. Good luck, Bill!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402000000 -0400" stop="20260402020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402000000 -0400" stop="20260402020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403050000 -0400" stop="20260403060000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Morning Call</title>
    <desc>Morning Call, anchored by Morgan Brennan, delivers the essential market intelligence that drives the trading day ahead. The program captures breaking business news as it unfolds and tracks pre‑market equity moves, commodity swings, U.S. futures, and overnight action across global markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403060000 -0400" stop="20260403100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403060000 -0400" stop="20260403090000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk Box</title>
    <desc>Squawk Box is a business news television program that airs at breakfast time on the CNBC network. The program is currently co-hosted by Joe Kernen, Rebecca Quick, and Andrew Ross Sorkin. Since debuting in 1995, the show has spawned a number of versions across CNBC's international channels, many of which employ a similar format. The program title originates from a term used in investment banks and stock brokerages for a permanent voice circuit or intercom used to communicate stock deals or sales priorities; it also may refer to the squawk of a bird, like a peacock, which is the logo of CNBC.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403070000 -0400" stop="20260403090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403070000 -0400" stop="20260403090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403070000 -0400" stop="20260403090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403080000 -0400" stop="20260403100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403090000 -0400" stop="20260403100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403090000 -0400" stop="20260403100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403090000 -0400" stop="20260403110000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk on the Street</title>
    <desc>Squawk on the Street is headquartered live on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange. We are there when the all-important opening bell rings every day. With our exclusive "Eye on the Floor" wireless cameras at the NYSE we take the viewer onto the floor of the exchange, right to the posts where the biggest companies in the world trade. In addition, our exclusive "Tick by Tick" charts track the action of every trade of every stock. Our live market coverage doesn't stop on the corner of Wall and Broad Streets in lower Manhattan. We also have exclusive coverage from the floor of the CME Group in Chicago giving our viewers the treasury, currency and commodity action in real time. In addition, "Squawk on the Street" is also on the air when the closing bells ring throughout Europe. That final hour of European trading starting at 10:30am eastern has proven to be very volatile and has a major impact on all U.S. based markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403100000 -0400" stop="20260403120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403100000 -0400" stop="20260403110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403100000 -0400" stop="20260403120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403110000 -0400" stop="20260403120000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Money Movers</title>
    <desc>Money Movers provides investors with real-time analysis of the stories and the people attracting the attention of the markets each day. Capturing the energy of day's early trading, the program includes the breaking news and numbers driving stocks and sectors, helping investors make critical decisions. "Money Movers" anchors Carl Quintanilla and Sara Eisen speak with the CEOs, government decision-makers and newsmakers who play a relevant role in how money is moving.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403120000 -0400" stop="20260403140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403120000 -0400" stop="20260403130000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Fast Money Halftime Report</title>
    <desc>The hot trades in the market from the floor of the New York Stock Exchange.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403123000 -0400" stop="20260403133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403130000 -0400" stop="20260403140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403130000 -0400" stop="20260403140000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>The Exchange</title>
    <desc>Anchor Kelly Evans reports on the most important stories to today's markets and investors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403133000 -0400" stop="20260403140000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Bold and the Beautiful</title>
    <desc>They created a dynasty where passion rules, they are the Forresters, the first name in Fashion. The Bold and the Beautiful, a world of fashion, glamor and romance. A place where power, money and success are there for the taking in a city where dreams really do come true. Follow the lives and loves of the Forresters on The Bold and the Beautiful...</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403140000 -0400" stop="20260403150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403140000 -0400" stop="20260403150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403140000 -0400" stop="20260403160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403140000 -0400" stop="20260403150000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Power Lunch</title>
    <desc>Power Lunch takes you through the heart of the business day, focusing on real-time market coverage, breaking news and up-to-the-instant stock information. The show delves into the economy, the markets, real estate, media and technology -- any place where there's money to be made. The program features daily contributions from the Nasdaq MarketSite's Times Square studio and coverage from CNBC's Post 9 position on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange, as well as from CNBC's bureaus around the world. "Power Lunch" showcases the best stories of the day from CNBC's roster of digital and television journalists.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403150000 -0400" stop="20260403160000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Let's Make a Deal</title>
    <desc>Let's Make a Deal is an updated version of the classic television game show, hosted by Emmy Award-winner Wayne Brady, where audience members try to win cash and prizes by making wacky deals.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403160000 -0400" stop="20260403180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403180000 -0400" stop="20260403190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403183000 -0400" stop="20260403190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403183000 -0400" stop="20260403190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403183000 -0400" stop="20260403190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403190000 -0400" stop="20260403200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403210000 -0400" channel="STARZ.US">
    <title>Outlander</title>
    <desc>Outlander follows the story of Claire Randall, a married combat nurse from 1945 who is mysteriously swept back in time to 1743, where she is immediately thrown into an unknown world where her life is threatened. When she is forced to marry Jamie, a chivalrous and romantic young Scottish warrior, a passionate affair is ignited that tears Claire's heart between two vastly different men in two irreconcilable lives.The Outlander series, adapted from Diana Gabaldon's international best-selling books, spans the genres of romance, science fiction, history and adventure into one epic tale.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Sheriff Country</title>
    <desc>Sheriff Country focuses on straight-shooting sheriff Mickey Fox, the stepsister of Cal Fire's division chief Sharon Leone, who investigates criminal activity as she patrols the streets of small-town Edgewater while contending with her ex-con father, Wes, who is an off-the-grid marijuana grower, and a mysterious incident involving her wayward daughter.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403203000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Happy's Place</title>
    <desc>Happy's Place follows Bobbie who inherits her father's restaurant and is less than thrilled to discover that she has a new business partner in the half-sister she never knew she had.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403203000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Washington Week with The Atlantic</title>
    <desc>On Washington Week (formerly Washington Week with Gwen Ifill) guest journalists weigh in on issues of the week in this venerable roundtable, the first program ever fed by PBS (previously it had aired on WETA-TV in Washington, D.C., and other East Coast public stations). Though its format is panel discussion, there have been occasional one-on-one interviews, a notable example being host Paul Duke's 1994 White House visit with President Bill Clinton. The series won a DuPont-Columbia University Award in 1974.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403210700 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Gold Rush</title>
    <desc>Gold Rush follows six men who, in the face of an economic meltdown, risk everything - their families, their dignity, and in some cases, their lives - to strike it rich mining for gold in the wilds of Alaska. Inspired by his father Jack, Todd Hoffman of Sandy, Oregon, leads a group of greenhorn miners to forge a new frontier and save their families from dire straits. While leasing a gold claim in Alaska, Todd and his company of newbies face the grandeur of Alaska as well as its hardships, including an impending winter that will halt operations and the opportunity to strike gold. In an effort to keep the operation running, the team takes fate into their own hands with a make or break venture that will change their lives forever.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403203000 -0400" stop="20260403210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Firing Line with Margaret Hoover</title>
    <desc>Firing Line with Margaret Hoover maintains the character of the original, providing a platform that is diligent in its commitment to civility and the rigorous exchange of opinion. Interviews and debates will highlight leading lights from the left and right, complemented by archival footage from the original Firing Line to remind viewers of longstanding conservative and liberal arguments, where they've been disproved or reinforced over time.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403210000 -0400" stop="20260403220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Fire Country</title>
    <desc>In Fire Country, seeking redemption and a shortened prison sentence, young convict Bode Donovan joins a firefighting program that returns him to his small Northern California hometown, where he and other inmates work alongside elite firefighters to extinguish massive blazes across the region.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403210000 -0400" stop="20260403220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The UnBelievable with Dan Aykroyd</title>
    <desc>Did you know that a brown bear became a war hero for the Allies during WWII? Or that a flying lawnmower once killed a spectator at a football game? What about the story of the 19th century doctor who ate vomit to understand how yellow fever is transmitted?If you haven't, then brace yourself for The UnBelievable with Dan Aykroyd.Each hour-long episode will open up our cabinet of curiosities to reveal the strangest-but-true stories in human history, brought to life through dynamic recreation, compelling graphics, and arresting archival. These seemingly tall tales all actually happened, and our cast of experts dives into the historical record to tell you how and why.It's a bizarro barrage of people, places and events that prove just how weird our world can be.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403210000 -0400" stop="20260403220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403210000 -0400" stop="20260403220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403210700 -0400" stop="20260403230700 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Gold Rush: Mine Rescue with Freddy &amp; Juan</title>
    <desc>Freddy Dodge is no stranger when it comes to gold mining. With nearly 40 years of mining under his belt, he's known around the world as the "Gold Guru" and the person struggling mine owners call when they're striking out. Now he's going on the road to help struggling mine owners to hit the motherlode in Gold Rush: Mine Rescue with Freddy &amp;amp; Juan. To help him turnaround the operations, Freddy has teamed up with expert mechanic and fellow Gold Rush miner Juan Ibarra. At each location, the mining duo will use their knowledge of geology, prospecting, drilling and testing to get back on the paydirt. But it isn't just running their dirt faster. It's about making the operations better, and more importantly, running cheaper.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403220000 -0400" stop="20260403230000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Boston Blue</title>
    <desc>In Boston Blue, NYPD Detective Danny Reagan takes a position with Boston PD. Once in Boston, he is paired with Detective Lena Silver, the eldest daughter of a prominent law enforcement family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403220000 -0400" stop="20260404000000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Dateline NBC presents in-depth coverage of news stories. Rather than just reading news reports, as most news shows do, the reporters for this show research their subjects and interview the people closely involved to create an informative work of investigative journalism.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403220000 -0400" stop="20260403230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403220000 -0400" stop="20260403230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403220300 -0400" stop="20260403230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Proof Is Out There</title>
    <desc>The Proof Is Out There takes an in-depth look at some of the most incredible and thought provoking videos of unexplained phenomena and mysterious must-see moments of all time. Each half-hour episode explores and analyzes the full story of each irregularity in question from bizarre footage of people seemingly immune to lightning, to a fifty-foot snake, apocalyptic sounds in a man's backyard, enigmatic creatures, and UFOS that split and dive underwater. Through expert examination and the use of the latest technologies, The Proof Is Out There aims to get to the bottom of what's real? What's fake? And everything in between.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403230000 -0400" stop="20260404000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403230000 -0400" stop="20260404000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403230000 -0400" stop="20260404000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403000000 -0400" stop="20260403020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403000000 -0400" stop="20260403020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404060000 -0400" stop="20260404100000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox &amp; Friends Weekend</title>
    <desc>Early risers get a chance to experience their own news, information and entertainment that "FOX and Friends" viewers get during the week with this weekend version of the show. In addition to reporting and discussion of the latest news, the show features weather forecasts to help viewers plan their weekend activities.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404070000 -0400" stop="20260404100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404070000 -0400" stop="20260404100000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Weekend Morning in America</title>
    <desc>NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, today announced the debut of the weekend edition of Morning in America with Hena Doba. The new weekend show will premiere on Saturday, January 27, and will be anchored by journalist Hena Doba on Saturdays and Sundays from 7-10 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404070000 -0400" stop="20260404080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404070000 -0400" stop="20260404090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Saturday Morning</title>
    <desc>Hosts Jeff Glor, Dana Jacobson and Michelle Miller provide original reporting, breaking news, and profiles of leading figures in culture and the arts from the Times Square studio on the Saturday edition of the CBS morning news family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404090000 -0400" stop="20260404100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Smerconish</title>
    <desc>After serving as an MSNBC contributor and guest-host on the network for four years, TV and radio personality Michael Smerconish believed he was ready to head a show of his own. CNN agreed, and thus was born Smerconish, an hour long Saturday morning program that takes after its host's independent views. Using a topical, conversational format, he aims for the TV show to be an extension of his weekday radio broadcast, with free-flowing topics and the ability to discuss issues that strike a chord with the audience. Along the same lines, he thinks it's important to present the content in an engaging manner, free of my-way-or-the-highway ideology. Smerconish, who has a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania, is also a New York Times' best-selling author.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404090000 -0400" stop="20260404110000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>America Right Now</title>
    <desc>Tom Basile tackles the week's biggest stories with top talkers from politics, Hollywood, and across America.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404100000 -0400" stop="20260404120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Saturday in America</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers across the political landscape, Saturday in America with Kayleigh McEnany will provide a comprehensive look at the headlines dominating the news cycle.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404100000 -0400" stop="20260404130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Velshi</title>
    <desc>MSNBC anchor Ali Velshi brings his sharp analysis and point-of-view to weekend mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404110000 -0400" stop="20260404120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Amanpour Hour</title>
    <desc>Christiane Amanpour, CNN's chief international anchor, brings valuable insight to the biggest global and domestic news stories of the week.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404120000 -0400" stop="20260404140000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News Live</title>
    <desc>The latest political and socio-economic news and updates from around the world, live.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404120000 -0400" stop="20260404130000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Oceanfront Property Hunt</title>
    <desc>Prospective buyers look to make their dream of living by the ocean a reality as they hunt for oceanfront properties along the Atlantic coastline.Who doesn't dream of living by the ocean? Oceanfront Property Hunt follows prospective buyers looking to purchase their first oceanfront home. Our buyers are families from all walks of life. In some episodes, we'll meet people looking for a unique fixer-upper. Or we'll follow their search for a modest family home. Other folks want a spacious, turn-key dream home along the rugged coastline.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404123000 -0400" stop="20260404133000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Oceanfront Property Hunt</title>
    <desc>Prospective buyers look to make their dream of living by the ocean a reality as they hunt for oceanfront properties along the Atlantic coastline.Who doesn't dream of living by the ocean? Oceanfront Property Hunt follows prospective buyers looking to purchase their first oceanfront home. Our buyers are families from all walks of life. In some episodes, we'll meet people looking for a unique fixer-upper. Or we'll follow their search for a modest family home. Other folks want a spacious, turn-key dream home along the rugged coastline.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404130000 -0400" stop="20260404160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404150000 -0400" stop="20260404170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX Report with Jon Scott</title>
    <desc>FNC's signature weekend newscast, FOX Report with Jon Scott, anchored by Jon Scott, highlights the latest developments and breaking news in the U.S. and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404170000 -0400" stop="20260404180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404170000 -0400" stop="20260404200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Big Weekend Show</title>
    <desc>Rotating panelists will discuss the big news of the day. Join the hosts live for reaction to the issues facing the country right now and the top stories Americans are buzzing about.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404180000 -0400" stop="20260404210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend Primetime</title>
    <desc>A diverse panel of journalists navigates the week's biggest stories and sets the agenda for the week ahead, offering context, analysis, and civil debate in a three-hour Saturday and Sunday evening format.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404200000 -0400" stop="20260404210000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Storage Wars: Back to the Locker</title>
    <desc>Storage Wars: Back to the Locker refers to a series of episodes within the larger "Storage Wars" series, where the focus is on the competitive bidding and treasure hunting within abandoned storage units. These episodes continue the main show's premise of professional buyers vying to acquire the contents of storage lockers, often with the hope of finding valuable items among the discarded belongings. The "Back to the Locker" part emphasizes the return to the core concept of exploring what lies behind the doors of these storage units.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404210000 -0400" stop="20260404220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Storage Wars follows professional buyers and their teams as they scour repossessed storage units in search of hidden treasure. Part gamblers, part detectives, these auction pros have found everything from coffins to the world's most valuable comic book collection, paying as little as ten dollars for items valued in the millions.Each episode of Storage Wars follows a group of bidders as they get a quick peek inside the units, aided only by the beam of a flashlight. They then must assess on the spot if the unit is worth a bid and how high they will actually go to grasp the gold. The high-stakes fun begins as we see if the resulting buy is full of mostly trash... or true treasure.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404220100 -0400" stop="20260404230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Duck Dynasty: The Revival</title>
    <desc>Duck Dynasty: The Revival centers on Willie and Korie Robertson as they navigate life with their growing family of adult children and grandchildren, now part of the next generation carrying on the Robertson legacy at their Louisiana homestead. As the family business expands beyond ducks, Willie and Korie bring their signature wit and down-home charm while they explore the future of Duck Commander, support their children through marriage, parenthood, and entrepreneurship, and work to keep their legacy alive. However, Willie quickly realizes that this next generation isn't as Robertson as he originally thought.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404232900 -0400" stop="20260405010200 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Saturday Night Live</title>
    <desc>Saturday Night Live is an Emmy Award-winning late-night comedy showcase.Since its inception in 1975, "SNL" has launched the careers of many of the brightest comedy performers of their generation. As The New York Times noted on the occasion of the show's Emmy-winning 25th Anniversary special in 1999, "in defiance of both time and show business convention, 'SNL' is still the most pervasive influence on the art of comedy in contemporary culture." At the close of the century, "Saturday Night Live" placed seventh on Entertainment Weekly's list of the Top 100 Entertainers of the past fifty years.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405060000 -0400" stop="20260405100000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox &amp; Friends Weekend</title>
    <desc>Early risers get a chance to experience their own news, information and entertainment that "FOX and Friends" viewers get during the week with this weekend version of the show. In addition to reporting and discussion of the latest news, the show features weather forecasts to help viewers plan their weekend activities.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405070000 -0400" stop="20260405100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405070000 -0400" stop="20260405100000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Weekend Morning in America</title>
    <desc>NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, today announced the debut of the weekend edition of Morning in America with Hena Doba. The new weekend show will premiere on Saturday, January 27, and will be anchored by journalist Hena Doba on Saturdays and Sundays from 7-10 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405070000 -0400" stop="20260405080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405080000 -0400" stop="20260405090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist</title>
    <desc>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist delivers morning news, videos, and photos about current events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405090000 -0400" stop="20260405100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Meet the Press</title>
    <desc>For almost as long as there has been television, there's been Meet the Press. The hourlong Sunday morning public affairs program has featured interviews with countless U.S. and world leaders, and has reviewed, analyzed and discussed the news of the week -- all while looking toward the week ahead.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405090000 -0400" stop="20260405103000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS News Sunday Morning</title>
    <desc>CBS News Sunday Morning is a early morning news and magazine program that airs on Sunday's on CBS.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405090000 -0400" stop="20260405100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>State of the Union with Jake Tapper and Dana Bash</title>
    <desc>Jake Tapper and Dana Bash bring together major newsmakers, analysts and experts to tackle pressing domestic issues and diplomacy on the global stage.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405100000 -0400" stop="20260405130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Velshi</title>
    <desc>MSNBC anchor Ali Velshi brings his sharp analysis and point-of-view to weekend mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405100000 -0400" stop="20260405110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Sunday Morning Futures with Maria Bartiromo</title>
    <desc>As part of her role as FOX Business Network's global markets editor, business journalist Maria Bartiromo hosts this weekly Sunday morning show on FBN sister network FOX News Channel Sunday Morning Futures with Maria Bartiromo that focuses more on the general economy than the stock market specifically. The hourlong show provides viewers with information about how recent news events affect the economy. In addition, Bartiromo interviews business leaders and newsmakers on topics that include job creation and investment opportunities.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405100000 -0400" stop="20260405110000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill Sunday</title>
    <desc>The Hill Sunday is NewsNation's live public affairs show hosted by Chris Stirewalt.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405100000 -0400" stop="20260405110000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>This Week</title>
    <desc>This Week  is hosted by former Clinton White House staffer and current co-anchor of ABC's weekday morning news show "Good Morning America", George Stephanopoulos offers a look at current events with a focus on the politics of the day. Each week's show includes interviews with top newsmakers (including some of the nation's top political leaders) as well as a roundtable discussion, usually featuring journalists from ABC and other news organizations, of the week's happenings. Since 2008, the program has broadcast from a studio at the Newseum in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405103000 -0400" stop="20260405113000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Face the Nation</title>
    <desc>Face the Nation is a news interview program which airs every Sunday morning, live from the CBS studio in Washington D.C. It is dedicated to interviewing newsmakers on the latest issues. Guests include government leaders, politicians, and international figures in the news. CBS News… More correspondents engage the guests in a lively roundtable discussion focusing on current topics. The show started on November 7th, 1954, and was originally broadcast on both CBS Television and Radio Networks. After close to two decades, the program was taken off CBS radio.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405110000 -0400" stop="20260405120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Sunday Briefing</title>
    <desc>The Sunday Briefing will tackle all facets of the White House beat, including the President of the United States' national and international moves as well as the key issues impacting the administration.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405120000 -0400" stop="20260405140000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News Live</title>
    <desc>The latest political and socio-economic news and updates from around the world, live.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405130000 -0400" stop="20260405160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405140000 -0400" stop="20260405150000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>FOX News Sunday</title>
    <desc>FOX News Sunday, anchored by Shannon Bream, is a one-hour live broadcast that airs Sunday mornings across the nation on FOX Broadcasting Company, and is presented again on FNC during the afternoon. This show's weekly guest roster is among the most diverse in Sunday morning talk, featuring interviews with political, business and public affairs newsmakers from the U.S. and abroad</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405150000 -0400" stop="20260405170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX Report with Jon Scott</title>
    <desc>FNC's signature weekend newscast, FOX Report with Jon Scott, anchored by Jon Scott, highlights the latest developments and breaking news in the U.S. and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405170000 -0400" stop="20260405180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405170000 -0400" stop="20260405200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Big Weekend Show</title>
    <desc>Rotating panelists will discuss the big news of the day. Join the hosts live for reaction to the issues facing the country right now and the top stories Americans are buzzing about.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405180000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend Primetime</title>
    <desc>A diverse panel of journalists navigates the week's biggest stories and sets the agenda for the week ahead, offering context, analysis, and civil debate in a three-hour Saturday and Sunday evening format.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405190000 -0400" stop="20260405200000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>ABC's longest-running primetime entertainment show, America's Funniest Home Videos, returns for season 36 this fall with the same mission -- giving families something genuinely funny to enjoy together on Sunday nights."AFV," the longest-running primetime entertainment show in ABC history, returns for season 36 with the same mission - to provide viewers with hysterical moments that fly by at a dizzying pace.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405200000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>The Faithful: Women of the Bible</title>
    <desc>The Faithful: Women of the Bible is inspired by the best-selling book of all time, the Bible, and showcases a faithful dramatization of the Book of Genesis as told through the eyes of the courageous and passionate, yet flawed women whose descendants would shape the future of faith as we know it today. Dimensional, dramatic, intimate, even surprising, The Faithful: Women of the Bible is about discovering and losing love, the challenges of marriage, the joys and heartbreak of children, confronting temptation, and finding faith. Episodes of The Faithful will be told through the lens of five of The Old Testament's most legendary women: Sarah and her maidservant Hagar, Sarah's great-niece Rebekah, and Rebekah's nieces, sisters Leah and Rachel.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405200000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Marshals</title>
    <desc>Marshals stars Luke Grimes reprising his role as Kayce Dutton. With the Yellowstone Ranch behind him, Dutton joins an elite unit of U.S. Marshals, combining his skills as a cowboy and Navy SEAL to bring range justice to Montana. Kayce and his teammates - Pete Calvin, Belle Skinner, Andrea Cruz and Miles Kittle - must balance the high psychological cost of serving as the last line of defense in the region's war on violence with their duty to their families, which for Kayce includes his son Tate and his confidants Thomas Rainwater and Mo from the Broken Rock reservation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405200000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Atlanta</title>
    <desc>An up-close and personal look at life in Hotlanta, The Real Housewives of Atlanta follows five glamorous southern belles as they balance motherhood, demanding careers and a fast-paced social calendar, and shows what life is like in the most exclusive areas of Atlanta. These driven and ambitious women prove that they're not just "housewives," but entrepreneurs, doting mothers and classy southern women. These ladies show the world what it takes to live large in some of the hottest zip codes in the south.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405200000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Naked and Afraid</title>
    <desc>Each week on Naked and Afraid, a new pair of complete and total strangers - one man and one woman - will find themselves stranded in and, quite literally, exposed to one of the world's most extreme weather environments. This duo will be left high and dry with no food, no water... and no clothes. They must survive on their own for a full 21 days, with nothing but one personal item each and the knowledge that the only prize is their pride and sense of accomplishment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405200000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>American Pickers</title>
    <desc>This isn't your grandmother's antiquing. The American Pickers are on a mission to recycle America, even if it means diving into countless piles of grimy junk or getting chased off a gun-wielding homeowner's land. Hitting back roads from coast to coast, the Pickers earn a living by restoring forgotten relics to their former glory, transforming one person's trash into another's treasure. The show follows the team as they scour the country for hidden gems in junkyards, basements, garages and barns, meeting quirky characters and hearing their amazing stories. If you think the antique business is all about upscale boutiques and buttoned-up dealers, this show may change your mind – and teach you a thing or two about American history along the way.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>DTF St. Louis</title>
    <desc>DTF St. Louis is a darkly comedic limited series about a love triangle between three adults experiencing middle-age malaise, that leads to one of them ending up dead.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Sunday Night in America with Trey Gowdy</title>
    <desc>Trey Gowdy will offer insightful analysis and a new outlook on the latest issues facing the country. Capitalizing on his experiences as a former prosecutor and Chairman of the House Oversight and Government Reform Committee, the former South Carolina Congressman will utilize his signature mixture of wisdom, humor and historical references to break down the latest legal and political news from across the nation. "Sunday Night in America" will offer seasoned perspective while providing viewers with the tools and information to draw their own conclusions. The program will also feature timely, solution-oriented interviews with decision makers and Washington insiders, as well as original stories of triumph and success highlighting why Americans should be optimistic about the future.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>The Faithful: Women of the Bible</title>
    <desc>The Faithful: Women of the Bible is inspired by the best-selling book of all time, the Bible, and showcases a faithful dramatization of the Book of Genesis as told through the eyes of the courageous and passionate, yet flawed women whose descendants would shape the future of faith as we know it today. Dimensional, dramatic, intimate, even surprising, The Faithful: Women of the Bible is about discovering and losing love, the challenges of marriage, the joys and heartbreak of children, confronting temptation, and finding faith. Episodes of The Faithful will be told through the lens of five of The Old Testament's most legendary women: Sarah and her maidservant Hagar, Sarah's great-niece Rebekah, and Rebekah's nieces, sisters Leah and Rachel.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Tracker</title>
    <desc>Tracker features lone-wolf survivalist Colter Shaw, who roams the country as a "reward seeker," using his expert tracking skills to help private citizens and law enforcement to solve all manner of mysteries while contending with his own fractured family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Rhode Island</title>
    <desc>They may live in the smallest state in the country, but their drama? Extra large. Bravo is expanding the distinguished franchise with The Real Housewives of Rhode Island, spotlighting a fresh, charismatic group of women whose lives intertwine across the storied coastline of New England luxury.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Filthy Fortunes</title>
    <desc>Filthy Fortunes spotlights Matt Paxton and his team as they complete the most squalid and hazardous jobs to help everyday Americans cash in. Before the treasure hunt can begin, Matt will assess the property to determine potential costs associated with the clean-out and estimate the value of items hidden inside the hoard. With each property, he wagers that he'll discover enough to cover all the costs and make a profit. Matt takes all the risk, and if all goes according to plan, it's a win-win situation for both him and the client.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>History's Greatest Picks with Mike Wolfe</title>
    <desc>Mike Wolfe has spent decades tracking down elusive treasures, hidden gems and bargaining with awesome collectors of the past, but now, it's Mike's turn to share that history by revealing the stories of extraordinary finds by ordinary people.History's Greatest Picks with Mike Wolfe explores the epic journeys, captivating tales, and astonishing monetary values behind legendary treasures, relics, and artifacts from history. Mike draws on his decades of experience and infectious curiosity to showcase some of history's most unbelievable and high valued items—from iconic vintage cars and motorcycles to pop culture touchstones, rare collectibles, and historic oddities.With expert insight, compelling historical context, and Mike guiding the audience through these stories, the series reveals surprising new details about how these extraordinary objects have changed hands and risen dramatically in value over time—bringing history to life, one unforgettable pick at a time.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405220000 -0400" stop="20260405230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>One Nation with Brian Kilmeade</title>
    <desc>One Nation with Brian Kilmeade: In-depth analysis of the issues and stories that matter most to Americans, while offering context and solutions to help bring the country together.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405220000 -0400" stop="20260405230000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Watson</title>
    <desc>In Watson a year after the death of his friend and partner Sherlock Holmes at the hands of Moriarty, Dr. John Watson resumes his medical career as the head of a clinic dedicated to treating rare disorders. Watson's old life isn't done with him, though — Moriarty and Watson are set to write their own chapter of a story that has fascinated audiences for more than a century. Watson is a medical show with a strong investigative spine, featuring a modern version of one of history's greatest detectives as he turns his attention from solving crimes to addressing the greatest mystery of all: illness, and the ways it disrupts our lives.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405220000 -0400" stop="20260405230000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>Rooster</title>
    <desc>Rooster follows a middle aged author navigating a complicated relationship with his daughter.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405220000 -0400" stop="20260405230000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Betrayal: Secrets &amp; Lies</title>
    <desc>Based on the No. 1 true crime podcast, new weekly docuseries featuring a new story each week. The eight episodes follow lives undone by unthinkable betrayals and the courage it takes to survive scandalous confessions, secret lives, terrifying acts of violence, financial ruin and more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405220000 -0400" stop="20260405230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Whole Story with Anderson Cooper</title>
    <desc>The Whole Story with Anderson Cooper is a collection of unique and immersive single-subject, one-hour episodes from CNN's Emmy®  and Peabody Award-winning long-form storytelling team.  The recurring weekly series will be hosted by Cooper and showcase character-driven stories, special interviews, profiles, and investigative deep dives featuring reporting from CNN's anchors and correspondents.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405223000 -0400" stop="20260405230000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>The Comeback</title>
    <desc>The limited comedy series stars Lisa Kudrow as the embattled Valerie Cherish, a fading TV "It Girl" who was once so desperate to stay in the spotlight that she allowed cameras to follow her every move as she appeared on a new sitcom - with disastrous results. Now, it's ten years later, and Valerie thinks she has it all figured out this time. She doesn't.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406050000 -0400" stop="20260406060000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Morning Call</title>
    <desc>Morning Call, anchored by Morgan Brennan, delivers the essential market intelligence that drives the trading day ahead. The program captures breaking business news as it unfolds and tracks pre‑market equity moves, commodity swings, U.S. futures, and overnight action across global markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406060000 -0400" stop="20260406090000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk Box</title>
    <desc>Squawk Box is a business news television program that airs at breakfast time on the CNBC network. The program is currently co-hosted by Joe Kernen, Rebecca Quick, and Andrew Ross Sorkin. Since debuting in 1995, the show has spawned a number of versions across CNBC's international channels, many of which employ a similar format. The program title originates from a term used in investment banks and stock brokerages for a permanent voice circuit or intercom used to communicate stock deals or sales priorities; it also may refer to the squawk of a bird, like a peacock, which is the logo of CNBC.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406060000 -0400" stop="20260406100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406070000 -0400" stop="20260406090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406070000 -0400" stop="20260406090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406070000 -0400" stop="20260406090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406080000 -0400" stop="20260406100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406090000 -0400" stop="20260406110000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk on the Street</title>
    <desc>Squawk on the Street is headquartered live on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange. We are there when the all-important opening bell rings every day. With our exclusive "Eye on the Floor" wireless cameras at the NYSE we take the viewer onto the floor of the exchange, right to the posts where the biggest companies in the world trade. In addition, our exclusive "Tick by Tick" charts track the action of every trade of every stock. Our live market coverage doesn't stop on the corner of Wall and Broad Streets in lower Manhattan. We also have exclusive coverage from the floor of the CME Group in Chicago giving our viewers the treasury, currency and commodity action in real time. In addition, "Squawk on the Street" is also on the air when the closing bells ring throughout Europe. That final hour of European trading starting at 10:30am eastern has proven to be very volatile and has a major impact on all U.S. based markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406090000 -0400" stop="20260406100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406100000 -0400" stop="20260406120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406100000 -0400" stop="20260406110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406100000 -0400" stop="20260406120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406110000 -0400" stop="20260406120000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Money Movers</title>
    <desc>Money Movers provides investors with real-time analysis of the stories and the people attracting the attention of the markets each day. Capturing the energy of day's early trading, the program includes the breaking news and numbers driving stocks and sectors, helping investors make critical decisions. "Money Movers" anchors Carl Quintanilla and Sara Eisen speak with the CEOs, government decision-makers and newsmakers who play a relevant role in how money is moving.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406120000 -0400" stop="20260406140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406120000 -0400" stop="20260406130000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Fast Money Halftime Report</title>
    <desc>The hot trades in the market from the floor of the New York Stock Exchange.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406130000 -0400" stop="20260406140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406130000 -0400" stop="20260406140000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>The Exchange</title>
    <desc>Anchor Kelly Evans reports on the most important stories to today's markets and investors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406133000 -0400" stop="20260406140000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Bold and the Beautiful</title>
    <desc>They created a dynasty where passion rules, they are the Forresters, the first name in Fashion. The Bold and the Beautiful, a world of fashion, glamor and romance. A place where power, money and success are there for the taking in a city where dreams really do come true. Follow the lives and loves of the Forresters on The Bold and the Beautiful...</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406140000 -0400" stop="20260406150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406140000 -0400" stop="20260406160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406140000 -0400" stop="20260406150000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Power Lunch</title>
    <desc>Power Lunch takes you through the heart of the business day, focusing on real-time market coverage, breaking news and up-to-the-instant stock information. The show delves into the economy, the markets, real estate, media and technology -- any place where there's money to be made. The program features daily contributions from the Nasdaq MarketSite's Times Square studio and coverage from CNBC's Post 9 position on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange, as well as from CNBC's bureaus around the world. "Power Lunch" showcases the best stories of the day from CNBC's roster of digital and television journalists.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406160000 -0400" stop="20260406180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406180000 -0400" stop="20260406190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406190000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406203000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>St. Denis Medical</title>
    <desc>St. Denis Medical is a mockumentary about an underfunded, understaffed Oregon hospital where the dedicated doctors and nurses try their best to treat patients while maintaining their own sanity.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Below Deck Down Under</title>
    <desc>Below Deck Down Under follows yachties as they work and play on a super-yacht sailing around Australia. The series also showcases a unique additional challenge for the crew as the guests expect not only an adventure on the water but also underwater with scuba diving and other activities as some of the main attractions of the region.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Extracted</title>
    <desc>Extracted features 12 untrained competitors attempting to survive extremely grueling conditions, perilous terrain, and the threat of fearsome predators in the unforgiving Canadian wilderness. Meanwhile, some miles away, their family members are locked down at a secluded headquarters watching them navigate their dangerous surroundings alone via a 24/7 live feed. The fate of each untrained contestant in the wilderness lies in the hands of their family members back in HQ. Each amateur survivalist's family has the power to decide whether their loved one has what it takes to brave the elements and fight to be the last one standing, or whether the family will push the ominous "Extract" button and remove their loved one and their whole family from the competition. Extracted begs the question: how far will their loved ones let them go for a chance for their family to win $250,000?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406220000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>American Idol</title>
    <desc>American Idol is an American singing competition show, where contestants perform in front of a panel of star judges, representing the music industry. The winner is determined by viewers' vote.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406203000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Neighborhood</title>
    <desc>The Neighborhood telling about what happens when the friendly guy in the Midwest moves his family to a neighborhood in Los Angeles where not everyone looks like him or appreciates his extreme neighborliness. When Dave Johnson and his family arrive from Michigan, they're unfazed that their new dream home is located in a community quite different from their small town. However, their opinionated next-door neighbor, Calvin Butler, is wary of the newcomers, certain that they'll disrupt the culture on the block. Dave realizes that fitting into their new community is more complex than he expected, but if he can find a way to connect with Calvin, they have an excellent chance of making their new neighborhood their home.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Antiques Roadshow</title>
    <desc>Antiques Roadshow turns 20! PBS' most-watched ongoing series celebrates 20 seasons with a new look, new hidden treasures and more appraisals than ever. Tune in to discover finds from Spokane, Washington; Tucson, Arizona; Little Rock, Arkansas; Charleston, South Carolina; Cleveland, Ohio; and Omaha, Nebraska. - Mondays, beginning January 4, 8:00-9:00 p.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Contraband: Seized at the Airport</title>
    <desc>Follows Dept of Homeland Security officers at five different airports across the country, from San Francisco, Detroit, Newark, Atlanta, and Honolulu, as they search for contraband both leaving and coming into the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406203000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Fall and Rise of Reggie Dinkins</title>
    <desc>The Fall and Rise of Reggie Dinkins focuses on a disgraced former football player, who is on a mission to rehabilitate his image.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406203000 -0400" stop="20260406213000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Neighborhood</title>
    <desc>The Neighborhood telling about what happens when the friendly guy in the Midwest moves his family to a neighborhood in Los Angeles where not everyone looks like him or appreciates his extreme neighborliness. When Dave Johnson and his family arrive from Michigan, they're unfazed that their new dream home is located in a community quite different from their small town. However, their opinionated next-door neighbor, Calvin Butler, is wary of the newcomers, certain that they'll disrupt the culture on the block. Dave realizes that fitting into their new community is more complex than he expected, but if he can find a way to connect with Calvin, they have an excellent chance of making their new neighborhood their home.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Voice</title>
    <desc>The Voice is a singing competition where famous musicians serve as coaches to mentor aspiring artists through a series of blind auditions, battles, and live performances, with the ultimate goal of finding and crowning America's best new vocal talent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Rachel Maddow Show</title>
    <desc>With honesty and rigor, Rachel Maddow uniquely connects dots to advance stories on her show The Rachel Maddow Show. By exposing the layers of complex issues, she reveals their significance to viewers. In her irreverent style, Maddow transcends the narrative and provides unique perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Memory of a Killer</title>
    <desc>Memory of a Killer is a dramatic thriller about a hitman who develops early onset Alzheimer's. Angelo lives a double life as an assassin and a family man - which all worked out well until he was hit with early onset Alzheimer's. Now his worlds are colliding, putting his family in danger.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406213000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>Born to Bowl</title>
    <desc>Born to Bowl takes viewers inside the colorful world of professional bowling, chronicling five stars of the sport – Kyle Troup, Anthony Simonsen, EJ Tackett, Cameron Crowe, and Jason Belmonte – as they chase glory, respect, and much-needed prize money on the Professional Bowlers Association (PBA) Tour.Set within bowling's blue‑collar culture, the series examines a familiar American family pastime that evokes myriad pop cultural references and reveals a quirky sport with ancient roots shaped as much by personality and persistence as by skill and precision. Every season, members of the PBA Tour travel from tournament to tournament with their balls in tow, fighting for victories from Akron to Reno, often needing to share budget hotel rooms along the way. At different stages of their careers, each man balances their ambition and love of the sport with the uncertainty of a profession built on week‑to‑week performance and earnings that often require them to take day jobs to make a living.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406221500 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Top Chef</title>
    <desc>Top Chef is a competition show in which chefs competing against each other in various culinary challenges, judged by the team of professional chefs and notable people from food industry.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>History's Greatest Mysteries</title>
    <desc>History's Greatest Mysteries will investigate a wide range of historically compelling topics and the mysteries surrounding each including the Titanic, D.B. Cooper, Roswell, John Wilkes Booth, and more. Each program within the franchise will showcase fresh, new evidence and perspectives including never-before-released documents to the general public, personal diaries and DNA evidence to unearth brand-new information about these infamous and enigmatic chapters in history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406220000 -0400" stop="20260406230000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The Rookie</title>
    <desc>The Rookie is inspired by a true story. John Nolan is the oldest rookie in the LAPD. At an age where most are at the peak of their career, Nolan cast aside his comfortable, small town life and moved to L.A. to pursue his dream of being a cop. Now, surrounded by rookies twenty years his junior, Nolan must navigate the dangerous, humorous and unpredictable world of a "young" cop, determined to make his second shot at life count.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406220000 -0400" stop="20260406233000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Independent Lens</title>
    <desc>Independent Lens is an anthology of independent documentary films.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406220000 -0400" stop="20260406230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406220000 -0400" stop="20260406230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406220300 -0400" stop="20260406230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>History's Greatest Warriors</title>
    <desc>History's Greatest Warriors explores the step-by-step process to produce some of history's most infamous and lethal warriors. Each episode introduces viewers to a legendary fighter - from Samurai, Spartans, Delta Force, Navy SEALS, Vikings, and more - and breaks down the selection, training, weaponry, and combat expertise specifically used.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406230000 -0400" stop="20260407000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406230000 -0400" stop="20260407000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406000000 -0400" stop="20260406020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406000000 -0400" stop="20260406020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407050000 -0400" stop="20260407060000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Morning Call</title>
    <desc>Morning Call, anchored by Morgan Brennan, delivers the essential market intelligence that drives the trading day ahead. The program captures breaking business news as it unfolds and tracks pre‑market equity moves, commodity swings, U.S. futures, and overnight action across global markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407060000 -0400" stop="20260407090000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk Box</title>
    <desc>Squawk Box is a business news television program that airs at breakfast time on the CNBC network. The program is currently co-hosted by Joe Kernen, Rebecca Quick, and Andrew Ross Sorkin. Since debuting in 1995, the show has spawned a number of versions across CNBC's international channels, many of which employ a similar format. The program title originates from a term used in investment banks and stock brokerages for a permanent voice circuit or intercom used to communicate stock deals or sales priorities; it also may refer to the squawk of a bird, like a peacock, which is the logo of CNBC.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407060000 -0400" stop="20260407100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407070000 -0400" stop="20260407090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407070000 -0400" stop="20260407090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407070000 -0400" stop="20260407090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407080000 -0400" stop="20260407100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407090000 -0400" stop="20260407110000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Squawk on the Street</title>
    <desc>Squawk on the Street is headquartered live on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange. We are there when the all-important opening bell rings every day. With our exclusive "Eye on the Floor" wireless cameras at the NYSE we take the viewer onto the floor of the exchange, right to the posts where the biggest companies in the world trade. In addition, our exclusive "Tick by Tick" charts track the action of every trade of every stock. Our live market coverage doesn't stop on the corner of Wall and Broad Streets in lower Manhattan. We also have exclusive coverage from the floor of the CME Group in Chicago giving our viewers the treasury, currency and commodity action in real time. In addition, "Squawk on the Street" is also on the air when the closing bells ring throughout Europe. That final hour of European trading starting at 10:30am eastern has proven to be very volatile and has a major impact on all U.S. based markets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407090000 -0400" stop="20260407100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407100000 -0400" stop="20260407120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407100000 -0400" stop="20260407110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407100000 -0400" stop="20260407120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407110000 -0400" stop="20260407120000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Money Movers</title>
    <desc>Money Movers provides investors with real-time analysis of the stories and the people attracting the attention of the markets each day. Capturing the energy of day's early trading, the program includes the breaking news and numbers driving stocks and sectors, helping investors make critical decisions. "Money Movers" anchors Carl Quintanilla and Sara Eisen speak with the CEOs, government decision-makers and newsmakers who play a relevant role in how money is moving.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407120000 -0400" stop="20260407140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407120000 -0400" stop="20260407130000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Fast Money Halftime Report</title>
    <desc>The hot trades in the market from the floor of the New York Stock Exchange.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407130000 -0400" stop="20260407140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407130000 -0400" stop="20260407140000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>The Exchange</title>
    <desc>Anchor Kelly Evans reports on the most important stories to today's markets and investors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407133000 -0400" stop="20260407140000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Bold and the Beautiful</title>
    <desc>They created a dynasty where passion rules, they are the Forresters, the first name in Fashion. The Bold and the Beautiful, a world of fashion, glamor and romance. A place where power, money and success are there for the taking in a city where dreams really do come true. Follow the lives and loves of the Forresters on The Bold and the Beautiful...</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407140000 -0400" stop="20260407150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407140000 -0400" stop="20260407160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407140000 -0400" stop="20260407150000 -0400" channel="CNBC.US">
    <title>Power Lunch</title>
    <desc>Power Lunch takes you through the heart of the business day, focusing on real-time market coverage, breaking news and up-to-the-instant stock information. The show delves into the economy, the markets, real estate, media and technology -- any place where there's money to be made. The program features daily contributions from the Nasdaq MarketSite's Times Square studio and coverage from CNBC's Post 9 position on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange, as well as from CNBC's bureaus around the world. "Power Lunch" showcases the best stories of the day from CNBC's roster of digital and television journalists.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407160000 -0400" stop="20260407180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407180000 -0400" stop="20260407190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407190000 -0400" stop="20260407200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Finding Your Roots with Henry Louis Gates Jr.</title>
    <desc>Since the premiere of his groundbreaking series African American Lives through the first season of Finding Your Roots, noted Harvard scholar Henry Louis Gates, Jr. has been helping people discover long-lost relatives hidden for generations within the branches of their family trees. Professor Gates utilizes a team of genealogists to reconstruct the paper trail left behind by our ancestors and the world's leading geneticists to decode our DNA and help us travel thousands of years into the past to discover the origins of our earliest forebears.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Summer House</title>
    <desc>When a group of beautiful and successful New Yorkers leaves the comforts of the Big Apple behind to party the summer away in their home away from home, nothing is off limits. Bravo's new series Summer House takes the beach town of Montauk, New York by storm, while following a group of nine friends who make the exclusive enclave their go-to party spot between Memorial Day and Labor Day — that is, when they're not hustling at their day jobs. You could say they work hard and party way harder.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Best Medicine</title>
    <desc>In Best Medicine a brilliant surgeon leaves Boston to become a small-town doctor where he spent childhood summers. Despite his medical skills, his rude manner alienates locals as he battles hidden phobias and struggles with personal connections.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>NCIS (Naval Criminal Investigative Service) is more than just an action drama. With liberal doses of humor, it's a show that focuses on the sometimes complex and always amusing dynamics of a team forced to work together in high-stress situations. Leroy Jethro Gibbs, a former Marine gunnery sergeant, whose skills as an investigator are unmatched, leads this troupe of colorful personalities. Rounding out the team are Anthony DiNozzo, an ex-homicide detective whose instincts in the field are unparalleled and whose quick wit and humorous take on life make him a team favorite; the youthful and energetic forensic specialist Abby Sciuto, a talented scientist whose sharp mind matches her Goth style and eclectic tastes; Caitlin Todd, an ex-Secret Service Agent; and Timothy McGee, an MIT graduate whose brilliance with computers far overshadows his insecurities in the field; Assisting the team is medical examiner Dr. Donald "Ducky" Mallard, who knows it all because he's seen it all, and he's not afraid to let you know. From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, these special agents travel the globe to investigate all crimes with Navy or Marine Corps ties.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Will Trent</title>
    <desc>In Will Trent Special Agent Will Trent of the Georgia Bureau of Investigations was abandoned at birth and endured a harsh coming-of-age in Atlanta's overwhelmed foster care system. But now, determined to use his unique point of view to make sure no one is abandoned like he was, Trent has the highest clearance rate in the GBI.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Moonshiners</title>
    <desc>The secret and illegal world of moonshining stretches all across Appalachia raking in a pretty penny for those who choose to shine. Moonshiners will go to unprecedented extremes in their efforts to hide their still sites and cloak their distribution networks, some can hide in plain sight. With new styles of shine being tested and sold there is a king's ransom waiting for those bold enough to grab it. But those who enforce the law are wise to shiner deceptions and more determined than ever to catch them red handed and in the act of making Moonshine. The day of reckoning may be around the corner, but don't sell the Moonshiners short. Each has a keen understanding of how to stay one step ahead of the law in their region, and in this ongoing cat and mouse game you never know who will end up in the trap.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>WWE NXT</title>
    <desc>Each Wednesday at 8:00 p.m. ET, WWE Superstars and Divas of tomorrow face off on WWE NXT, a one-hour weekly show that features the brightest and best of WWE's rising stars. WWE NXT showcases the Superstars and Divas from WWE's Performance Center as well as appearances from WWE Superstars and Legends in an intimate setting. WWE NXT broadcasts from the state-of-the-art Full Sail LIVE venue on the Full Sail University in campus in Orlando, Florida.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Doc</title>
    <desc>Doc centers on the hard-charging, brilliant Dr. Amy Larsen, Chief of Internal and Family Medicine at Westside Hospital in Minneapolis. After a brain injury erases the last eight years of her life, Amy must navigate an unfamiliar world where she has no recollection of patients she's treated, colleagues she's crossed, the soulmate she divorced, the man she now loves and the tragedy that caused her to push everyone away. She can rely only on her estranged 17-year-old daughter, whom she remembers as a 9-year-old, and a handful of devoted friends, as she struggles to continue practicing medicine, despite having lost nearly a decade of knowledge and experience.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Road Wars</title>
    <desc>Roadways can be a wild place. With violent road rage incidents increasing 500% over the last decade, "road raging" is a human behavior that has become widely known. Road Wars takes a deep dive into American roadways, examining extreme human behavior, wild weather, insane accidents and a few welcome instances of acts of kindness.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>NCIS: Origins</title>
    <desc>In NCIS: Origins, young Leroy Jethro Gibbs starts his career as a newly minted special agent at the fledgling NCIS Camp Pendleton office where he forges his place on a gritty, ragtag team led by NCIS legend Mike Franks.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Curse of Oak Island</title>
    <desc>The Curse of Oak Island documents brothers Rick and Marty Lagina as they pursue their lifelong dream of solving more than a 220-year old Oak Island mystery. For over two centuries, teams of searchers, including Franklin D. Roosevelt, have attempted to crack the code that will unearth the treasure believed to be buried on the small island off the coast of Nova Scotia. Armed with the knowledge of those that came before them, the muscle of heavy machinery and decades of engineering know-how, the Lagina's and their partners may be closer than anyone in history to finding the treasure that has so far claimed the lives of six men.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>High Potential</title>
    <desc>High Potential follows Morgan, a single mom with an exceptional mind, whose unconventional knack for solving crimes leads to an unusual and unstoppable partnership with a by-the-book seasoned detective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407213000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Jeff Dunham's The Cars That Drove Us</title>
    <desc>Cars began rolling off the assembly line over 100 years ago. Two billion vehicles later, we still can't get enough. The Cars That Drove Us takes viewers into Jeff Dunham's garage - home to 130 legendary cars. Joined by his cast of characters, Dunham reveals the storied history of era-defining rides, from the Corvette Stingngray to the ill-fated Vector W8, as told by the engineers, artists, and socket slingers who built them</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407213000 -0400" stop="20260407220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Road Wars</title>
    <desc>Roadways can be a wild place. With violent road rage incidents increasing 500% over the last decade, "road raging" is a human behavior that has become widely known. Road Wars takes a deep dive into American roadways, examining extreme human behavior, wild weather, insane accidents and a few welcome instances of acts of kindness.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407213000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Jeff Dunham's The Cars That Drove Us</title>
    <desc>Cars began rolling off the assembly line over 100 years ago. Two billion vehicles later, we still can't get enough. The Cars That Drove Us takes viewers into Jeff Dunham's garage - home to 130 legendary cars. Joined by his cast of characters, Dunham reveals the storied history of era-defining rides, from the Corvette Stingngray to the ill-fated Vector W8, as told by the engineers, artists, and socket slingers who built them</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407220000 -0400" stop="20260407230000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Frontline</title>
    <desc>Since it began in 1983, Frontline has been airing public-affairs documentaries that explore a wide scope of the complex human experience. Frontline's goal is to extend the impact of the documentary beyond its initial broadcast by serving as a catalyst for change..</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407220000 -0400" stop="20260407230000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>R.J. Decker</title>
    <desc>R.J. Decker centers on the eponymous R.J. Decker, a disgraced newspaper photographer and ex-con who starts over as a private investigator in the colorful-if-crime-filled world of South Florida, tackling cases that range from slightly odd to outright bizarre with the help of his journalist ex, her police detective wife, and a shadowy new benefactor, a woman from his past who could be his greatest ally... or his one-way ticket back to prison.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407220000 -0400" stop="20260407230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407220100 -0400" stop="20260407223200 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>With supply chain shortages, prices skyrocketing and more shoplifting than ever before, positive customer relations are nearly impossible. Customer Wars spotlights the conflicts that arise when disgruntled and irrational customers come face-to-face with the employees doing their best to take care of their needs. From fiery exchanges at the fast-food drive thru to loss-prevention brawls, this series proves once and for all that "The customer is always right" is the exception rather than the rule.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407220300 -0400" stop="20260407230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Secrets Declassified with David Duchovny</title>
    <desc>Secrets Declassified tells the incredible stories of government secrets that have only recently come to light. This series proves that secrets can be uncovered, and mysteries can still be unraveled." Each episode will find Duchovny focusing on a different topic, speaking with different experts. Subjects include the real-life story behind Argo and the mystery of the Area 51 conspiracy. Mulder would approve.From black ops and bizarre experiments to deadly cover-ups and nefarious gadgets, David Duchovny pulls the curtain back on all the government secrets in modern history we always suspected, but were never given the answers to. Through the strange and shocking things countries the world over ? and those who work for them ? have done in the name of national interest, we?ll investigate the explosive evidence from newly declassified files that will finally shine a new light on what?s really going on deep in the shadows.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407223200 -0400" stop="20260407230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>With supply chain shortages, prices skyrocketing and more shoplifting than ever before, positive customer relations are nearly impossible. Customer Wars spotlights the conflicts that arise when disgruntled and irrational customers come face-to-face with the employees doing their best to take care of their needs. From fiery exchanges at the fast-food drive thru to loss-prevention brawls, this series proves once and for all that "The customer is always right" is the exception rather than the rule.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407230000 -0400" stop="20260408000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401070000 -0400" stop="20260401072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401124500 -0400" stop="20260401125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401141000 -0400" stop="20260401150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401170000 -0400" stop="20260401180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401185500 -0400" stop="20260401190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401190000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Great British Menu</title>
    <desc>Top chefs from across the nation compete for the chance to cook a four-course banquet for a high-profile figure.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401193000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Celebrity Lingo</title>
    <desc>Celebrity Lingo will see famous faces go head-to-head in the fast-paced wordplay game, as they vie to fill in the blanks and find the missing words.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401195500 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Warship: Life in the Royal Navy</title>
    <desc>JJ Chalmers and Kate Humble are given unprecedented access to the Royal Navy, both at sea and across many of their establishments back home. Our cameras are on board as a British warship hunts down a Russian submarine; Kate gets special clearance to go behind the scenes at Britian's secretive submarine base at Faslane in Scotland and JJ reveals what it takes to be an elite Royal Marine Commando as he journeys back to the beginning of his military career.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Help! I Bought It at Auction with Sarah Beeny</title>
    <desc>Help! I Bought It at Auction with Sarah Beeny explores the drama, risk, and reward of buying property at auction. From bargain terraces to sprawling mansions—and even the occasional castle—each episode follows gripping real-life stories of buyers seeking a bargain and gambling their life savings in pursuit of their dream home. But with many properties in dire need of renovation, the journey is rarely straightforward. Behind every wall and beneath every floorboard could lie a costly surprise.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401203000 -0400" channel="Sky Arts.GB">
    <title>Beyond the Brush</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Brush takes viewers on a journey through the ages of art, exploring the evolution of creativity across centuries. Each episode uncovers hidden secrets, personal struggles, and the cultural shifts that shaped history's greatest masterpieces. From the brushstrokes of genius to the untold stories behind the canvas, this series will reveal how every work of art holds far more than meets the eye.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="National Geographic.GB">
    <title>Decoding History's Prophecies</title>
    <desc>Revelations, fortunes and harbingers of doom … human history is scattered with mysterious people rumored to have supernatural insight into the future. Have forces beyond our understanding endowed these extraordinary individuals with the gift of prophecy, or is there a rational explanation for these visions?This riveting documentary series blends dramatic reenactments, sweeping footage, and interviews with a panel of experts to present three captivating stories per episode. From ancient China to medieval Europe and modern-day West Virginia, some cases turn out to be elaborate deceptions, others remain eerily unexplained, and all reveal a perpetual human desire to see beyond the veil of time — with reverberating effects on history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Enter a workshop filled with expert craftspeople, bringing loved pieces of family history and the memories they hold back to life. A heartwarming antidote to throwaway culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401203000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="Sky Arts.GB">
    <title>Beyond the Brush</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Brush takes viewers on a journey through the ages of art, exploring the evolution of creativity across centuries. Each episode uncovers hidden secrets, personal struggles, and the cultural shifts that shaped history's greatest masterpieces. From the brushstrokes of genius to the untold stories behind the canvas, this series will reveal how every work of art holds far more than meets the eye.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>The Teacher</title>
    <desc>Helen Simpson is a teacher with 30 years' experience who dismisses the woke ideologies of the younger generation. Influential female student Cressida Bancroft dislikes Helen for accusing her of being a woke warrior to gain popularity.After this clash of ideals, Cressida sets out to turning the world against Helen, before focussing her attention on Helen's family, including her son Sam.As Helen delves deeper into Cressida's past, she uncovers a world of sadness and neglect. But has she learnt enough about Cressida to stop her final act of revenge?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Ambulance</title>
    <desc>Ambulance is a BAFTA winning documentary series giving exclusive insight into how the ambulance service functions amidst the huge challenges it faces. The series meets the people working day in and day out, from paramedics to 999 call operators, to keep on top of the pressure and provide emergency care to the public.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="Quest.GB">
    <title>The Derbyshire Auction House</title>
    <desc>Irita Marriott, one of the few women in the country to helm an auction house, and her team use their expertise to launch Britain's newest saleroom.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>It'll Be Alright on the Night</title>
    <desc>Hilarious out-takes from the worlds of TV, cinema and commercials. The blooper-snooper team uncover calamities and catastrophes from cutting room floors around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401211000 -0400" stop="20260401221000 -0400" channel="E4.GB">
    <title>Vicky Pattison: Maybe, Baby?</title>
    <desc>Vicky Pattison and her husband Ercan Ramadan face a big decision; should they start a family? As they explore the routes to parenthood and the realities of having kids, will they decide it's for them?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401220000 -0400" stop="20260401230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Fatal Fraud</title>
    <desc>Fatal Fraud delves into cases where financial schemes spiral into betrayal, violence and murder, exposing the deadly cost of lies fueled by greed.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402070000 -0400" stop="20260402072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402124500 -0400" stop="20260402125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402141000 -0400" stop="20260402150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402170000 -0400" stop="20260402180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402185500 -0400" stop="20260402190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Great British Menu</title>
    <desc>Top chefs from across the nation compete for the chance to cook a four-course banquet for a high-profile figure.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402190000 -0400" stop="20260402193000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Tonight</title>
    <desc>A news-magazine programme presented by Julie Etchingham.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402195500 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <desc>Race Across the World will pit pairs of travellers against each other in a race to reach the Far East without taking a single flight, with no smartphone in sight. Each contestant will only have the cash equivalent of an air fare to their destination to pay for their overland travel. If they run out, they'll need to earn more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402200000 -0400" stop="20260402210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Yorkshire's Poshest Hotel: Grantley Hall</title>
    <desc>Behind the opulent doors of Grantley Hall, North Yorkshire as it pursues its ambition to be one of the world's best hotels, with rooms ranging from £1000-£4500 a night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>The Teacher</title>
    <desc>Helen Simpson is a teacher with 30 years' experience who dismisses the woke ideologies of the younger generation. Influential female student Cressida Bancroft dislikes Helen for accusing her of being a woke warrior to gain popularity.After this clash of ideals, Cressida sets out to turning the world against Helen, before focussing her attention on Helen's family, including her son Sam.As Helen delves deeper into Cressida's past, she uncovers a world of sadness and neglect. But has she learnt enough about Cressida to stop her final act of revenge?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402210000 -0400" stop="20260402220000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>The Apprentice</title>
    <desc>The Apprentice sees fourteen candidates, competing against each other for a position at Lord Alan Sugar's company. Each week the candidates take part in a task set by Lord Sugar. Each team will have a Team Leader who managers that group for that task. The team that performs the best will win a reward and avoid the boardroom. The losing team will be summoned to the boardroom where their team leader will be forced to pick two people in their team who we join them in the boardroom and a chance to be fired. After twelve weeks Lord Sugar will be left with his Apprentice, who will work for him at a salary of £100,000. Lord Sugar is very busy so he has Nick and Karen, who act as his eyes and ears, to inform him of what's going on.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Britain's Almost Perfect Murders</title>
    <desc>Britain's Almost Perfect Murders follows expert-led, forensic investigations of cases where meticulous, near-flawless crimes were ultimately uncovered due to tiny, overlooked fatal mistakes by the perpetrators.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402223000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>The Apprentice: Unfinished Business</title>
    <desc>A look behind the curtain of The Apprentice to analyse every task and tactic in detail as Lord Sugar searches for a new business partner.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Dispatches</title>
    <desc>Dispatches is the British TV current affairs documentary series on Channel 4, first transmitted in 1987. The programme covers issues about British society, politics, health,religion, international current affairs and the environment, and often features a mole inside organisations under journalistic investigation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403070000 -0400" stop="20260403072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403124500 -0400" stop="20260403125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403141000 -0400" stop="20260403150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403170000 -0400" stop="20260403180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403185500 -0400" stop="20260403190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403190000 -0400" stop="20260403200000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Great British Menu</title>
    <desc>Top chefs from across the nation compete for the chance to cook a four-course banquet for a high-profile figure.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403195500 -0400" stop="20260403200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403210000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Beyond Paradise</title>
    <desc>Death in Devon. DI Humphrey Goodman relocates from tropical Saint Marie to sleepy Shipton Abbott, cracking cases and hoping for happily ever after with fiancée Martha.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403200000 -0400" stop="20260403210000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Gardeners' World</title>
    <desc>Gardening show packed with good ideas, tips, advice from experts and timely reminders to get the most out of your garden, whatever its size or type.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403210000 -0400" stop="20260403213000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Have I Got News for You</title>
    <desc>Based on the week's news, Have I Got News for You is fronted by guest hosts and features two regular team captains, Paul Merton and Ian Hislop. Each week the show invites two guests to cast a jaundiced eye over the week's news, resulting in a fast flow of anarchic, spontaneous and hugely entertaining wit and humour. Guests typically represent the world of politics, comedy, show-business and journalism, and are often themselves particularly newsworthy participants. The final touches of Have I Got News for You are put together only hours before recording, allowing guests to comment on the late-breaking news stories of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403210000 -0400" stop="20260403220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>Gogglebox is a British observational documentary television show which has aired on Channel 4 since 2013. The show focuses on families, friends and couples from around the country in their living rooms watching the last week's of British television.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403220000 -0400" stop="20260403230500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>The Last Leg</title>
    <desc>Adam Hills and co-hosts Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker provide some offbeat commentary on the significant moments of the past seven days.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403223000 -0400" stop="20260403231500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>The Claudia Winkleman Show</title>
    <desc>Good vibes, great guests, glorious fringe. Your weekly dose of Claudia‑powered joy, as she has a chat with Hollywood stars, the best of British and her gorgeous studio audience.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404133000 -0400" stop="20260404163000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>The Boat Race</title>
    <desc>Coverage from the River Thames as rowing crews from Oxford and Cambridge Universities race each other over four and a quarter miles from Putney to Mortlake.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404140000 -0400" stop="20260404150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Catching Up With the Royals</title>
    <desc>Catching Up With the Royals is a brand-new weekly visualised podcast for 5, offering audiences a smart, entertaining and always-curious look at the royal family.Every week Reverend Richard Coles and royal journalist Emily Andrews deep dive on the latest royal news, inside whispers and intel from their royal sources to lift the lid on what life is really like behind palace walls. They'll also look back on key moments from history that informed the way the monarchy is today and answer viewer/listener questions about the royal topics they've always wanted to know more about.The show delivers fresh perspective and behind-the-scenes access into Britain's most famous institution with warmth, humour and genuine insider knowledge bringing viewers and listeners closer than ever to the monarchy both past and present.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404174500 -0400" stop="20260404184500 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>A celebrity version of the game show Catchphrase where contestants have to identify a familiar catchphrase represented by a piece of animation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404184500 -0400" stop="20260404200000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Britain's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>Britain's Got Talent brings together the very best variety acts from across the nation as they compete to win a life changing £250,000 and a coveted spot on The Royal Variety Performance.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404192500 -0400" stop="20260404193000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News Weekend</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404200000 -0400" stop="20260404203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404200000 -0400" stop="20260404210000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Celebrity Sabotage</title>
    <desc>Joel Dommett, Judi Love, Sam Thompson and GK Barry, alongside a whole host of celebrities, get ready to shock the nation in a brand new ITV entertainment reality game show, Celebrity Sabotage.Each week our gang of celebrity saboteurs will be joined by a NEW guest saboteur, including Jill Scott MBE, Fay Ripley, Olivia Attwood, Jo Brand, Guz Khan and Harry Redknapp. Who will join in on all the action and cause even more mischief and mayhem.In each episode a fresh set of unsuspecting contestants will arrive, believing they're participating in a brand-new ITV show. These range from cooking challenges and relationship tests to business tasks and even murder mystery games. Little do they know that these shows are completely made up! To make it even more convincing, these fake shows will have believable hosts, including familiar faces such as Clare Balding, Matt and Emma Willis, Monica Galetti, Jason Fox, Sara Davies and Rylan Clark. Everyone involved, from the celebrity saboteurs and the crew to the famous hosts, is in on the secret.The celebrities are hidden away in their very own high-tech mission HQ, secretly watching the contestants' every move. With props and disguises at their disposal, the question is: can the celebrities hold their nerve to successfully pull off some delightfully devious and convincingly cunning stunts, to win that big cash prize?  The stakes are high for our celebrity saboteurs. Every successfully executed sabotage mission will add more money to a secret prize pot. At the end of each episode, this pot will be revealed and shared equally among all the contestants - a complete surprise for them!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260404220000 -0400" stop="20260404230000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>The Jonathan Ross Show</title>
    <desc>Jonathan Ross, the king of chat, is back. Employing his infectious wit and sense of fun, he chats to some terrific celebrity guests and asks the questions to which everyone wants to know the answers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405070000 -0400" stop="20260405072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405082500 -0400" stop="20260405092500 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Jimmy and Shivi's Farmhouse Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Join Jimmy Doherty and Shivi Ramoutar at Jimmy's Suffolk farm for the show weekends were made for! A series full of delicious food and drink, craft, animals and country life…there really is something for everyone. Each week Jimmy and Shivi will whip up a tasty meal or two on their outdoor kitchen and suggest some drinks to go with them. They'll try their hand at arts and crafts, from making terrariums to upcycling wooden pallets, and they'll be chatting to a different celeb face in every show, getting the lowdown on the worlds of entertainment and sports. As if that weren't enough, Jimmy will give viewers a unique behind the scenes glimpse into the lives of the animals at his wildlife park, and Shivi explores the local area meeting great characters with stories to tell and skills to share.Jimmy &amp;amp; Shivi's Farmhouse Breakfast really is everything you need for a fun-packed weekend!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405093000 -0400" stop="20260405113000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Love Your Weekend with Alan Titchmarsh</title>
    <desc>Set in the heart of Hampshire, Alan Titchmarsh celebrates all that is great about the British countryside, art, crafts, manufacturing and produce. Alan chats to celebrity guests as well as wildlife, craft and sustainability experts who will share their top tips on how to make the most of our outside spaces no matter how big or small.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405192500 -0400" stop="20260405193000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News Weekend</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405194000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>The Great Celebrity Bake Off for Stand Up to Cancer</title>
    <desc>Celebrity bakers enter Britain's most famous tent and put their skills to the test, as they Stand Up To Cancer and inspire viewers to do the same.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405200000 -0400" stop="20260405203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>The Hunt</title>
    <desc>The Hunt - a heart-pounding, high-stakes game of predator versus prey, where there is only one rule – hunt or be hunted.Deep in a vast unforgiving forest, contestants are dropped into the ultimate real-world game of hide and seek - where losing means walking away with nothing and winning could mean pocketing up to £100,000. Surviving the game isn't about being the fastest. It's about being the smartest.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405210000 -0400" stop="20260405220000 -0400" channel="National Geographic.GB">
    <title>Planes That Changed History</title>
    <desc>Dive into the 125 years of aviation to uncover how aircraft have reshaped our world. The series explores the engineering secrets behind its success, its humble origins, and what made these aircraft icons years after their initial success.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406070000 -0400" stop="20260406072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406180000 -0400" stop="20260406180500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Love Nature</title>
    <desc>Love Nature is a new initiative to create multiple short films, spotlighting positive environmental stories from across the UK.   Each film, approximately three minutes long, will showcase inspiring campaigns and grassroots efforts within local communities, supporting and protecting nature. Produced in collaboration with regional independent production companies, the films aim to bring authentic, local voices to the forefront of environmental storytelling.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406190000 -0400" stop="20260406193000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Global Eye</title>
    <desc>Award-winning investigations - revealing secrets, rooting out injustice, and exposing crime, corruption, and abuse. The biggest stories from BBC correspondents all over the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406203000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Mastermind</title>
    <desc>Mastermind is a British quiz show, well known for its challenging questions, intimidating setting and air of seriousness. It first aired on 11 September 1972 &amp;amp; is still running today. Four contestants brave the black chair as they answer questions on their specialist subjects and test their general knowledge to win the coveted trophy.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406203000 -0400" stop="20260406210000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>University Challenge</title>
    <desc>Academic quiz show where teams of students from UK universities answer questions on all manner of subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406223000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>I'm a Celebrity, Get Me Out of Here! South Africa</title>
    <desc>Campmates have already proved that they can survive the Australian jungle, but this is I'm A Celebrity… on a whole new level, it's where legends are made. The trials are tougher than ever and with that, so are the stakes. With relentless twists and turns, the campmates will never know what's coming next. They will be faced with challenges at every turn, quickly learning that with big decisions come even bigger consequences…</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406220000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Ben Fogle in China</title>
    <desc>Ben Fogle embarks on a once-in-a-lifetime journey to China to see its staggering sights, meet its biggest characters, go beyond the stereotypes and discover its true story. Ben delves into an epic 3000-year tale of how China got to now – how centuries of Imperial rule gave way to Communist revolution and the breakneck economic transformation of recent years.From ancient temples to mega-factories and glittering modern cities, Ben is on a mission to get under the skin of China - how it sees itself in the world and how it's shaping the future for us all. But above all it's a journey of wonder amid the amazing visual splendour of the real China today.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406220500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>The Hunt</title>
    <desc>The Hunt - a heart-pounding, high-stakes game of predator versus prey, where there is only one rule – hunt or be hunted.Deep in a vast unforgiving forest, contestants are dropped into the ultimate real-world game of hide and seek - where losing means walking away with nothing and winning could mean pocketing up to £100,000. Surviving the game isn't about being the fastest. It's about being the smartest.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406210000 -0400" stop="20260406220000 -0400" channel="Quest.GB">
    <title>Shed &amp; Buried: Classic Cars</title>
    <desc>Shed &amp;amp; Buried: Classic Cars sees Henry team-up with Fuzz Townshend once again. The duo will be doing what they do best: digging in the nation's sheds, barns and outbuildings, this time to (hopefully) find a tidy profit in some vintage motors.Henry's love of motorbikes and tractors is well-known, but he still has a soft spot for classic cars. Fuzz - who has an encyclopaedic knowledge of all things automotive - is the perfect partner to help him unearth some classic four-wheelers and turn them into nice little earners.That's only half the battle - once their finds are back in the shed, restorer extraordinaire Guy Willison and engineering genius Allen Millyard will be put to the test, turning the rusty wrecks the lads have unearthed into right royal runners.As always, Henry will need to keep Fuzz focused, to make sure he doesn't buy an obscure vintage bus or lorry. Fuzz will have to keep an eye on Henry too, as he's usually done a deal before Fuzz can even lift the bonnet.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407070000 -0400" stop="20260407072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407150000 -0400" stop="20260407154500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>A series which helps prospective buyers find their dream home in the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407180000 -0400" stop="20260407180500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Love Nature</title>
    <desc>Love Nature is a new initiative to create multiple short films, spotlighting positive environmental stories from across the UK.   Each film, approximately three minutes long, will showcase inspiring campaigns and grassroots efforts within local communities, supporting and protecting nature. Produced in collaboration with regional independent production companies, the films aim to bring authentic, local voices to the forefront of environmental storytelling.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407222000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>I'm a Celebrity, Get Me Out of Here! South Africa</title>
    <desc>Campmates have already proved that they can survive the Australian jungle, but this is I'm A Celebrity… on a whole new level, it's where legends are made. The trials are tougher than ever and with that, so are the stakes. With relentless twists and turns, the campmates will never know what's coming next. They will be faced with challenges at every turn, quickly learning that with big decisions come even bigger consequences…</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Ben Fogle in China</title>
    <desc>Ben Fogle embarks on a once-in-a-lifetime journey to China to see its staggering sights, meet its biggest characters, go beyond the stereotypes and discover its true story. Ben delves into an epic 3000-year tale of how China got to now – how centuries of Imperial rule gave way to Communist revolution and the breakneck economic transformation of recent years.From ancient temples to mega-factories and glittering modern cities, Ben is on a mission to get under the skin of China - how it sees itself in the world and how it's shaping the future for us all. But above all it's a journey of wonder amid the amazing visual splendour of the real China today.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>The Hunt</title>
    <desc>The Hunt - a heart-pounding, high-stakes game of predator versus prey, where there is only one rule – hunt or be hunted.Deep in a vast unforgiving forest, contestants are dropped into the ultimate real-world game of hide and seek - where losing means walking away with nothing and winning could mean pocketing up to £100,000. Surviving the game isn't about being the fastest. It's about being the smartest.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407210000 -0400" stop="20260407220000 -0400" channel="Sky Arts.GB">
    <title>Spymasters: The Great Spy Writers</title>
    <desc>Spymasters: The Great Spy Writers explores the lives, works, and secrets of some of the most brilliant spy authors in literature.They have shaped what has become a hugely popular genre, weaving intricate plots, clandestine operations, and intense suspense into their novels, and sometimes exploring political issues and international relations with unsettling and often cynical insight.Successful film and television franchises have been built around spies, while spy novels sell in great numbers. Lying behind recurring plots based on the successful negotiation of risk and betrayal safely exposed is an altogether bleaker world, based on violence, and incessant surveillance by state actors to benefit state activities.The series explores the interlocking world of public and private, state and individual and combines analysis of the biographies of the writers and their work, together with an examination of the geopolitical settings in which they operate.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401210000 -0400" stop="20260401220000 -0400" channel="CBC.CA">
    <title>Allegiance</title>
    <desc>Allegiance follows on identity and belonging, policing and politics, and finding truth within the heart of a flawed justice system. Sabrina Sohal is a star rookie police officer who must grapple with the limits of the justice system as she fights to exonerate her politician father Ajeet Sohal. Sohal serves her diverse hometown of Surrey alongside Vince Brambilla, a veteran training officer who sees her potential but doesn't always agree with her forward-thinking methods. Allegiance is the story of a young woman caught between her allegiance to her flag, to her badge, and to her family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402220000 -0400" stop="20260402230000 -0400" channel="Citytv.CA">
    <title>Law &amp; Order Toronto: Criminal Intent</title>
    <desc>In Toronto's war on crime, the worst offenders are pursued by the detectives of the specialized criminal investigations unit. These are their stories.As a psychological thriller wrapped in a criminal investigation, Law &amp;amp; Order Toronto: Criminal Intent follows an elite squad of detectives who investigate high-profile crime and corruption in metro Toronto.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405200000 -0400" stop="20260405210000 -0400" channel="CTV.CA">
    <title>Sullivan's Crossing</title>
    <desc>After Neurosurgeon Maggie Sullivan's personal and professional life are thrown into turmoil she returns home to Sullivan's Crossing. While there, Maggie is forced to navigate her complicated present while confronting the painful past she has chosen to ignore for years.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407210000 -0400" channel="Citytv.CA">
    <title>The Price is Right Tonight</title>
    <desc>Hosted by legendary comedian and television personality Howie Mandel, The Price Is Right Tonight is a new Canadian series that brings the iconic game show's joyful wins and classic format to a primetime audience.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401060000 -0400" stop="20260401090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401120000 -0400" stop="20260401130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401193000 -0400" stop="20260401200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401200000 -0400" stop="20260401203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Tonight At The Museum</title>
    <desc>Filmed on location in a real museum after dark, surrounded by priceless artefacts, taxidermy and historical curiosities, Alex Lee guides four celebrity players through a series of challenges and quizzes that deliver gags quick and fast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401203000 -0400" stop="20260401210000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>The Weekly with Charlie Pickering</title>
    <desc>The Weekly with Charlie Pickering is the one show on TV that knows the world is far too serious to be taken too seriously. You give us 30 minutes, we'll give you the week.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401213000 -0400" stop="20260401233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Melbourne International Comedy Festival</title>
    <desc>Each year, the red carpet rolls out, the celebrities roll up and the cameras roll for a night that proves how powerful laughter can be. A cavalcade of international and Australian comedy superstars donate their best five minutes of material in exchange for the generosity of those in the audience, and those watching in TV Land.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260401230000 -0400" stop="20260401233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402060000 -0400" stop="20260402090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402120000 -0400" stop="20260402130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402193000 -0400" stop="20260402200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260402230000 -0400" stop="20260402233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403060000 -0400" stop="20260403090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403120000 -0400" stop="20260403130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403193000 -0400" stop="20260403203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Gardening Australia</title>
    <desc>Gardening Australia provides practical, realistic, and credible horticultural and gardening advice, inspiring and entertaining all Australian gardeners around the nation. Presented by Australia's leading horticultural experts, Gardening Australia is a valuable resource to all gardeners through the television program, the magazine, books, DVDs and extensive online content.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260403230000 -0400" stop="20260403233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260405123000 -0400" stop="20260405133000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Landline</title>
    <desc>Pip Courtney &amp;amp; a team of Landline reporters around the country bring you up to date with the issues affecting rural &amp;amp; regional Australia. From farming, agriculture, food, economics, innovation, climate, infrastructure &amp;amp; more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406193000 -0400" stop="20260406200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406200000 -0400" stop="20260406203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Australian Story</title>
    <desc>These are the stories of who we are. Australian Story presents unique tales that provide an insight into Australian life with all its complexities and challenges.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406203000 -0400" stop="20260406211500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Four Corners</title>
    <desc>Four Corners is Australia's premier television current affairs program. It has been part of the national story since August 1961, exposing scandals, triggering inquiries, firing debate, confronting taboos and interpreting fads, trends and sub-cultures. Its consistently high standards of journalism and film-making have earned international recognition and an array of Walkleys, Logies and other national awards.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406213500 -0400" stop="20260406220500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Planet America</title>
    <desc>Chas Licciardello and John Barron set out to discover the real America - its politics and its people - with analysis from US and Australian experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260406230000 -0400" stop="20260406233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260407200000 -0400" stop="20260407203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Foreign Correspondent</title>
    <desc>Australia's leading international affairs program featuring fascinating, in-depth stories from the ABC's unrivalled network of foreign correspondents.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
</tv>