<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv generator-info-name="TVMaze EPG Generator" generator-info-url="https://www.tvmaze.com/api">
  <channel id="CNN.US">
    <display-name>CNN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="MS NOW.US">
    <display-name>MS NOW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Newsmax.US">
    <display-name>Newsmax</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.US">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CBS.US">
    <display-name>CBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="A&amp;E.US">
    <display-name>A&amp;E</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Fox News Channel.US">
    <display-name>Fox News Channel</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NBC.US">
    <display-name>NBC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ESPN.US">
    <display-name>ESPN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="The CW.US">
    <display-name>The CW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Bravo.US">
    <display-name>Bravo</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery.US">
    <display-name>Discovery</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="HBO.US">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="History.US">
    <display-name>History</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NewsNation.US">
    <display-name>NewsNation</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="PBS.US">
    <display-name>PBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="STARZ.US">
    <display-name>STARZ</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="5.GB">
    <display-name>5</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ITV1.GB">
    <display-name>ITV1</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC One.GB">
    <display-name>BBC One</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Channel 4.GB">
    <display-name>Channel 4</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Comedy Central.GB">
    <display-name>Comedy Central</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Quest.GB">
    <display-name>Quest</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC Two.GB">
    <display-name>BBC Two</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <display-name>TRUE CRIME</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery.GB">
    <display-name>Discovery</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.AU">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>AU</country>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260626000000 -0400" stop="20260626020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627070000 -0400" stop="20260627100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627070000 -0400" stop="20260627090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Weekend</title>
    <desc>Start your weekend days with real news and analysis from Michael Grimm, Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627070000 -0400" stop="20260627080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627070000 -0400" stop="20260627090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Saturday Morning</title>
    <desc>Hosts Jeff Glor, Dana Jacobson and Michelle Miller provide original reporting, breaking news, and profiles of leading figures in culture and the arts from the Times Square studio on the Saturday edition of the CBS morning news family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627090000 -0400" stop="20260627110000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>America Right Now</title>
    <desc>Tom Basile tackles the week's biggest stories with top talkers from politics, Hollywood, and across America.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627090000 -0400" stop="20260627100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Smerconish</title>
    <desc>After serving as an MSNBC contributor and guest-host on the network for four years, TV and radio personality Michael Smerconish believed he was ready to head a show of his own. CNN agreed, and thus was born Smerconish, an hour long Saturday morning program that takes after its host's independent views. Using a topical, conversational format, he aims for the TV show to be an extension of his weekday radio broadcast, with free-flowing topics and the ability to discuss issues that strike a chord with the audience. Along the same lines, he thinks it's important to present the content in an engaging manner, free of my-way-or-the-highway ideology. Smerconish, who has a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania, is also a New York Times' best-selling author.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627100000 -0400" stop="20260627130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Connect with Jacob Soboroff</title>
    <desc>Connect with Jacob Soboroffwill be the network's first Los Angeles-based program. Built around the connection Soboroff has forged with the MS NOW audience for more than a decade, Connect will bring viewers closer to the stories shaping the country. Connect will also bring Soboroff's storied reporting from the ground in Los Angeles and beyond to help connect the dots between what's happening in local communities throughout the country and larger national conversations driving politics, culture, and daily life.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627100000 -0400" stop="20260627110000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>When a house has been left for dead, the Zombie House Flippers bring it back to life and into beautifully remade shape for top dollar. These flippers show the inner workings of this high-stakes world full of unexpected disasters, hidden costs, and quirky personalities. With tight budgets and short timelines, it's a mad scramble to finish these flips and make bank for the team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627110000 -0400" stop="20260627120000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Million Dollar Zombie Flips</title>
    <desc>Million Dollar Zombie Flips follows James Dainard and his team as they hunt for, fix, and flip zombie houses in the Seattle area. In each episode, James brings the cash and teams up with a rookie flipper who finds a dilapidated house and together, they attempt to turn it into a stunning million-dollar home. Following James' plan, the flipping partner is in charge of the renovation process and if all goes smoothly, they split the profit 50/50. However, if the newbie can't meet the team's standards, James will take over and keep the full profit for himself. With millions of dollars on the line, do these real-estate newbies have what it takes to turn big bucks in the high-stakes world of flipping?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627110000 -0400" stop="20260627130000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Saturday Report</title>
    <desc>Rita Cosby and Jon Glasgow tackles the big headlines with smart analysis from top experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627110000 -0400" stop="20260627120000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Zombie House Flipping: Family Business</title>
    <desc>In Columbus, Ohio, power flipper Tommy Harr and his family have built a business on seeing opportunity where others see disaster. Their edge comes from within the family — two generations of elite home inspectors, a fearless construction crew led by his middle brother, and a mom who doubles as both designer and real estate agent. Together, they take on the city's worst "zombie" houses, transforming rundown properties into stunning dream homes.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627130000 -0400" stop="20260627150000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Saturday Agenda</title>
    <desc>Rob Astorino reveals Washington's inner workings and the fight for core values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627130000 -0400" stop="20260627160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627170000 -0400" stop="20260627180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627170000 -0400" stop="20260627190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Count</title>
    <desc>Newsmax counts up the top stories of the week, while offering analysis by lawmakers, newsmakers, and policy experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627180000 -0400" stop="20260627210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend Primetime</title>
    <desc>A diverse panel of journalists navigates the week's biggest stories and sets the agenda for the week ahead, offering context, analysis, and civil debate in a three-hour Saturday and Sunday evening format.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627193000 -0400" stop="20260627200000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>WNBA Tip-Off</title>
    <desc>WNBA Tip-Off serves as the pre-game telecast on CBS. It features a less-scripted format, highlighted by a lively round-table discussion and debate of the top story lines around the league.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627200000 -0400" stop="20260627210000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Storage Wars: Back to the Locker</title>
    <desc>Storage Wars: Back to the Locker refers to a series of episodes within the larger "Storage Wars" series, where the focus is on the competitive bidding and treasure hunting within abandoned storage units. These episodes continue the main show's premise of professional buyers vying to acquire the contents of storage lockers, often with the hope of finding valuable items among the discarded belongings. The "Back to the Locker" part emphasizes the return to the core concept of exploring what lies behind the doors of these storage units.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627210000 -0400" stop="20260627220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>My View with Lara Trump</title>
    <desc>My View with Lara Trump features big picture analysis and interviews with thought leaders, shedding light on the headlines driving the national conversation and affecting families around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627210000 -0400" stop="20260627220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Storage Wars follows professional buyers and their teams as they scour repossessed storage units in search of hidden treasure. Part gamblers, part detectives, these auction pros have found everything from coffins to the world's most valuable comic book collection, paying as little as ten dollars for items valued in the millions.Each episode of Storage Wars follows a group of bidders as they get a quick peek inside the units, aided only by the beam of a flashlight. They then must assess on the spot if the unit is worth a bid and how high they will actually go to grasp the gold. The high-stakes fun begins as we see if the resulting buy is full of mostly trash... or true treasure.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627210000 -0400" stop="20260627220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Craig Ferguson: American on Purpose</title>
    <desc>Follows a cross-country journey exploring modern America's identity, freedoms, contradictions, and cultural quirks as the nation celebrates its 250th anniversary of independence.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628070000 -0400" stop="20260628100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628070000 -0400" stop="20260628090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Weekend</title>
    <desc>Start your weekend days with real news and analysis from Michael Grimm, Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628070000 -0400" stop="20260628080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628080000 -0400" stop="20260628090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist</title>
    <desc>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist delivers morning news, videos, and photos about current events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628090000 -0400" stop="20260628100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Meet the Press</title>
    <desc>For almost as long as there has been television, there's been Meet the Press. The hourlong Sunday morning public affairs program has featured interviews with countless U.S. and world leaders, and has reviewed, analyzed and discussed the news of the week -- all while looking toward the week ahead.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628090000 -0400" stop="20260628103000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS News Sunday Morning</title>
    <desc>CBS News Sunday Morning is a early morning news and magazine program that airs on Sunday's on CBS.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628090000 -0400" stop="20260628100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>State of the Union with Jake Tapper and Dana Bash</title>
    <desc>Jake Tapper and Dana Bash bring together major newsmakers, analysts and experts to tackle pressing domestic issues and diplomacy on the global stage.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628100000 -0400" stop="20260628130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Connect with Jacob Soboroff</title>
    <desc>Connect with Jacob Soboroffwill be the network's first Los Angeles-based program. Built around the connection Soboroff has forged with the MS NOW audience for more than a decade, Connect will bring viewers closer to the stories shaping the country. Connect will also bring Soboroff's storied reporting from the ground in Los Angeles and beyond to help connect the dots between what's happening in local communities throughout the country and larger national conversations driving politics, culture, and daily life.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628100000 -0400" stop="20260628110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Sunday Morning Futures with Maria Bartiromo</title>
    <desc>As part of her role as FOX Business Network's global markets editor, business journalist Maria Bartiromo hosts this weekly Sunday morning show on FBN sister network FOX News Channel Sunday Morning Futures with Maria Bartiromo that focuses more on the general economy than the stock market specifically. The hourlong show provides viewers with information about how recent news events affect the economy. In addition, Bartiromo interviews business leaders and newsmakers on topics that include job creation and investment opportunities.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628100000 -0400" stop="20260628110000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>This Week</title>
    <desc>This Week  is hosted by former Clinton White House staffer and current co-anchor of ABC's weekday morning news show "Good Morning America", George Stephanopoulos offers a look at current events with a focus on the politics of the day. Each week's show includes interviews with top newsmakers (including some of the nation's top political leaders) as well as a roundtable discussion, usually featuring journalists from ABC and other news organizations, of the week's happenings. Since 2008, the program has broadcast from a studio at the Newseum in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628100000 -0400" stop="20260628110000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Fareed Zakaria GPS</title>
    <desc>Fareed Zakaria GPS is a weekly public affairs show hosted by journalist and author Fareed Zakaria. As of November 2011, the show airs Sundays at 10 am Eastern Time and 1 pm Eastern Time on CNN. The show also airs Sundays at 1200 and 1900 GMT on CNN International. The "GPS" in the show's title stands for "Global Public Square," a reference to the show's focus on international issues and foreign affairs. On August 10, 2012, CNN suspended the program pending their investigation of suspected plagiarism. One week later, the New York Times reported, "Time and CNN said they had completed their reviews, found no evidence of plagiarism, and restored Mr. Zakaria to his demanding schedule." Each installment features Zakaria leading a panel discussion and conducting an extended one-on-one interview.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628103000 -0400" stop="20260628113000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Face the Nation</title>
    <desc>Face the Nation is a news interview program which airs every Sunday morning, live from the CBS studio in Washington D.C. It is dedicated to interviewing newsmakers on the latest issues. Guests include government leaders, politicians, and international figures in the news. CBS News… More correspondents engage the guests in a lively roundtable discussion focusing on current topics. The show started on November 7th, 1954, and was originally broadcast on both CBS Television and Radio Networks. After close to two decades, the program was taken off CBS radio.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628130000 -0400" stop="20260628160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628133000 -0400" stop="20260628140000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>WNBA Tip-Off</title>
    <desc>WNBA Tip-Off serves as the pre-game telecast on CBS. It features a less-scripted format, highlighted by a lively round-table discussion and debate of the top story lines around the league.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628170000 -0400" stop="20260628180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628180000 -0400" stop="20260628210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend Primetime</title>
    <desc>A diverse panel of journalists navigates the week's biggest stories and sets the agenda for the week ahead, offering context, analysis, and civil debate in a three-hour Saturday and Sunday evening format.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628183000 -0400" stop="20260628190000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>WNBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>WNBA Countdown serves as the primer for game telecasts on both ESPN2 and ESPN. It features a less-scripted format, highlighted by a lively round-table discussion and debate of the top story lines around the league.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628190000 -0400" stop="20260628200000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>WWE NXT Premium Live Events</title>
    <desc>This is a list of WWE NXT pay-per-view and livestreaming supercards, detailing all professional wrestling cards promoted by the American promotion WWE on pay-per-view (PPV) and available via livestreaming on services such as the WWE Network. Due to the American version of the WWE Network merging under Peacock, and with the WWE Network still available in most international markets, as well as less focus being given to traditional PPV channels, in 2022, the company began using the term "Premium Live Event" to refer to their events airing on PPV and the livestreaming services. The terminology "TakeOver" was dropped in December of 2021 as the NXT brand transformed.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628200000 -0400" stop="20260628210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Atlanta</title>
    <desc>An up-close and personal look at life in Hotlanta, The Real Housewives of Atlanta follows five glamorous southern belles as they balance motherhood, demanding careers and a fast-paced social calendar, and shows what life is like in the most exclusive areas of Atlanta. These driven and ambitious women prove that they're not just "housewives," but entrepreneurs, doting mothers and classy southern women. These ladies show the world what it takes to live large in some of the hottest zip codes in the south.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628200000 -0400" stop="20260628220100 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Naked and Afraid: Global Showdown</title>
    <desc>Survivalists from all over the world - including Brazil, Australia, Mexico, and the United States - represent their homelands in a grueling 40-day primitive bushcraft competition. Paired with a partner, their skills, toughness and teamwork will be tested as they compete for national pride and the largest cash prize in franchise history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628210000 -0400" stop="20260628220800 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>Set 200 years before the events of Game of Thrones, House of the Dragon tells the history of House Targaryen as they fight through a civil war.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628210000 -0400" stop="20260628220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Hazardous History with Henry Winkler</title>
    <desc>The eight-episode fast-paced, nostalgia-fueled series will take viewers on a thrilling ride through America's past.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628210000 -0400" stop="20260628220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Rhode Island</title>
    <desc>They may live in the smallest state in the country, but their drama? Extra large. Bravo is expanding the distinguished franchise with The Real Housewives of Rhode Island, spotlighting a fresh, charismatic group of women whose lives intertwine across the storied coastline of New England luxury.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628220000 -0400" stop="20260628230000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>In the Eye of the Storm</title>
    <desc>In the Eye of the Storm Megastorms like 2021's Hurricane Ida and the 2023 Maui Wildfires were captured by onlookers who found themselves in the wrong place at the right time and boldly held up their camera phones to document their experiences.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628220100 -0400" stop="20260628230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE LFG</title>
    <desc>WWE LFG (Legends &amp;amp; Future Greats) will offer viewers an inside look at the rigorous training process, featuring iconic WWE Legends such as Paul "Triple H" Levesque and Shawn Michaels and weekly regular coaches Undertaker, Booker T, Mickie James and Bubba Ray Dudley as they mentor a new generation in weekly matches on their quest to become the next WWE Superstars.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628220300 -0400" stop="20260628230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Food That Built America</title>
    <desc>For generations of Americans, food titans like Henry Heinz, Milton Hershey, John and Will Kellogg, C.W. Post and the McDonald brothers have literally been household names, but you don't know their stories. Before they were brand names, they were brilliant, sometimes ruthless, visionaries who revolutionized food and changed the landscape of America forever. This miniseries event will tell the fascinating stories of the people behind the food that built America – those who used brains, muscle, blood, sweat and tears to get to America's heart through its stomach, and along the way built cities, invented new technologies and helped win wars.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628221500 -0400" stop="20260628224500 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628230000 -0400" stop="20260628233000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>Last Week Tonight with John Oliver</title>
    <desc>On Last Week Tonight with John Oliver, John Oliver presents a satirical look at the week in news, politics and current events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628230400 -0400" stop="20260628233400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE's Greatest Moments</title>
    <desc>WWE's Greatest Moments will feature legendary play-by-play announcer Michael Cole hosting half-hour episodes with various WWE Superstars &amp;amp; Legends, including "Stone Cold" Steve Austin, Hulk Hogan, Kevin Owens and others, to share vivid recollections and perspectives on the most remarkable moments in wrestling history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628233400 -0400" stop="20260629000300 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE's Greatest Moments</title>
    <desc>WWE's Greatest Moments will feature legendary play-by-play announcer Michael Cole hosting half-hour episodes with various WWE Superstars &amp;amp; Legends, including "Stone Cold" Steve Austin, Hulk Hogan, Kevin Owens and others, to share vivid recollections and perspectives on the most remarkable moments in wrestling history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629050000 -0400" stop="20260629060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629050000 -0400" stop="20260629060000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends First</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the day, FOX &amp;amp; Friends First delivers all the headlines viewers may have missed overnight, along with a preview of upcoming news events. Presented two hours before FOX &amp;amp; Friends, the first hour of the program is hosted by Todd Piro and Carley Shimkus</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629060000 -0400" stop="20260629090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629060000 -0400" stop="20260629070000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Early</title>
    <desc>Wake up to reliable reporting that delivers the essential facts you need to start your day informed, along with expert commentary and thoughtful analysis. Get an early look at the top stories shaping national and global conversations. Whether it's politics, business, culture, or breaking news, you'll be prepared for whatever the day brings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629060000 -0400" stop="20260629090000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Morning in America</title>
    <desc>Morning in America is NewsNation's live national morning newscast hosted by Markie Martin.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629060000 -0400" stop="20260629090000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends</title>
    <desc>FOX &amp;amp; Friends is a conservative American early-morning news and opinion talk show on the Fox News Channel. It begins at 6:00 a.m. Eastern Time with the latest Fox News Live headlines and news of the morning and continues with a variety of segments including current events, interviews, updates of news stories with correspondents, right-leaning analysis from the hosts, and entertainment segments.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629060000 -0400" stop="20260629070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629070000 -0400" stop="20260629090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America</title>
    <desc>Start your day and weekend with real news and analysis from Rob Finnerty, Michael Grimm &amp;amp; Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629070000 -0400" stop="20260629090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629070000 -0400" stop="20260629090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629070000 -0400" stop="20260629090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629070000 -0400" stop="20260629100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629090000 -0400" stop="20260629110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629090000 -0400" stop="20260629120000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>National Report</title>
    <desc>National Report with Shaun Kraisman and Emma Rechenberg for live breaking news from NY and Washington, on politics, health, finance, and lifestyle that impact you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629090000 -0400" stop="20260629120000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes</title>
    <desc>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes brings you a fast-paced look at the latest from the border to Main Street to the White House and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629090000 -0400" stop="20260629110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629090000 -0400" stop="20260629100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629100000 -0400" stop="20260629110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629100000 -0400" stop="20260629120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629110000 -0400" stop="20260629120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Faulkner Focus</title>
    <desc>Emmy-winning journalist Harris Faulkner provides the latest news driving the day with insightful analysis and interviews with top newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629120000 -0400" stop="20260629140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629120000 -0400" stop="20260629140000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Newsline</title>
    <desc>Bianca de la Garza tackles the big news from D.C., N.Y., across America, and around the world!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629120000 -0400" stop="20260629150000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Nichole Berlie</title>
    <desc>The day's top news headlines with reports from correspondents around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629120000 -0400" stop="20260629130000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Outnumbered</title>
    <desc>Featuring an ensemble of four female panelists and one rotating male, Outnumbered examines the top news stories as well as the leading pop culture and relationship issues dominating the headlines. FNC's Harris Faulkner, Kayleigh McEnany and Emily Compagno lead the program's coverage, while alternating co-panelists weigh in with analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629120000 -0400" stop="20260629130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629130000 -0400" stop="20260629150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629130000 -0400" stop="20260629140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629130000 -0400" stop="20260629160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629140000 -0400" stop="20260629160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629140000 -0400" stop="20260629160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629140000 -0400" stop="20260629150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629150000 -0400" stop="20260629180000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live With Connell McShane</title>
    <desc>Connell McShane presents reports and analysis of the day's national and international newsworthy events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629150000 -0400" stop="20260629160000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Story</title>
    <desc>The Story with Martha MacCallum, anchored by Martha MacCallum, focuses on the stories that are most important to Americans with insight from top newsmakers and analysts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629160000 -0400" stop="20260629180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629160000 -0400" stop="20260629170000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Record with Greta Van Susteren</title>
    <desc>Award-winning journalist Greta Van Susteren digs into the top stories of the day with the focus on why they matter to the American people. Greta speaks with the top newsmakers on both sides of the aisle, creating a conversation and dialogue that is imperative for the nation's well-being.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629160000 -0400" stop="20260629170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Will Cain Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers from across politics, business, culture and sports, The Will Cain Show will offer a comprehensive look at the news of the day in a signature podcast style.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629160000 -0400" stop="20260629170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629170000 -0400" stop="20260629180000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Ed Henry the Big Take</title>
    <desc>Ed Henry offers his common-sense take on the news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629170000 -0400" stop="20260629180000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Five</title>
    <desc>The Five is an American news and talk show on Fox News Channel featuring a rotating panel who discuss current stories, political issues, and pop culture. The show premiered in July 2011, replacing the Glenn Beck program, and airs on weekdays at 5:00 p.m. ET with replays at 4:00 a.m. ET. On October 3, 2011, after successful ratings and high popularity, Fox News announced that The Five would become the permanent 5 p.m. series, as the program had previously been announced to last only during the summer. The Five is currently the second-most-watched program in all of cable news in the United States, placing only behind The O'Reilly Factor, also on the Fox News Channel. The program has occasionally been the number one rated cable news series in the key 25 to 54 viewing demographic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629170000 -0400" stop="20260629190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629180000 -0400" stop="20260629190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629180000 -0400" stop="20260629190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Carl Higbie Frontline</title>
    <desc>Carl Higbie Frontline focuses on providing commonsense news analysis, exposing big government overreach and the media's shortfalls — all while always fighting for American values. Produced from Newsmax's Manhattan studios covering breaking news and exploring key issues such as personal liberty, security, and government transparency.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629180000 -0400" stop="20260629190000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hill on NewsNation combines the power of two trusted news sources into one must-watch hour. The Hill, the nation's #1 political website, and NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, team up to define today's most-pressing issues, and question Washington's power brokers on what matters most to the people they serve and what matters most to Americans.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629180000 -0400" stop="20260629190000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Special Report</title>
    <desc>Special Report with Bret Baier (formerly Special Report with Brit Hume) is an American television news and political commentary program appearing on Fox News Channel, currently hosted by Bret Baier. It airs live each Monday through Friday at 6:00 PM ET. The show focuses on both reporting and analysis of the day's events, with a primary focus on national political news. The show has been a part of the Fox News program lineup since 1998 and is the number one cable news broadcast in its time slot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629183000 -0400" stop="20260629190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629190000 -0400" stop="20260629200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629190000 -0400" stop="20260629200000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Rob Schmitt Tonight</title>
    <desc>Rob Schmitt Tonight locks in all the late-breaking stories that matter to you, and delivers the up-to-the-minute news you need to hear before turning in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629190000 -0400" stop="20260629200000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Elizabeth Vargas Reports</title>
    <desc>In-depth coverage of the biggest news stories of the day; NewsNation's home for exclusive and enterprise reporting; hosted live by Elizabeth Vargas.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629190000 -0400" stop="20260629200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Ingraham Angle</title>
    <desc>The Ingraham Angle cuts through the Washington chatter to speak directly with unexpected voices and the actual people who are impacted by the news of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629190000 -0400" stop="20260629200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>World War II with Tom Hanks</title>
    <desc>For eighty years, the Second World War has remained the most devastating and defining conflict in human history. World War II with Tom Hanks is a landmark documentary event that reexamines the war through the lens of a new century. Told over twenty hours and guided by Tom Hanks, whose lifelong passion for this history has shaped some of the most profound screen portrayals of the era, the series captures the full arc of the war — from the rise of fascism in Europe to the fall of Berlin, from Pearl Harbor to Hiroshima, and the uneasy peace that follows. Each episode uncovers new dimensions of the conflict: the decisions that shaped the battlefield, the unseen networks that sustained the war effort, and the aftershocks that still shape our world today. "World War II with Tom Hanks" is the definitive retelling of that story for a new generation: a sweeping, deeply human portrait of how the modern world was forged in the fires of global war.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Finnerty</title>
    <desc>Finnerty will look to cut through the noise to bring unfiltered truth, sharp debates, and a focus on the most pressing issues facing America today while standing up for American values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Cuomo</title>
    <desc>Chris Cuomo hosts CUOMO, a no-nonsense show featuring the day's most important news from all perspectives. CUOMO airs weeknights at 8 p.m./7C on NewsNation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Jesse Watters Primetime</title>
    <desc>Jesse Watters brings his fresh take to Primetime. Each night, he'll speak with newsmakers from across the country and give Americans a show where straight talk is the only talk, and the obvious will never be left unsaid.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Below Deck Mediterranean</title>
    <desc>With a new boat, new location, and new faces, the excitement, drama, and adventure of life aboard a private luxury yacht is taken to another level in the Mediterranean. Providing unparalleled service to wealthy and uncompromising guests is made even more difficult as the team faces everything from love triangles to seeing fellow crew members shockingly cross the line with guests. Voyaging from Santorini, Mykonos, and many of the Greek islands, each episode features a new group of elite clientele who present a new set of challenges, all while offering the crew a glamorous lifestyle and exotic perks that most people only dream of experiencing. For these young, attractive, and adventurous yachties, the "work hard, play harder" nature of the job combined with the pressure of working in the most exclusive yachting scene in the world pushes the team close to the breaking point on Below Deck Mediterranean.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>World War II with Tom Hanks</title>
    <desc>For eighty years, the Second World War has remained the most devastating and defining conflict in human history. World War II with Tom Hanks is a landmark documentary event that reexamines the war through the lens of a new century. Told over twenty hours and guided by Tom Hanks, whose lifelong passion for this history has shaped some of the most profound screen portrayals of the era, the series captures the full arc of the war — from the rise of fascism in Europe to the fall of Berlin, from Pearl Harbor to Hiroshima, and the uneasy peace that follows. Each episode uncovers new dimensions of the conflict: the decisions that shaped the battlefield, the unseen networks that sustained the war effort, and the aftershocks that still shape our world today. "World War II with Tom Hanks" is the definitive retelling of that story for a new generation: a sweeping, deeply human portrait of how the modern world was forged in the fires of global war.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Rachel Maddow Show</title>
    <desc>With honesty and rigor, Rachel Maddow uniquely connects dots to advance stories on her show The Rachel Maddow Show. By exposing the layers of complex issues, she reveals their significance to viewers. In her irreverent style, Maddow transcends the narrative and provides unique perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Greg Kelly Reports</title>
    <desc>The hardest-hitting stories from coast to coast: We take you from the Beltway to the Rust Belt and beyond — never forgetting we're here to enlighten, expose, inform, and spotlight the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>On Balance with Leland Vittert</title>
    <desc>The day's hottest subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>American Ninja Warrior</title>
    <desc>American Ninja Warrior is an action-packed series that follows competitors as they tackle a series of challenging obstacle courses in both qualifying and finals rounds across the country. Those that successfully complete a course in their designated region move on to the national finals round in Las Vegas, where they face a stunning four-stage course modeled after the famed Mt. Midoriyama in Japan.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The McBee Dynasty: Real American Cowboys</title>
    <desc>The McBee Dynasty: Real American Cowboys follows patriarch Steve McBee, the hard-working founder of the family business, and his four sons: Steven Jr. the business-minded heir apparent, Cole the underdog who works hard in the field, Jesse the quiet cowboy, and Brayden who has the least interest in farming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Hannity</title>
    <desc>Sean Hannity interviews political figures and newsmakers and offers his own perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629220000 -0400" stop="20260629230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629220000 -0400" stop="20260629230000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Chris Plante: The Right Squad</title>
    <desc>Chris Plante and his "THE RIGHT SQUAD" are the most interesting, informative and funny group of talking heads in the world! It's a big claim. But it's true!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629220000 -0400" stop="20260629230000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Katie Pavlich Tonight</title>
    <desc>Katie Pavlich Tonight offers a conservative take on the day's events while welcoming all viewpoints. The goal: cutting through left-right bias in pursuit of plain facts and honest analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629220000 -0400" stop="20260629230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Gutfeld!</title>
    <desc>Late night show with author, comedian and television host and producer Greg Gutfeld, offering up satirical political and social commentary with a weekly panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629220000 -0400" stop="20260629230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629220300 -0400" stop="20260629230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>History's Greatest Machines with Dolph Lundgren</title>
    <desc>Machines can rewrite history – and no one knows that better than action legend and chemical engineer graduate Dolph Lundgren. Join him as he uncovers the stories behind history's most groundbreaking machines: witness secret stealth helicopters, spy planes outrunning missiles, espionage tech that won wars, to the rocket that took humanity to the moon. Guided by Dolph's keen insight and charisma, this is a thrilling ride through the gears, guts, and genius behind the machines that reshaped our world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629230000 -0400" stop="20260630000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629230000 -0400" stop="20260630000000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Jesse Weber Live</title>
    <desc>A fresh, fast-paced, and often unexpected take on the day's headlines, diving into the biggest stories through the lens of an expert in legal affairs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629230000 -0400" stop="20260630000000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News @ Night</title>
    <desc>Fox News @ Night is a live hour of hard news and analysis of the most compelling stories from Washington and across the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629000000 -0400" stop="20260629020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629000000 -0400" stop="20260629020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630050000 -0400" stop="20260630060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630050000 -0400" stop="20260630060000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends First</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the day, FOX &amp;amp; Friends First delivers all the headlines viewers may have missed overnight, along with a preview of upcoming news events. Presented two hours before FOX &amp;amp; Friends, the first hour of the program is hosted by Todd Piro and Carley Shimkus</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630060000 -0400" stop="20260630090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630060000 -0400" stop="20260630070000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Early</title>
    <desc>Wake up to reliable reporting that delivers the essential facts you need to start your day informed, along with expert commentary and thoughtful analysis. Get an early look at the top stories shaping national and global conversations. Whether it's politics, business, culture, or breaking news, you'll be prepared for whatever the day brings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630060000 -0400" stop="20260630090000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Morning in America</title>
    <desc>Morning in America is NewsNation's live national morning newscast hosted by Markie Martin.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630060000 -0400" stop="20260630090000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends</title>
    <desc>FOX &amp;amp; Friends is a conservative American early-morning news and opinion talk show on the Fox News Channel. It begins at 6:00 a.m. Eastern Time with the latest Fox News Live headlines and news of the morning and continues with a variety of segments including current events, interviews, updates of news stories with correspondents, right-leaning analysis from the hosts, and entertainment segments.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630060000 -0400" stop="20260630070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630070000 -0400" stop="20260630090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America</title>
    <desc>Start your day and weekend with real news and analysis from Rob Finnerty, Michael Grimm &amp;amp; Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630070000 -0400" stop="20260630090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630070000 -0400" stop="20260630090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630070000 -0400" stop="20260630090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630070000 -0400" stop="20260630100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630090000 -0400" stop="20260630110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630090000 -0400" stop="20260630120000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>National Report</title>
    <desc>National Report with Shaun Kraisman and Emma Rechenberg for live breaking news from NY and Washington, on politics, health, finance, and lifestyle that impact you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630090000 -0400" stop="20260630120000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes</title>
    <desc>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes brings you a fast-paced look at the latest from the border to Main Street to the White House and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630090000 -0400" stop="20260630110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630090000 -0400" stop="20260630100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630100000 -0400" stop="20260630110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630100000 -0400" stop="20260630120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630110000 -0400" stop="20260630120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Faulkner Focus</title>
    <desc>Emmy-winning journalist Harris Faulkner provides the latest news driving the day with insightful analysis and interviews with top newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630120000 -0400" stop="20260630140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630120000 -0400" stop="20260630140000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Newsline</title>
    <desc>Bianca de la Garza tackles the big news from D.C., N.Y., across America, and around the world!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630120000 -0400" stop="20260630150000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Nichole Berlie</title>
    <desc>The day's top news headlines with reports from correspondents around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630120000 -0400" stop="20260630130000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Outnumbered</title>
    <desc>Featuring an ensemble of four female panelists and one rotating male, Outnumbered examines the top news stories as well as the leading pop culture and relationship issues dominating the headlines. FNC's Harris Faulkner, Kayleigh McEnany and Emily Compagno lead the program's coverage, while alternating co-panelists weigh in with analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630120000 -0400" stop="20260630130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630130000 -0400" stop="20260630150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630130000 -0400" stop="20260630140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630130000 -0400" stop="20260630160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630140000 -0400" stop="20260630160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630140000 -0400" stop="20260630160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630140000 -0400" stop="20260630150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630150000 -0400" stop="20260630180000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live With Connell McShane</title>
    <desc>Connell McShane presents reports and analysis of the day's national and international newsworthy events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630150000 -0400" stop="20260630160000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Story</title>
    <desc>The Story with Martha MacCallum, anchored by Martha MacCallum, focuses on the stories that are most important to Americans with insight from top newsmakers and analysts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630160000 -0400" stop="20260630180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630160000 -0400" stop="20260630170000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Record with Greta Van Susteren</title>
    <desc>Award-winning journalist Greta Van Susteren digs into the top stories of the day with the focus on why they matter to the American people. Greta speaks with the top newsmakers on both sides of the aisle, creating a conversation and dialogue that is imperative for the nation's well-being.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630160000 -0400" stop="20260630170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Will Cain Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers from across politics, business, culture and sports, The Will Cain Show will offer a comprehensive look at the news of the day in a signature podcast style.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630160000 -0400" stop="20260630170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630170000 -0400" stop="20260630180000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Ed Henry the Big Take</title>
    <desc>Ed Henry offers his common-sense take on the news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630170000 -0400" stop="20260630180000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Five</title>
    <desc>The Five is an American news and talk show on Fox News Channel featuring a rotating panel who discuss current stories, political issues, and pop culture. The show premiered in July 2011, replacing the Glenn Beck program, and airs on weekdays at 5:00 p.m. ET with replays at 4:00 a.m. ET. On October 3, 2011, after successful ratings and high popularity, Fox News announced that The Five would become the permanent 5 p.m. series, as the program had previously been announced to last only during the summer. The Five is currently the second-most-watched program in all of cable news in the United States, placing only behind The O'Reilly Factor, also on the Fox News Channel. The program has occasionally been the number one rated cable news series in the key 25 to 54 viewing demographic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630170000 -0400" stop="20260630190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630180000 -0400" stop="20260630190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630180000 -0400" stop="20260630190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Carl Higbie Frontline</title>
    <desc>Carl Higbie Frontline focuses on providing commonsense news analysis, exposing big government overreach and the media's shortfalls — all while always fighting for American values. Produced from Newsmax's Manhattan studios covering breaking news and exploring key issues such as personal liberty, security, and government transparency.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630180000 -0400" stop="20260630190000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hill on NewsNation combines the power of two trusted news sources into one must-watch hour. The Hill, the nation's #1 political website, and NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, team up to define today's most-pressing issues, and question Washington's power brokers on what matters most to the people they serve and what matters most to Americans.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630180000 -0400" stop="20260630190000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Special Report</title>
    <desc>Special Report with Bret Baier (formerly Special Report with Brit Hume) is an American television news and political commentary program appearing on Fox News Channel, currently hosted by Bret Baier. It airs live each Monday through Friday at 6:00 PM ET. The show focuses on both reporting and analysis of the day's events, with a primary focus on national political news. The show has been a part of the Fox News program lineup since 1998 and is the number one cable news broadcast in its time slot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630183000 -0400" stop="20260630190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630190000 -0400" stop="20260630200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630190000 -0400" stop="20260630200000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Rob Schmitt Tonight</title>
    <desc>Rob Schmitt Tonight locks in all the late-breaking stories that matter to you, and delivers the up-to-the-minute news you need to hear before turning in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630190000 -0400" stop="20260630200000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Elizabeth Vargas Reports</title>
    <desc>In-depth coverage of the biggest news stories of the day; NewsNation's home for exclusive and enterprise reporting; hosted live by Elizabeth Vargas.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630190000 -0400" stop="20260630200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Ingraham Angle</title>
    <desc>The Ingraham Angle cuts through the Washington chatter to speak directly with unexpected voices and the actual people who are impacted by the news of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630190000 -0400" stop="20260630200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>WWE NXT</title>
    <desc>Each Wednesday at 8:00 p.m. ET, WWE Superstars and Divas of tomorrow face off on WWE NXT, a one-hour weekly show that features the brightest and best of WWE's rising stars. WWE NXT showcases the Superstars and Divas from WWE's Performance Center as well as appearances from WWE Superstars and Legends in an intimate setting. WWE NXT broadcasts from the state-of-the-art Full Sail LIVE venue on the Full Sail University in campus in Orlando, Florida.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630210000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Finnerty</title>
    <desc>Finnerty will look to cut through the noise to bring unfiltered truth, sharp debates, and a focus on the most pressing issues facing America today while standing up for American values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630210000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Cuomo</title>
    <desc>Chris Cuomo hosts CUOMO, a no-nonsense show featuring the day's most important news from all perspectives. CUOMO airs weeknights at 8 p.m./7C on NewsNation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>With the talent search open to acts of all ages, America's Got Talent has brought the variety format back to the forefront of American culture by showcasing performers from across the country. The series is a true celebration of the American spirit, featuring a colorful array of singers, dancers, comedians, contortionists, impressionists, jugglers, magicians, ventriloquists and hopeful stars, all vying for their chance to win America's hearts and the $1 million prize.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630210000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Jesse Watters Primetime</title>
    <desc>Jesse Watters brings his fresh take to Primetime. Each night, he'll speak with newsmakers from across the country and give Americans a show where straight talk is the only talk, and the obvious will never be left unsaid.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630210000 -0400" stop="20260630213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>With a record number of Americans trading city life for homes in the suburbs, relationships between neighbors are being put to the test. Neighborhood Wars takes viewers into the homes and backyards of neighbors across the country with some of the most unexpected and emotionally charged events caught on camera. Featuring footage from cell phones, drones, home security cameras and more, the series showcases the kindness and conflict between real-life neighbors throughout the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630210000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630210000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Greg Kelly Reports</title>
    <desc>The hardest-hitting stories from coast to coast: We take you from the Beltway to the Rust Belt and beyond — never forgetting we're here to enlighten, expose, inform, and spotlight the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630210000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>On Balance with Leland Vittert</title>
    <desc>The day's hottest subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630210000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch</title>
    <desc>Gaining full and unprecedented access to one of the most infamous and secretive hotspots of paranormal and UFO-related activities on earth, The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch will feature a team of scientists and experts who will conduct a thorough search of this infamous 512-acre property located in Utah's Uinta Basin. They will attempt to find out the truth behind more than 200 years of mysteries - involving everything from UFO sightings and paranormal activities to animal mutilations and Native American legends of a shape-shifting creature known simply as The Skinwalker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630210000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>In the City</title>
    <desc>In the city that never sleeps, a group of New Yorkers navigates the biggest transitions of their lives — marriage, parenthood, reinvention, and the reality of growing up without growing apart. Can they have it all, or will they need to choose between the lives they've built and the futures they never saw coming?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630210000 -0400" stop="20260630220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Hannity</title>
    <desc>Sean Hannity interviews political figures and newsmakers and offers his own perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630213000 -0400" stop="20260630220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>With a record number of Americans trading city life for homes in the suburbs, relationships between neighbors are being put to the test. Neighborhood Wars takes viewers into the homes and backyards of neighbors across the country with some of the most unexpected and emotionally charged events caught on camera. Featuring footage from cell phones, drones, home security cameras and more, the series showcases the kindness and conflict between real-life neighbors throughout the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630223000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Password</title>
    <desc>Password is a reboot of the 1960s game show in which two teams, composed of a celebrity player and a contestant, attempt to convey mystery words to each other using only single-word clues in order to win a cash prize.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630230000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Chris Plante: The Right Squad</title>
    <desc>Chris Plante and his "THE RIGHT SQUAD" are the most interesting, informative and funny group of talking heads in the world! It's a big claim. But it's true!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630230000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Katie Pavlich Tonight</title>
    <desc>Katie Pavlich Tonight offers a conservative take on the day's events while welcoming all viewpoints. The goal: cutting through left-right bias in pursuit of plain facts and honest analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630230000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Frontline</title>
    <desc>Since it began in 1983, Frontline has been airing public-affairs documentaries that explore a wide scope of the complex human experience. Frontline's goal is to extend the impact of the documentary beyond its initial broadcast by serving as a catalyst for change..</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Gutfeld!</title>
    <desc>Late night show with author, comedian and television host and producer Greg Gutfeld, offering up satirical political and social commentary with a weekly panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220000 -0400" stop="20260630223000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch: Behind the Gates</title>
    <desc>The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch: Behind the Gates offers a more in-depth look at the mysteries surrounding the ranch and the team's investigations, often featuring interviews with team members and experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630220100 -0400" stop="20260630223200 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Squatters</title>
    <desc>Squatters are taking over homes across the country and Flash Shelton is the man who gets them out. With bold tactics and street smarts, Flash and his team face tense and sometimes dangerous situations to help families reclaim their property. Each episode reveals the emotional and high-stakes battles where the fight for justice can quickly escalate, putting everyone involved at risk. This is the struggle to take back what rightfully belongs to them.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630223000 -0400" stop="20260630230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Password</title>
    <desc>Password is a reboot of the 1960s game show in which two teams, composed of a celebrity player and a contestant, attempt to convey mystery words to each other using only single-word clues in order to win a cash prize.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630223200 -0400" stop="20260630233300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Proof Is Out There: Unexplained Edition</title>
    <desc>In this special edition series of The Proof Is Out There, journalist Tony Harris explores some of the most astonishing phenomena ever captured on camera. From UFOs and cryptids to eerie encounters and unexplained forces, Tony and a team of experts analyze the evidence and deliver their verdict.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630223200 -0400" stop="20260630230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Squatters</title>
    <desc>Squatters are taking over homes across the country and Flash Shelton is the man who gets them out. With bold tactics and street smarts, Flash and his team face tense and sometimes dangerous situations to help families reclaim their property. Each episode reveals the emotional and high-stakes battles where the fight for justice can quickly escalate, putting everyone involved at risk. This is the struggle to take back what rightfully belongs to them.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630230000 -0400" stop="20260701000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630230000 -0400" stop="20260701000000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Jesse Weber Live</title>
    <desc>A fresh, fast-paced, and often unexpected take on the day's headlines, diving into the biggest stories through the lens of an expert in legal affairs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630230000 -0400" stop="20260701000000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News @ Night</title>
    <desc>Fox News @ Night is a live hour of hard news and analysis of the most compelling stories from Washington and across the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630000000 -0400" stop="20260630020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630000000 -0400" stop="20260630020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701050000 -0400" stop="20260701060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701050000 -0400" stop="20260701060000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends First</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the day, FOX &amp;amp; Friends First delivers all the headlines viewers may have missed overnight, along with a preview of upcoming news events. Presented two hours before FOX &amp;amp; Friends, the first hour of the program is hosted by Todd Piro and Carley Shimkus</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701060000 -0400" stop="20260701090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701060000 -0400" stop="20260701070000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Early</title>
    <desc>Wake up to reliable reporting that delivers the essential facts you need to start your day informed, along with expert commentary and thoughtful analysis. Get an early look at the top stories shaping national and global conversations. Whether it's politics, business, culture, or breaking news, you'll be prepared for whatever the day brings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701060000 -0400" stop="20260701090000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Morning in America</title>
    <desc>Morning in America is NewsNation's live national morning newscast hosted by Markie Martin.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701060000 -0400" stop="20260701090000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends</title>
    <desc>FOX &amp;amp; Friends is a conservative American early-morning news and opinion talk show on the Fox News Channel. It begins at 6:00 a.m. Eastern Time with the latest Fox News Live headlines and news of the morning and continues with a variety of segments including current events, interviews, updates of news stories with correspondents, right-leaning analysis from the hosts, and entertainment segments.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701060000 -0400" stop="20260701070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701070000 -0400" stop="20260701090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America</title>
    <desc>Start your day and weekend with real news and analysis from Rob Finnerty, Michael Grimm &amp;amp; Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701070000 -0400" stop="20260701090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701070000 -0400" stop="20260701090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701070000 -0400" stop="20260701090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701070000 -0400" stop="20260701100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701090000 -0400" stop="20260701110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701090000 -0400" stop="20260701120000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>National Report</title>
    <desc>National Report with Shaun Kraisman and Emma Rechenberg for live breaking news from NY and Washington, on politics, health, finance, and lifestyle that impact you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701090000 -0400" stop="20260701120000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes</title>
    <desc>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes brings you a fast-paced look at the latest from the border to Main Street to the White House and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701090000 -0400" stop="20260701110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701090000 -0400" stop="20260701100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701100000 -0400" stop="20260701110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701100000 -0400" stop="20260701120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701110000 -0400" stop="20260701120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Faulkner Focus</title>
    <desc>Emmy-winning journalist Harris Faulkner provides the latest news driving the day with insightful analysis and interviews with top newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701120000 -0400" stop="20260701140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701120000 -0400" stop="20260701140000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Newsline</title>
    <desc>Bianca de la Garza tackles the big news from D.C., N.Y., across America, and around the world!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701120000 -0400" stop="20260701150000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Nichole Berlie</title>
    <desc>The day's top news headlines with reports from correspondents around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701120000 -0400" stop="20260701130000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Outnumbered</title>
    <desc>Featuring an ensemble of four female panelists and one rotating male, Outnumbered examines the top news stories as well as the leading pop culture and relationship issues dominating the headlines. FNC's Harris Faulkner, Kayleigh McEnany and Emily Compagno lead the program's coverage, while alternating co-panelists weigh in with analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701120000 -0400" stop="20260701130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701130000 -0400" stop="20260701150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701130000 -0400" stop="20260701140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701130000 -0400" stop="20260701160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701140000 -0400" stop="20260701160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701140000 -0400" stop="20260701160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701140000 -0400" stop="20260701150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701150000 -0400" stop="20260701180000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live With Connell McShane</title>
    <desc>Connell McShane presents reports and analysis of the day's national and international newsworthy events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701150000 -0400" stop="20260701160000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Story</title>
    <desc>The Story with Martha MacCallum, anchored by Martha MacCallum, focuses on the stories that are most important to Americans with insight from top newsmakers and analysts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701160000 -0400" stop="20260701180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701160000 -0400" stop="20260701170000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Record with Greta Van Susteren</title>
    <desc>Award-winning journalist Greta Van Susteren digs into the top stories of the day with the focus on why they matter to the American people. Greta speaks with the top newsmakers on both sides of the aisle, creating a conversation and dialogue that is imperative for the nation's well-being.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701160000 -0400" stop="20260701170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Will Cain Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers from across politics, business, culture and sports, The Will Cain Show will offer a comprehensive look at the news of the day in a signature podcast style.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701160000 -0400" stop="20260701170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701170000 -0400" stop="20260701180000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Ed Henry the Big Take</title>
    <desc>Ed Henry offers his common-sense take on the news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701170000 -0400" stop="20260701180000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Five</title>
    <desc>The Five is an American news and talk show on Fox News Channel featuring a rotating panel who discuss current stories, political issues, and pop culture. The show premiered in July 2011, replacing the Glenn Beck program, and airs on weekdays at 5:00 p.m. ET with replays at 4:00 a.m. ET. On October 3, 2011, after successful ratings and high popularity, Fox News announced that The Five would become the permanent 5 p.m. series, as the program had previously been announced to last only during the summer. The Five is currently the second-most-watched program in all of cable news in the United States, placing only behind The O'Reilly Factor, also on the Fox News Channel. The program has occasionally been the number one rated cable news series in the key 25 to 54 viewing demographic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701170000 -0400" stop="20260701190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701180000 -0400" stop="20260701190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701180000 -0400" stop="20260701190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Carl Higbie Frontline</title>
    <desc>Carl Higbie Frontline focuses on providing commonsense news analysis, exposing big government overreach and the media's shortfalls — all while always fighting for American values. Produced from Newsmax's Manhattan studios covering breaking news and exploring key issues such as personal liberty, security, and government transparency.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701180000 -0400" stop="20260701190000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hill on NewsNation combines the power of two trusted news sources into one must-watch hour. The Hill, the nation's #1 political website, and NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, team up to define today's most-pressing issues, and question Washington's power brokers on what matters most to the people they serve and what matters most to Americans.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701180000 -0400" stop="20260701190000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Special Report</title>
    <desc>Special Report with Bret Baier (formerly Special Report with Brit Hume) is an American television news and political commentary program appearing on Fox News Channel, currently hosted by Bret Baier. It airs live each Monday through Friday at 6:00 PM ET. The show focuses on both reporting and analysis of the day's events, with a primary focus on national political news. The show has been a part of the Fox News program lineup since 1998 and is the number one cable news broadcast in its time slot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701183000 -0400" stop="20260701190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701190000 -0400" stop="20260701200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701190000 -0400" stop="20260701200000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Rob Schmitt Tonight</title>
    <desc>Rob Schmitt Tonight locks in all the late-breaking stories that matter to you, and delivers the up-to-the-minute news you need to hear before turning in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701190000 -0400" stop="20260701200000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Elizabeth Vargas Reports</title>
    <desc>In-depth coverage of the biggest news stories of the day; NewsNation's home for exclusive and enterprise reporting; hosted live by Elizabeth Vargas.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701190000 -0400" stop="20260701200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Ingraham Angle</title>
    <desc>The Ingraham Angle cuts through the Washington chatter to speak directly with unexpected voices and the actual people who are impacted by the news of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701190000 -0400" stop="20260701200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Brilliant Minds</title>
    <desc>Inspired by the extraordinary life and work of world-famous author and physician Oliver Sacks, Brilliant Minds follows a revolutionary, larger-than-life neurologist and his team of interns as they explore the last great frontier - the human mind - while grappling with their own relationships and mental health.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Finnerty</title>
    <desc>Finnerty will look to cut through the noise to bring unfiltered truth, sharp debates, and a focus on the most pressing issues facing America today while standing up for American values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Cuomo</title>
    <desc>Chris Cuomo hosts CUOMO, a no-nonsense show featuring the day's most important news from all perspectives. CUOMO airs weeknights at 8 p.m./7C on NewsNation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Valley</title>
    <desc>The Valley follows a group of close friends as they trade bottle service in West Hollywood for baby bottles in the Valley all while they navigate bustling businesses, rocky relationships and feisty friendships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Jesse Watters Primetime</title>
    <desc>Jesse Watters brings his fresh take to Primetime. Each night, he'll speak with newsmakers from across the country and give Americans a show where straight talk is the only talk, and the obvious will never be left unsaid.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701210000 -0400" stop="20260701220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701210000 -0400" stop="20260701220000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Greg Kelly Reports</title>
    <desc>The hardest-hitting stories from coast to coast: We take you from the Beltway to the Rust Belt and beyond — never forgetting we're here to enlighten, expose, inform, and spotlight the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701210000 -0400" stop="20260701220000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>On Balance with Leland Vittert</title>
    <desc>The day's hottest subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701210000 -0400" stop="20260701213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>My Strange Arrest</title>
    <desc>An in-depth look at the people who were arrested for allegedly committing some of the weirdest, wildest and most bizarre crimes ever. We dig beyond the headlines and the viral videos to look at the incidents and their consequences, hearing the stories from the accused, the arresting officers and eyewitnesses. These are bizarre crimes with real-life ramifications.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701210000 -0400" stop="20260701223400 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Alone</title>
    <desc>Alone places ten hardcore survivalists alone in the wilderness - no camera crew, no teams, no producers - on a single mission to stay alive. At stake is $500,000 awarded to the person who can last the longest. They will face extreme isolation and psychological distress as they plunge into the unknown, self-documenting their experience.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701210000 -0400" stop="20260701220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Next Gen NYC</title>
    <desc>Next Gen NYC follows a tangled web of friends raised in the spotlight — or at least close enough for good lighting — as they stumble into adulthood one brunch, breakup and spontaneous decision at a time. Whether stepping out of their parents' shadows or creating their own legacies from scratch, these twentysomethings are determined to conquer Manhattan — if they can figure out how to adult first. Together, they'll navigate friendships, careers and romance, proving that trouble runs on espresso martinis and questionable decisions.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701210000 -0400" stop="20260701220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Hannity</title>
    <desc>Sean Hannity interviews political figures and newsmakers and offers his own perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701213000 -0400" stop="20260701220000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>My Strange Arrest</title>
    <desc>An in-depth look at the people who were arrested for allegedly committing some of the weirdest, wildest and most bizarre crimes ever. We dig beyond the headlines and the viral videos to look at the incidents and their consequences, hearing the stories from the accused, the arresting officers and eyewitnesses. These are bizarre crimes with real-life ramifications.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701230000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Chris Plante: The Right Squad</title>
    <desc>Chris Plante and his "THE RIGHT SQUAD" are the most interesting, informative and funny group of talking heads in the world! It's a big claim. But it's true!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701230000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Katie Pavlich Tonight</title>
    <desc>Katie Pavlich Tonight offers a conservative take on the day's events while welcoming all viewpoints. The goal: cutting through left-right bias in pursuit of plain facts and honest analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701223100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Swamp Patrol</title>
    <desc>SWAMP PATROL pulls viewers into the unpredictable world of law enforcement operating in America's most unforgiving swamps. From the tangled bayous of Louisiana to the coastal inlets of Florida, Swamp Patrol follows officers in real time through bodycam footage as they respond to a wide range of threats, including armed suspects, drug busts, missing persons, stolen boats, 11-foot gators, and deadly snakes. Every call comes with its own dangers, and in the depths of the swamp, there is no backup. The series offers a captivating look at the chaos and courage required to hold the line in places most people never step.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Gutfeld!</title>
    <desc>Late night show with author, comedian and television host and producer Greg Gutfeld, offering up satirical political and social commentary with a weekly panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220800 -0400" stop="20260701230800 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Mystery at Blind Frog Ranch</title>
    <desc>There are some places on earth where the land just seems different, and Blind Frog Ranch in eastern Utah is one of those places. Locals say the land is cursed. That it's trying to hold on to something. From Aztec treasure to caverns of gold and silver to lost Mormon mines, legends surround Duane Ollinger's 160-acre ranch in Utah's Uintah Basin. But Duane isn't concerned with the lore. After discovering a system of seven underground caves that run through his property, he is singularly focused on finding what's hidden in them - no matter what the cost.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701223200 -0400" stop="20260701230300 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Swamp Patrol</title>
    <desc>SWAMP PATROL pulls viewers into the unpredictable world of law enforcement operating in America's most unforgiving swamps. From the tangled bayous of Louisiana to the coastal inlets of Florida, Swamp Patrol follows officers in real time through bodycam footage as they respond to a wide range of threats, including armed suspects, drug busts, missing persons, stolen boats, 11-foot gators, and deadly snakes. Every call comes with its own dangers, and in the depths of the swamp, there is no backup. The series offers a captivating look at the chaos and courage required to hold the line in places most people never step.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701223400 -0400" stop="20260701233400 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Forged in Fire</title>
    <desc>Forged in Fire features world-class bladesmiths competing against each other to create some of the most iconic edged weapons from history. In each episode, four of the best bladesmiths in the country will come together to put both their skills and reputations on the line. Whether they are making a Japanese katana, a medieval broadsword, or an ancient throwing blade like the chakram, the weapons they forge will be fully functional and lethal works of art and war. The unique histories contained within each weapon will be creatively told during the forging process and the final weapons themselves will be assessed and ruthlessly tested by our panel of expert judges. These dynamic and explosive tests will be individually designed to push the weapons to their absolute limit. One by one, the bladesmiths will be eliminated until only one remains to be crowned the champion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701230000 -0400" stop="20260702000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701230000 -0400" stop="20260702000000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Jesse Weber Live</title>
    <desc>A fresh, fast-paced, and often unexpected take on the day's headlines, diving into the biggest stories through the lens of an expert in legal affairs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701230000 -0400" stop="20260702000000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News @ Night</title>
    <desc>Fox News @ Night is a live hour of hard news and analysis of the most compelling stories from Washington and across the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702050000 -0400" stop="20260702060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702050000 -0400" stop="20260702060000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends First</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the day, FOX &amp;amp; Friends First delivers all the headlines viewers may have missed overnight, along with a preview of upcoming news events. Presented two hours before FOX &amp;amp; Friends, the first hour of the program is hosted by Todd Piro and Carley Shimkus</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702060000 -0400" stop="20260702090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702060000 -0400" stop="20260702070000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Early</title>
    <desc>Wake up to reliable reporting that delivers the essential facts you need to start your day informed, along with expert commentary and thoughtful analysis. Get an early look at the top stories shaping national and global conversations. Whether it's politics, business, culture, or breaking news, you'll be prepared for whatever the day brings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702060000 -0400" stop="20260702090000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Morning in America</title>
    <desc>Morning in America is NewsNation's live national morning newscast hosted by Markie Martin.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702060000 -0400" stop="20260702090000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends</title>
    <desc>FOX &amp;amp; Friends is a conservative American early-morning news and opinion talk show on the Fox News Channel. It begins at 6:00 a.m. Eastern Time with the latest Fox News Live headlines and news of the morning and continues with a variety of segments including current events, interviews, updates of news stories with correspondents, right-leaning analysis from the hosts, and entertainment segments.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702060000 -0400" stop="20260702070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702070000 -0400" stop="20260702090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America</title>
    <desc>Start your day and weekend with real news and analysis from Rob Finnerty, Michael Grimm &amp;amp; Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702070000 -0400" stop="20260702090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702070000 -0400" stop="20260702090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702070000 -0400" stop="20260702090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702070000 -0400" stop="20260702100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702090000 -0400" stop="20260702110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702090000 -0400" stop="20260702120000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>National Report</title>
    <desc>National Report with Shaun Kraisman and Emma Rechenberg for live breaking news from NY and Washington, on politics, health, finance, and lifestyle that impact you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702090000 -0400" stop="20260702120000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes</title>
    <desc>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes brings you a fast-paced look at the latest from the border to Main Street to the White House and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702090000 -0400" stop="20260702110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702090000 -0400" stop="20260702100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702100000 -0400" stop="20260702110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702100000 -0400" stop="20260702120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702110000 -0400" stop="20260702120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Faulkner Focus</title>
    <desc>Emmy-winning journalist Harris Faulkner provides the latest news driving the day with insightful analysis and interviews with top newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702120000 -0400" stop="20260702140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702120000 -0400" stop="20260702140000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Newsline</title>
    <desc>Bianca de la Garza tackles the big news from D.C., N.Y., across America, and around the world!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702120000 -0400" stop="20260702150000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Nichole Berlie</title>
    <desc>The day's top news headlines with reports from correspondents around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702120000 -0400" stop="20260702130000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Outnumbered</title>
    <desc>Featuring an ensemble of four female panelists and one rotating male, Outnumbered examines the top news stories as well as the leading pop culture and relationship issues dominating the headlines. FNC's Harris Faulkner, Kayleigh McEnany and Emily Compagno lead the program's coverage, while alternating co-panelists weigh in with analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702120000 -0400" stop="20260702130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702130000 -0400" stop="20260702150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702130000 -0400" stop="20260702140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702130000 -0400" stop="20260702160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702140000 -0400" stop="20260702160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702140000 -0400" stop="20260702160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702140000 -0400" stop="20260702150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702150000 -0400" stop="20260702180000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live With Connell McShane</title>
    <desc>Connell McShane presents reports and analysis of the day's national and international newsworthy events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702150000 -0400" stop="20260702160000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Story</title>
    <desc>The Story with Martha MacCallum, anchored by Martha MacCallum, focuses on the stories that are most important to Americans with insight from top newsmakers and analysts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702160000 -0400" stop="20260702180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702160000 -0400" stop="20260702170000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Record with Greta Van Susteren</title>
    <desc>Award-winning journalist Greta Van Susteren digs into the top stories of the day with the focus on why they matter to the American people. Greta speaks with the top newsmakers on both sides of the aisle, creating a conversation and dialogue that is imperative for the nation's well-being.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702160000 -0400" stop="20260702170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Will Cain Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers from across politics, business, culture and sports, The Will Cain Show will offer a comprehensive look at the news of the day in a signature podcast style.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702160000 -0400" stop="20260702170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702170000 -0400" stop="20260702180000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Ed Henry the Big Take</title>
    <desc>Ed Henry offers his common-sense take on the news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702170000 -0400" stop="20260702180000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Five</title>
    <desc>The Five is an American news and talk show on Fox News Channel featuring a rotating panel who discuss current stories, political issues, and pop culture. The show premiered in July 2011, replacing the Glenn Beck program, and airs on weekdays at 5:00 p.m. ET with replays at 4:00 a.m. ET. On October 3, 2011, after successful ratings and high popularity, Fox News announced that The Five would become the permanent 5 p.m. series, as the program had previously been announced to last only during the summer. The Five is currently the second-most-watched program in all of cable news in the United States, placing only behind The O'Reilly Factor, also on the Fox News Channel. The program has occasionally been the number one rated cable news series in the key 25 to 54 viewing demographic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702170000 -0400" stop="20260702190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702180000 -0400" stop="20260702190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702180000 -0400" stop="20260702190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Carl Higbie Frontline</title>
    <desc>Carl Higbie Frontline focuses on providing commonsense news analysis, exposing big government overreach and the media's shortfalls — all while always fighting for American values. Produced from Newsmax's Manhattan studios covering breaking news and exploring key issues such as personal liberty, security, and government transparency.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702180000 -0400" stop="20260702190000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hill on NewsNation combines the power of two trusted news sources into one must-watch hour. The Hill, the nation's #1 political website, and NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, team up to define today's most-pressing issues, and question Washington's power brokers on what matters most to the people they serve and what matters most to Americans.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702180000 -0400" stop="20260702190000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Special Report</title>
    <desc>Special Report with Bret Baier (formerly Special Report with Brit Hume) is an American television news and political commentary program appearing on Fox News Channel, currently hosted by Bret Baier. It airs live each Monday through Friday at 6:00 PM ET. The show focuses on both reporting and analysis of the day's events, with a primary focus on national political news. The show has been a part of the Fox News program lineup since 1998 and is the number one cable news broadcast in its time slot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702183000 -0400" stop="20260702190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702190000 -0400" stop="20260702200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702190000 -0400" stop="20260702200000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Rob Schmitt Tonight</title>
    <desc>Rob Schmitt Tonight locks in all the late-breaking stories that matter to you, and delivers the up-to-the-minute news you need to hear before turning in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702190000 -0400" stop="20260702200000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Elizabeth Vargas Reports</title>
    <desc>In-depth coverage of the biggest news stories of the day; NewsNation's home for exclusive and enterprise reporting; hosted live by Elizabeth Vargas.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702190000 -0400" stop="20260702200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Ingraham Angle</title>
    <desc>The Ingraham Angle cuts through the Washington chatter to speak directly with unexpected voices and the actual people who are impacted by the news of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702190000 -0400" stop="20260702200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702200000 -0400" stop="20260702210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Surviving Earth</title>
    <desc>Surviving Earth will take an incredible journey into prehistory to learn the lessons from past mass extinctions.Adopting cutting-edge digital technology, each episode transports the viewer back to meet the bizarre and amazing creatures and breathtaking landscapes of a vibrant lost world. Audiences will witness how life finds a way to survive on a planet where meteors fall, super volcanoes erupt, seas boil and the land moves. From the creators of "Walking with Dinosaurs" and "Primeval," these are the stories of the survivors, fighters and lucky ones that shaped the world we live in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702200000 -0400" stop="20260702210000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Finnerty</title>
    <desc>Finnerty will look to cut through the noise to bring unfiltered truth, sharp debates, and a focus on the most pressing issues facing America today while standing up for American values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702200000 -0400" stop="20260702210000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Cuomo</title>
    <desc>Chris Cuomo hosts CUOMO, a no-nonsense show featuring the day's most important news from all perspectives. CUOMO airs weeknights at 8 p.m./7C on NewsNation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702200000 -0400" stop="20260702210000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>After the First 48</title>
    <desc>After the First 48 revisits some of the most powerful cases originally featured on the First 48 and features exclusive interviews with detectives, prosecutors, defense attorneys, and families of victims. After the First 48 takes viewers through the dramatic and emotional inside story; from the investigation, to the murder trial itself, the verdict and beyond.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702200000 -0400" stop="20260702210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702200000 -0400" stop="20260702210000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Jesse Watters Primetime</title>
    <desc>Jesse Watters brings his fresh take to Primetime. Each night, he'll speak with newsmakers from across the country and give Americans a show where straight talk is the only talk, and the obvious will never be left unsaid.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702200000 -0400" stop="20260702210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702210000 -0400" stop="20260702220000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Americas</title>
    <desc>The Americas showcases the wonders, secrets and fragilities of the world's greatest supercontinent. For the first time, the Americas stars in its own incomparable series, using cutting-edge technology to uncover never-before-seen behavior, and highlight the extraordinary, untold wildlife stories that will deeply connect with millions around the world. Five years in the making and filmed over 180 expeditions, this groundbreaking series reveals the spectacular landscapes of Earth's most varied landmass - the only one to stretch between both poles. The Americas' unprecedented scale and ambition delivers remarkable world firsts; new species, new intimate courtship, dramatic deep sea hunting and some of nature's strangest stories - even a frog that seems to defy death every day. Each hourlong episode features a different iconic location across the Americas: "The Atlantic Coast," "Mexico," "The Wild West," "The Amazon," "The Frozen North," "The Gulf Coast," "The Andes," "The Caribbean," "The West Coast" and "Patagonia."</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702210000 -0400" stop="20260702220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702210000 -0400" stop="20260702220000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Greg Kelly Reports</title>
    <desc>The hardest-hitting stories from coast to coast: We take you from the Beltway to the Rust Belt and beyond — never forgetting we're here to enlighten, expose, inform, and spotlight the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702210000 -0400" stop="20260702220000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>On Balance with Leland Vittert</title>
    <desc>The day's hottest subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702210000 -0400" stop="20260702220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Secrets Declassified with David Duchovny</title>
    <desc>Secrets Declassified tells the incredible stories of government secrets that have only recently come to light. This series proves that secrets can be uncovered, and mysteries can still be unraveled." Each episode will find Duchovny focusing on a different topic, speaking with different experts. Subjects include the real-life story behind Argo and the mystery of the Area 51 conspiracy. Mulder would approve.From black ops and bizarre experiments to deadly cover-ups and nefarious gadgets, David Duchovny pulls the curtain back on all the government secrets in modern history we always suspected, but were never given the answers to. Through the strange and shocking things countries the world over ? and those who work for them ? have done in the name of national interest, we?ll investigate the explosive evidence from newly declassified files that will finally shine a new light on what?s really going on deep in the shadows.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702210000 -0400" stop="20260702220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Hannity</title>
    <desc>Sean Hannity interviews political figures and newsmakers and offers his own perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702210000 -0400" stop="20260702220000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>E:60</title>
    <desc>E:60 is ESPN's first multi-subject prime-time newsmagazine program offering a combination of investigative features, profiles of intriguing sports personalities, and cutting edge stories on innovation in the sports world, including emerging sports and new technology. The series will tell life stories that relate or have a basis in sports, melding its stories with a glimpse of the reporters' experiences discussing the story ideas. The show will be produced and aired in high definition, a first for the newsmagazine genre.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702220000 -0400" stop="20260702230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702220000 -0400" stop="20260702230000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Chris Plante: The Right Squad</title>
    <desc>Chris Plante and his "THE RIGHT SQUAD" are the most interesting, informative and funny group of talking heads in the world! It's a big claim. But it's true!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702220000 -0400" stop="20260702230000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Katie Pavlich Tonight</title>
    <desc>Katie Pavlich Tonight offers a conservative take on the day's events while welcoming all viewpoints. The goal: cutting through left-right bias in pursuit of plain facts and honest analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702220000 -0400" stop="20260702230000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Killer Investigations</title>
    <desc>Detectives chase down leads, prosecutors go head-to-head with defense attorneys, and juries wrestle with life-or-death decisions.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702220000 -0400" stop="20260702230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Gutfeld!</title>
    <desc>Late night show with author, comedian and television host and producer Greg Gutfeld, offering up satirical political and social commentary with a weekly panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702220000 -0400" stop="20260702230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702220500 -0400" stop="20260702230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Ancient Aliens</title>
    <desc>Ancient Aliens explores the controversial theory that extraterrestrials have visited Earth for millions of years. From the age of the dinosaurs to ancient Egypt, from early cave drawings to continued mass sightings in the US, each episode in this hit History series gives historic depth to the questions, speculations, provocative controversies, first-hand accounts and grounded theories surrounding this age old debate. Did intelligent beings from outer space visit Earth thousands of years ago?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702230000 -0400" stop="20260703000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702230000 -0400" stop="20260703000000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Jesse Weber Live</title>
    <desc>A fresh, fast-paced, and often unexpected take on the day's headlines, diving into the biggest stories through the lens of an expert in legal affairs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702230000 -0400" stop="20260703000000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News @ Night</title>
    <desc>Fox News @ Night is a live hour of hard news and analysis of the most compelling stories from Washington and across the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703050000 -0400" stop="20260703060000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends First</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the day, FOX &amp;amp; Friends First delivers all the headlines viewers may have missed overnight, along with a preview of upcoming news events. Presented two hours before FOX &amp;amp; Friends, the first hour of the program is hosted by Todd Piro and Carley Shimkus</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703060000 -0400" stop="20260703070000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America Early</title>
    <desc>Wake up to reliable reporting that delivers the essential facts you need to start your day informed, along with expert commentary and thoughtful analysis. Get an early look at the top stories shaping national and global conversations. Whether it's politics, business, culture, or breaking news, you'll be prepared for whatever the day brings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703060000 -0400" stop="20260703090000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Morning in America</title>
    <desc>Morning in America is NewsNation's live national morning newscast hosted by Markie Martin.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703060000 -0400" stop="20260703090000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>FOX &amp; Friends</title>
    <desc>FOX &amp;amp; Friends is a conservative American early-morning news and opinion talk show on the Fox News Channel. It begins at 6:00 a.m. Eastern Time with the latest Fox News Live headlines and news of the morning and continues with a variety of segments including current events, interviews, updates of news stories with correspondents, right-leaning analysis from the hosts, and entertainment segments.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703060000 -0400" stop="20260703070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703070000 -0400" stop="20260703090000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Wake Up America</title>
    <desc>Start your day and weekend with real news and analysis from Rob Finnerty, Michael Grimm &amp;amp; Sarah Williamson and team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703070000 -0400" stop="20260703090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703070000 -0400" stop="20260703090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703070000 -0400" stop="20260703090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703070000 -0400" stop="20260703100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703090000 -0400" stop="20260703120000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>National Report</title>
    <desc>National Report with Shaun Kraisman and Emma Rechenberg for live breaking news from NY and Washington, on politics, health, finance, and lifestyle that impact you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703090000 -0400" stop="20260703120000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes</title>
    <desc>NewsNation Live with Marni Hughes brings you a fast-paced look at the latest from the border to Main Street to the White House and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703090000 -0400" stop="20260703110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703090000 -0400" stop="20260703100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703100000 -0400" stop="20260703110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703100000 -0400" stop="20260703120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703110000 -0400" stop="20260703120000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Faulkner Focus</title>
    <desc>Emmy-winning journalist Harris Faulkner provides the latest news driving the day with insightful analysis and interviews with top newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703120000 -0400" stop="20260703140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703120000 -0400" stop="20260703140000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Newsline</title>
    <desc>Bianca de la Garza tackles the big news from D.C., N.Y., across America, and around the world!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703120000 -0400" stop="20260703150000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live with Nichole Berlie</title>
    <desc>The day's top news headlines with reports from correspondents around the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703120000 -0400" stop="20260703130000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Outnumbered</title>
    <desc>Featuring an ensemble of four female panelists and one rotating male, Outnumbered examines the top news stories as well as the leading pop culture and relationship issues dominating the headlines. FNC's Harris Faulkner, Kayleigh McEnany and Emily Compagno lead the program's coverage, while alternating co-panelists weigh in with analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703120000 -0400" stop="20260703130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703130000 -0400" stop="20260703150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703130000 -0400" stop="20260703140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703130000 -0400" stop="20260703160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703140000 -0400" stop="20260703160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703140000 -0400" stop="20260703150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703150000 -0400" stop="20260703180000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>NewsNation Live With Connell McShane</title>
    <desc>Connell McShane presents reports and analysis of the day's national and international newsworthy events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703150000 -0400" stop="20260703160000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Story</title>
    <desc>The Story with Martha MacCallum, anchored by Martha MacCallum, focuses on the stories that are most important to Americans with insight from top newsmakers and analysts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703160000 -0400" stop="20260703170000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Record with Greta Van Susteren</title>
    <desc>Award-winning journalist Greta Van Susteren digs into the top stories of the day with the focus on why they matter to the American people. Greta speaks with the top newsmakers on both sides of the aisle, creating a conversation and dialogue that is imperative for the nation's well-being.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703160000 -0400" stop="20260703170000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Will Cain Show</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with newsmakers from across politics, business, culture and sports, The Will Cain Show will offer a comprehensive look at the news of the day in a signature podcast style.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703160000 -0400" stop="20260703170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703170000 -0400" stop="20260703180000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Ed Henry the Big Take</title>
    <desc>Ed Henry offers his common-sense take on the news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703170000 -0400" stop="20260703180000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Five</title>
    <desc>The Five is an American news and talk show on Fox News Channel featuring a rotating panel who discuss current stories, political issues, and pop culture. The show premiered in July 2011, replacing the Glenn Beck program, and airs on weekdays at 5:00 p.m. ET with replays at 4:00 a.m. ET. On October 3, 2011, after successful ratings and high popularity, Fox News announced that The Five would become the permanent 5 p.m. series, as the program had previously been announced to last only during the summer. The Five is currently the second-most-watched program in all of cable news in the United States, placing only behind The O'Reilly Factor, also on the Fox News Channel. The program has occasionally been the number one rated cable news series in the key 25 to 54 viewing demographic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703170000 -0400" stop="20260703190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703180000 -0400" stop="20260703190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Carl Higbie Frontline</title>
    <desc>Carl Higbie Frontline focuses on providing commonsense news analysis, exposing big government overreach and the media's shortfalls — all while always fighting for American values. Produced from Newsmax's Manhattan studios covering breaking news and exploring key issues such as personal liberty, security, and government transparency.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703180000 -0400" stop="20260703190000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>The Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hill on NewsNation combines the power of two trusted news sources into one must-watch hour. The Hill, the nation's #1 political website, and NewsNation, America's fastest-growing cable news network, team up to define today's most-pressing issues, and question Washington's power brokers on what matters most to the people they serve and what matters most to Americans.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703180000 -0400" stop="20260703190000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Special Report</title>
    <desc>Special Report with Bret Baier (formerly Special Report with Brit Hume) is an American television news and political commentary program appearing on Fox News Channel, currently hosted by Bret Baier. It airs live each Monday through Friday at 6:00 PM ET. The show focuses on both reporting and analysis of the day's events, with a primary focus on national political news. The show has been a part of the Fox News program lineup since 1998 and is the number one cable news broadcast in its time slot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703183000 -0400" stop="20260703190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703190000 -0400" stop="20260703200000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Rob Schmitt Tonight</title>
    <desc>Rob Schmitt Tonight locks in all the late-breaking stories that matter to you, and delivers the up-to-the-minute news you need to hear before turning in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703190000 -0400" stop="20260703200000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Elizabeth Vargas Reports</title>
    <desc>In-depth coverage of the biggest news stories of the day; NewsNation's home for exclusive and enterprise reporting; hosted live by Elizabeth Vargas.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703190000 -0400" stop="20260703200000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>The Ingraham Angle</title>
    <desc>The Ingraham Angle cuts through the Washington chatter to speak directly with unexpected voices and the actual people who are impacted by the news of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703190000 -0400" stop="20260703200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703200000 -0400" stop="20260703210000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Finnerty</title>
    <desc>Finnerty will look to cut through the noise to bring unfiltered truth, sharp debates, and a focus on the most pressing issues facing America today while standing up for American values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703200000 -0400" stop="20260703210000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Cuomo</title>
    <desc>Chris Cuomo hosts CUOMO, a no-nonsense show featuring the day's most important news from all perspectives. CUOMO airs weeknights at 8 p.m./7C on NewsNation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703200000 -0400" stop="20260703203000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Washington Week with The Atlantic</title>
    <desc>On Washington Week (formerly Washington Week with Gwen Ifill) guest journalists weigh in on issues of the week in this venerable roundtable, the first program ever fed by PBS (previously it had aired on WETA-TV in Washington, D.C., and other East Coast public stations). Though its format is panel discussion, there have been occasional one-on-one interviews, a notable example being host Paul Duke's 1994 White House visit with President Bill Clinton. The series won a DuPont-Columbia University Award in 1974.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703200000 -0400" stop="20260703210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703200000 -0400" stop="20260703210000 -0400" channel="STARZ.US">
    <title>Power Book III: Raising Kanan</title>
    <desc>Power Book III: Raising Kanan is a prequel story that takes viewers back to the '90s and the early years of iconic Power character Kanan Stark.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703200000 -0400" stop="20260703210000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Jesse Watters Primetime</title>
    <desc>Jesse Watters brings his fresh take to Primetime. Each night, he'll speak with newsmakers from across the country and give Americans a show where straight talk is the only talk, and the obvious will never be left unsaid.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703203000 -0400" stop="20260703210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Firing Line with Margaret Hoover</title>
    <desc>Firing Line with Margaret Hoover maintains the character of the original, providing a platform that is diligent in its commitment to civility and the rigorous exchange of opinion. Interviews and debates will highlight leading lights from the left and right, complemented by archival footage from the original Firing Line to remind viewers of longstanding conservative and liberal arguments, where they've been disproved or reinforced over time.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703220000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>President and Mrs. Obama wanted to honor America's 250th anniversary and celebrate the unique history of our nation on this special occasion....But then Larry David called.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703220000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Greg Kelly Reports</title>
    <desc>The hardest-hitting stories from coast to coast: We take you from the Beltway to the Rust Belt and beyond — never forgetting we're here to enlighten, expose, inform, and spotlight the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703220000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>On Balance with Leland Vittert</title>
    <desc>The day's hottest subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703213000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Totally Funny Animals features caught-on-camera videos that highlight the outrageous and wacky world of animals. Hosted by comedian Andy Woodhull, this clip show features everything from sneezing cats and calamitous canines to dumpster-diving bears and rascally racoons.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703220100 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>The Last Woodsmen</title>
    <desc>The Last Woodsmen takes us deep into the secluded wilderness with these courageous and highly skilled loggers as they literally risk their lives. It's a rarely explored, dangerous business which translates to incredibly engrossing television.On a floating barge hundreds of miles from civilization, veteran logger Jared Douglas puts everything on the line to harvest the largest timber in the world. One misstep in this high-risk industry could cost tens of thousands of dollars, or even a life. Joining him at the edge of the world is a tight-knit crew of lumbermen who, with only axes and hand-held power saws, take down massive, highly valuable trees that can be worth up to $70K each.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703220000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Hannity</title>
    <desc>Sean Hannity interviews political figures and newsmakers and offers his own perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703213000 -0400" stop="20260703220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Totally Funny Animals features caught-on-camera videos that highlight the outrageous and wacky world of animals. Hosted by comedian Andy Woodhull, this clip show features everything from sneezing cats and calamitous canines to dumpster-diving bears and rascally racoons.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703220000 -0400" stop="20260703230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703220000 -0400" stop="20260703230000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Chris Plante: The Right Squad</title>
    <desc>Chris Plante and his "THE RIGHT SQUAD" are the most interesting, informative and funny group of talking heads in the world! It's a big claim. But it's true!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703220000 -0400" stop="20260703230000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Katie Pavlich Tonight</title>
    <desc>Katie Pavlich Tonight offers a conservative take on the day's events while welcoming all viewpoints. The goal: cutting through left-right bias in pursuit of plain facts and honest analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703220000 -0400" stop="20260703230000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Gutfeld!</title>
    <desc>Late night show with author, comedian and television host and producer Greg Gutfeld, offering up satirical political and social commentary with a weekly panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703230000 -0400" stop="20260704000000 -0400" channel="NewsNation.US">
    <title>Jesse Weber Live</title>
    <desc>A fresh, fast-paced, and often unexpected take on the day's headlines, diving into the biggest stories through the lens of an expert in legal affairs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703230000 -0400" stop="20260704000000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>Fox News @ Night</title>
    <desc>Fox News @ Night is a live hour of hard news and analysis of the most compelling stories from Washington and across the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627060000 -0400" stop="20260627091500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Milkshake!</title>
    <desc>Milkshake! is presented by a number of different presenters who introduce children's TV shows every morning on Channel 5.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627140000 -0400" stop="20260627150000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Dermot's Taste of Ireland</title>
    <desc>From traditional Irish stew to soda bread, fresh seafood, and boxty potato pancakes - Dermot will taste his way across the island, meeting the chefs and locals that champion and celebrate Ireland's gastronomic heritage. Having opened two of his own fish-themed restaurants and sharing some of his favourite home recipes on ITV's This Morning, he is now taking his passion on the road whilst exploring Ireland's ancient landscapes, diverse cities and stunning coastlines. From Michelin Star restaurants in the ‘Gourmet Capital of Ireland' Kinsale; to fishing for oysters by the sea in Cork; sitting down for some home-grown comfort food in Wexford; and exploring the buzz of the Dublin food scene; before venturing across to Northern Ireland and the bustling city of Belfast and beyond - Dermot's Taste of Ireland promises to be a foodie delight, full of surprises.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627170500 -0400" stop="20260627180500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>The Royals: Uncensored</title>
    <desc>Katie Nicholl and Jo Elvin host this new show that pulls back the velvet curtain on the world's most famous family with fearless debate, insider analysis and exclusive insights.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627172000 -0400" stop="20260627180500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Bridge of Lies Celebrity Specials</title>
    <desc>Teams of celebrities take on the nail-biting quiz hosted by Ross Kemp.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627183000 -0400" stop="20260627200000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Formula 1</title>
    <desc>Steve Jones presents Channel 4's Formula1® comprehensive highlights coverage with expert analysis provided by 13-time Grands Prix winner David Coulthard.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627200000 -0400" stop="20260627210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Alexander Armstrong Across America</title>
    <desc>Alexander Armstrong embarks on a journey across the United States to explore how a nation founded on bold ideals has grown into one of the world's most powerful and complex countries. From historic heartlands to modern extremes, this is a country shaped by its past but constantly reinventing itself.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628060000 -0400" stop="20260628091500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Milkshake!</title>
    <desc>Milkshake! is presented by a number of different presenters who introduce children's TV shows every morning on Channel 5.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628131500 -0400" stop="20260628135000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Songs of Praise</title>
    <desc>Songs of Praise is a BBC Television religious programme that presents Christian hymns which first aired in October 1961. The first edition was broadcast from the Tabernacle Baptist Church in Cardiff, and the series is one of the longest-running of its kind on television anywhere in the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628135000 -0400" stop="20260628140500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Points of View</title>
    <desc>The show that lets you air your views on the BBC's television programmes.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628140000 -0400" stop="20260628150000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Dermot's Taste of Ireland</title>
    <desc>From traditional Irish stew to soda bread, fresh seafood, and boxty potato pancakes - Dermot will taste his way across the island, meeting the chefs and locals that champion and celebrate Ireland's gastronomic heritage. Having opened two of his own fish-themed restaurants and sharing some of his favourite home recipes on ITV's This Morning, he is now taking his passion on the road whilst exploring Ireland's ancient landscapes, diverse cities and stunning coastlines. From Michelin Star restaurants in the ‘Gourmet Capital of Ireland' Kinsale; to fishing for oysters by the sea in Cork; sitting down for some home-grown comfort food in Wexford; and exploring the buzz of the Dublin food scene; before venturing across to Northern Ireland and the bustling city of Belfast and beyond - Dermot's Taste of Ireland promises to be a foodie delight, full of surprises.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628183000 -0400" stop="20260628193000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Countryfile</title>
    <desc>The people, places and stories making news in the British countryside.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628183000 -0400" stop="20260628210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Formula 1</title>
    <desc>Steve Jones presents Channel 4's Formula1® comprehensive highlights coverage with expert analysis provided by 13-time Grands Prix winner David Coulthard.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628210000 -0400" stop="20260628220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Free Nelson Mandela</title>
    <desc>The story of Nelson Mandela's journey from activist to revolutionary prisoner, and the global movement and musical activism that helped bring his freedom.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629060000 -0400" stop="20260629091500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Milkshake!</title>
    <desc>Milkshake! is presented by a number of different presenters who introduce children's TV shows every morning on Channel 5.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629091500 -0400" stop="20260629113000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Jeremy Vine</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Vine and Storm discuss the latest news and get your views and opinions of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629100000 -0400" stop="20260629123000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>This Morning</title>
    <desc>A long-running daytime magazine show co-hosted by two presenters live on weekdays since 1988. Features news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629113000 -0400" stop="20260629124500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Storm &amp; Alexis</title>
    <desc>Two of 5's much-loved faces team up to focus on the issues that matter most to viewers - with your opinions front and centre.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629123000 -0400" stop="20260629134500 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629125000 -0400" stop="20260629140000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Matt Allwright</title>
    <desc>Matt looks at the big news stories developing during the day and offers help and advice to save you money and make your lives a little easier.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629140000 -0400" stop="20260629150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629141000 -0400" stop="20260629150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Dover 24/7: Britain's Busiest Port</title>
    <desc>Dover 24/7: Britain's Busiest Port takes viewers inside one of the UK's most critical transport hubs, the Port of Dover.The series takes viewers inside some of the key port control centres to meet frontline staff and shine a light on the teamwork, expertise, operational challenges, and crucial minute-by-minute decisions that impact millions around the UK to reveal some of the huge 24/7 operation that keeps the nation's most important transport hub open for business. From the terminal and port control teams to the Port of Dover Police and the ferry and cruise companies, viewers will get to know the individuals keeping the port moving around the clock.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Police Interceptors</title>
    <desc>Follow the action-packed lives of the high-speed police interception unit. Led by specially trained officers and equipped with the fastest vehicles in the force, the team tackles the most difficult-to-catch criminals on a daily basis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Cameras film around the clock in some of Britain's busiest A&amp;amp;E departments, where stories of life, love and loss unfold every day</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629213000 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.GB">
    <title>Stupid Central</title>
    <desc>Babatunde Aléshé presents funny videos from the internet.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629210000 -0400" stop="20260629213000 -0400" channel="Quest.GB">
    <title>Shed and Buried</title>
    <desc>The nation's favorite biker, Henry Cole, and ace-engineer, Sam 'The Bike Whisperer' Lovegrove, resume their quest to discover the amazing vintage vehicles lying abandoned in Britain's sheds. Motorbikes, cars, jeeps, tractors, yachts - whatever it is, they'll find it, do it up and flog it for a tidy profit!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629213000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.GB">
    <title>Stupid Central</title>
    <desc>Babatunde Aléshé presents funny videos from the internet.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629213000 -0400" stop="20260629220000 -0400" channel="Quest.GB">
    <title>Shed and Buried</title>
    <desc>The nation's favorite biker, Henry Cole, and ace-engineer, Sam 'The Bike Whisperer' Lovegrove, resume their quest to discover the amazing vintage vehicles lying abandoned in Britain's sheds. Motorbikes, cars, jeeps, tractors, yachts - whatever it is, they'll find it, do it up and flog it for a tidy profit!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629230000 -0400" stop="20260630000000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Today at Wimbledon</title>
    <desc>A look back at the day's action and a preview of the big matches.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630060000 -0400" stop="20260630091500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Milkshake!</title>
    <desc>Milkshake! is presented by a number of different presenters who introduce children's TV shows every morning on Channel 5.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630091500 -0400" stop="20260630113000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Jeremy Vine</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Vine and Storm discuss the latest news and get your views and opinions of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630100000 -0400" stop="20260630123000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>This Morning</title>
    <desc>A long-running daytime magazine show co-hosted by two presenters live on weekdays since 1988. Features news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630113000 -0400" stop="20260630124500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Storm &amp; Alexis</title>
    <desc>Two of 5's much-loved faces team up to focus on the issues that matter most to viewers - with your opinions front and centre.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630123000 -0400" stop="20260630134500 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630125000 -0400" stop="20260630140000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Matt Allwright</title>
    <desc>Matt looks at the big news stories developing during the day and offers help and advice to save you money and make your lives a little easier.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630140000 -0400" stop="20260630150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630141000 -0400" stop="20260630150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Bake Off: The Professionals</title>
    <desc>Twelve professional duos from across the U.K. go head to head in a series of competitive heats judged by celebrated pastry chefs Cherish Finden and Benoit Blin.In each episode the expert pairs are challenged to two rounds that will test their professional ability and allow them to showcase their creative flair. A new presenting line up of Tom Allen and Liam Charles will offer their own comedic take on events in the professional's kitchen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630200000 -0400" stop="20260630210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Reuben: Life in the Dales</title>
    <desc>Hill shepherds' son 19-year-old Reuben Owen from Channel 5's Our Yorkshire Farm is back, attempting to grow his new heavy plant machinery business with his best friends Tommy and Sarah in the remote Yorkshire Dales.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260630230500 -0400" stop="20260701000500 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Today at Wimbledon</title>
    <desc>A look back at the day's action and a preview of the big matches.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701060000 -0400" stop="20260701091500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Milkshake!</title>
    <desc>Milkshake! is presented by a number of different presenters who introduce children's TV shows every morning on Channel 5.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701091500 -0400" stop="20260701113000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Jeremy Vine</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Vine and Storm discuss the latest news and get your views and opinions of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701100000 -0400" stop="20260701123000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>This Morning</title>
    <desc>A long-running daytime magazine show co-hosted by two presenters live on weekdays since 1988. Features news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701113000 -0400" stop="20260701124500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Storm &amp; Alexis</title>
    <desc>Two of 5's much-loved faces team up to focus on the issues that matter most to viewers - with your opinions front and centre.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701123000 -0400" stop="20260701134500 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701125000 -0400" stop="20260701140000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Matt Allwright</title>
    <desc>Matt looks at the big news stories developing during the day and offers help and advice to save you money and make your lives a little easier.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701140000 -0400" stop="20260701150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701141000 -0400" stop="20260701150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Location, Location, Location</title>
    <desc>No floorboard is left unturned as dynamic property experts Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help house hunters find the perfect home in the perfect location.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Bloodline Detectives</title>
    <desc>Bloodline Detectives focuses on familial DNA investigation, a search technique which uses genetic material from relatives to track down a suspect to solve violent crimes.Each episode shows detectives from all over the world solving cold cases by using the DNA of family members and how that additional DNA information is revolutionising genetic profiling to solve criminal cases.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701220000 -0400" stop="20260701230000 -0400" channel="Discovery.GB">
    <title>Mighty Truckers</title>
    <desc>Being a truck driver isn't easy - long hours, huge loads and busy roads are just some of the issues. Truckers from Germany, Italy and Holland share their journeys.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701230000 -0400" stop="20260702000000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Today at Wimbledon</title>
    <desc>A look back at the day's action and a preview of the big matches.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702060000 -0400" stop="20260702091500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Milkshake!</title>
    <desc>Milkshake! is presented by a number of different presenters who introduce children's TV shows every morning on Channel 5.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702091500 -0400" stop="20260702113000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Jeremy Vine</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Vine and Storm discuss the latest news and get your views and opinions of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702100000 -0400" stop="20260702123000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>This Morning</title>
    <desc>A long-running daytime magazine show co-hosted by two presenters live on weekdays since 1988. Features news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702113000 -0400" stop="20260702124500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Storm &amp; Alexis</title>
    <desc>Two of 5's much-loved faces team up to focus on the issues that matter most to viewers - with your opinions front and centre.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702123000 -0400" stop="20260702133000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702125000 -0400" stop="20260702140000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Matt Allwright</title>
    <desc>Matt looks at the big news stories developing during the day and offers help and advice to save you money and make your lives a little easier.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702140000 -0400" stop="20260702150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702141000 -0400" stop="20260702150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260702230000 -0400" stop="20260703000000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Today at Wimbledon</title>
    <desc>A look back at the day's action and a preview of the big matches.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703060000 -0400" stop="20260703091500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Milkshake!</title>
    <desc>Milkshake! is presented by a number of different presenters who introduce children's TV shows every morning on Channel 5.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703091500 -0400" stop="20260703113000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Jeremy Vine</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Vine and Storm discuss the latest news and get your views and opinions of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703100000 -0400" stop="20260703123000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>This Morning</title>
    <desc>A long-running daytime magazine show co-hosted by two presenters live on weekdays since 1988. Features news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703113000 -0400" stop="20260703124500 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Storm &amp; Alexis</title>
    <desc>Two of 5's much-loved faces team up to focus on the issues that matter most to viewers - with your opinions front and centre.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703123000 -0400" stop="20260703134500 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703125000 -0400" stop="20260703140000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Matt Allwright</title>
    <desc>Matt looks at the big news stories developing during the day and offers help and advice to save you money and make your lives a little easier.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703140000 -0400" stop="20260703150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703143500 -0400" stop="20260703152500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703160000 -0400" stop="20260703174500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Formula 1</title>
    <desc>Steve Jones presents Channel 4's Formula1® comprehensive highlights coverage with expert analysis provided by 13-time Grands Prix winner David Coulthard.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703220000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Gardeners' World</title>
    <desc>Gardening show packed with good ideas, tips, advice from experts and timely reminders to get the most out of your garden, whatever its size or type.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703210000 -0400" stop="20260703220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Celebrity Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>A rolling cast of famous faces, some of Britain's best loved personalities, turn their hand to being the country's most opinionated viewers, sharing their opinions on what they have been watching during the week.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260703230000 -0400" stop="20260704000000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Today at Wimbledon</title>
    <desc>A look back at the day's action and a preview of the big matches.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628090000 -0400" stop="20260628100000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Insiders</title>
    <desc>Australia's must-watch political program continues to be a platform for the country's best political analysts and commentators, taking you to the heart of the action every Sunday morning.Insiders entered a very crowded Sunday morning political market in 2001. But our approach was to provide coverage with so many more elements, and to do it in a way that is informative but irreverent. And of course have a few laughs along the way. If you took politics too seriously you'd go mad," said founding host Barrie Cassidy.Insiders is the most watched morning show on Australian TV any day of the week. So start your week with the program the politicians rely on to find out what's going on.Insiders is broadcast on Sundays from 9am to 10am (AEST) on ABC TV and the ABC News channel.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628183000 -0400" stop="20260628190000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Compass</title>
    <desc>Compass explores the Australian soul - our beliefs, our ethical dilemmas and the changing face of our spirituality, with new host, popular journalist and broadcaster, Indira Naidoo.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260628193000 -0400" stop="20260628203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Race Around The World</title>
    <desc>In a time defined by fast-paced narratives and global connection, Race Around the World returns both as a homage to its original spirit and a bold reimagining. It celebrates the raw power of authentic, on-the-ground storytelling and the boundless curiosity that fuels it.The revival of the much-loved format is set to deliver fresh perspectives, discover new creative talent and reaffirm the ABC's commitment to original Australian content.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629200000 -0400" stop="20260629203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Deep End: The Scott Miller Story</title>
    <desc>A compelling new two-part documentary charting the dramatic rise and fall of Olympic swimmer Scott Miller, and his ongoing fight to rebuild his life. Once a golden boy of Australian sport, Scott Miller had it all: medals, fame, and a nation's admiration. Then came personal tragedy and a fall into addiction, crime and eventually prison.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629203000 -0400" stop="20260629211500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Four Corners</title>
    <desc>Four Corners is Australia's premier television current affairs program. It has been part of the national story since August 1961, exposing scandals, triggering inquiries, firing debate, confronting taboos and interpreting fads, trends and sub-cultures. Its consistently high standards of journalism and film-making have earned international recognition and an array of Walkleys, Logies and other national awards.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629212000 -0400" stop="20260629213500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Media Watch</title>
    <desc>Media Watch is Australia's leading forum for media analysis and comment.Conflicts of interest, bank backflips, deceit, misrepresentation, manipulation, plagiarism, abuse of power, technical lies and straight out fraud: Media Watch has built an unrivalled record of exposing media shenanigans since it first went to air in 1989.The media provides the information we need to make decisions about our lives, but how reliable are the media reports that shape our views of the world?Media Watch turns the spotlight onto those who literally 'make the news': the reporters, editors, sub-editors, producers, camera operators, sound recordists and photographers who claim to deliver the world to our doorsteps, radios, computers and living rooms. We also keep an eye on those who try to manipulate the media: the PR consultants, spin-doctors, lobbyists and "news makers" who set the agenda.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260629213500 -0400" stop="20260629220500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Planet America</title>
    <desc>Chas Licciardello and John Barron set out to discover the real America - its politics and its people - with analysis from US and Australian experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701200000 -0400" stop="20260701203500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Gruen</title>
    <desc>The Gruen Transfer is about advertising, how it works, and how it works on us. It decodes and defuses the commercial messages that swirl through our lives, with the help of a panel of ad industry experts. From Season 5 the show was renamed "Gruen Planet" and expanded the topics covered to include political and commercial "spin" as well as advertising. In 2015 it is re-named as Gruen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260701203500 -0400" stop="20260701212500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Guy Montgomery's Guy Mont Spelling Bee</title>
    <desc>Get ready to laugh-out-loud as Guy Montgomery and his loyal assistant Aaron Chen are joined by some of Australia's favourite personalities, testing their spelling prowess with wildly inventive spelling challenges designed to befuddle, bamboozle, and bedazzle them all.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
</tv>