<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv generator-info-name="TVMaze EPG Generator" generator-info-url="https://www.tvmaze.com/api">
  <channel id="MS NOW.US">
    <display-name>MS NOW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CNN.US">
    <display-name>CNN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.US">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NBC.US">
    <display-name>NBC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CBS.US">
    <display-name>CBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL Network.US">
    <display-name>NFL Network</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Syndication.US">
    <display-name>Syndication</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Fox News Channel.US">
    <display-name>Fox News Channel</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ESPN.US">
    <display-name>ESPN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Newsmax.US">
    <display-name>Newsmax</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Bravo.US">
    <display-name>Bravo</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery.US">
    <display-name>Discovery</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="PBS.US">
    <display-name>PBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="History.US">
    <display-name>History</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Comedy Central.US">
    <display-name>Comedy Central</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="The CW.US">
    <display-name>The CW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="FOX.US">
    <display-name>FOX</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="HBO.US">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="A&amp;E.US">
    <display-name>A&amp;E</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="National Geographic.US">
    <display-name>National Geographic</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="STARZ.US">
    <display-name>STARZ</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ITV1.GB">
    <display-name>ITV1</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="5.GB">
    <display-name>5</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Channel 4.GB">
    <display-name>Channel 4</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC One.GB">
    <display-name>BBC One</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="National Geographic.GB">
    <display-name>National Geographic</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC Alba.GB">
    <display-name>BBC Alba</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Quest.GB">
    <display-name>Quest</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="E4.GB">
    <display-name>E4</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <display-name>TRUE CRIME</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC Two.GB">
    <display-name>BBC Two</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Sky Arts.GB">
    <display-name>Sky Arts</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Citytv.CA">
    <display-name>Citytv</display-name>
    <country>CA</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CTV.CA">
    <display-name>CTV</display-name>
    <country>CA</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.AU">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>AU</country>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260511050000 -0400" stop="20260511060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511060000 -0400" stop="20260511100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511060000 -0400" stop="20260511070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511070000 -0400" stop="20260511100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511070000 -0400" stop="20260511090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511070000 -0400" stop="20260511090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511070000 -0400" stop="20260511090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511080000 -0400" stop="20260511100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511090000 -0400" stop="20260511100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511090000 -0400" stop="20260511100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511090000 -0400" stop="20260511110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511100000 -0400" stop="20260511120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511100000 -0400" stop="20260511120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511100000 -0400" stop="20260511110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511100000 -0400" stop="20260511120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511110000 -0400" stop="20260511120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511120000 -0400" stop="20260511130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511120000 -0400" stop="20260511140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511123000 -0400" stop="20260511133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511130000 -0400" stop="20260511160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511130000 -0400" stop="20260511140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511130000 -0400" stop="20260511150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511140000 -0400" stop="20260511150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511140000 -0400" stop="20260511160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511140000 -0400" stop="20260511150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511140000 -0400" stop="20260511160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511160000 -0400" stop="20260511180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511160000 -0400" stop="20260511170000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>NFL Live</title>
    <desc>NFL Live is a National Football League studio show, currently airing Monday through Friday at 7:00 p.m ET on ESPN2. Formerly known as NFL 2Night, the program is one of the only NFL-related studio programs to air during the week along with NFL Insiders. As such, NFL Live is not a highlight show, as Sunday and Monday game highlights are handled by the various other NFL studio shows, including NFL Primetime during the season. Unlike shows for other sports, NFL Live even runs throughout the entire off season.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511160000 -0400" stop="20260511170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511170000 -0400" stop="20260511190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511173000 -0400" stop="20260511180000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Pardon the Interruption is a sports television show that airs weekdays on various ESPN TV channels, TSN, ESPN America, XM, and Sirius satellite radio services, and as a downloadable podcast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511180000 -0400" stop="20260511190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511183000 -0400" stop="20260511190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511183000 -0400" stop="20260511190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511183000 -0400" stop="20260511190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511190000 -0400" stop="20260511200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511190000 -0400" stop="20260511200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511203000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Neighborhood</title>
    <desc>The Neighborhood telling about what happens when the friendly guy in the Midwest moves his family to a neighborhood in Los Angeles where not everyone looks like him or appreciates his extreme neighborliness. When Dave Johnson and his family arrive from Michigan, they're unfazed that their new dream home is located in a community quite different from their small town. However, their opinionated next-door neighbor, Calvin Butler, is wary of the newcomers, certain that they'll disrupt the culture on the block. Dave realizes that fitting into their new community is more complex than he expected, but if he can find a way to connect with Calvin, they have an excellent chance of making their new neighborhood their home.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Below Deck Down Under</title>
    <desc>Below Deck Down Under follows yachties as they work and play on a super-yacht sailing around Australia. The series also showcases a unique additional challenge for the crew as the guests expect not only an adventure on the water but also underwater with scuba diving and other activities as some of the main attractions of the region.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511220000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>American Idol</title>
    <desc>American Idol is an American singing competition show, where contestants perform in front of a panel of star judges, representing the music industry. The winner is determined by viewers' vote.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511210000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Contraband: Seized at the Airport</title>
    <desc>Follows Dept of Homeland Security officers at five different airports across the country, from San Francisco, Detroit, Newark, Atlanta, and Honolulu, as they search for contraband both leaving and coming into the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Antiques Roadshow</title>
    <desc>Antiques Roadshow turns 20! PBS' most-watched ongoing series celebrates 20 seasons with a new look, new hidden treasures and more appraisals than ever. Tune in to discover finds from Spokane, Washington; Tucson, Arizona; Little Rock, Arkansas; Charleston, South Carolina; Cleveland, Ohio; and Omaha, Nebraska. - Mondays, beginning January 4, 8:00-9:00 p.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511203000 -0400" stop="20260511210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>DMV</title>
    <desc>DMV is set at the place everyone dreads going most: the DMV. Our quirky and lovable characters are making minimum wage, doing a thankless job where customers are annoyed before they even walk in the door. Good thing they have each other.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511210000 -0400" stop="20260511220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>FBI is a fast-paced drama about the inner workings of the New York Field Office of the Federal Bureau of Investigation. These first-class agents, including Special Agent Maggie Bell and her partner, Special Agent Omar Adom 'OA' Zidan, bring all their talents, intellect and technical expertise on major cases in order to keep New York and the country safe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511210000 -0400" stop="20260511220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>History's Greatest Mysteries</title>
    <desc>History's Greatest Mysteries will investigate a wide range of historically compelling topics and the mysteries surrounding each including the Titanic, D.B. Cooper, Roswell, John Wilkes Booth, and more. Each program within the franchise will showcase fresh, new evidence and perspectives including never-before-released documents to the general public, personal diaries and DNA evidence to unearth brand-new information about these infamous and enigmatic chapters in history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511210000 -0400" stop="20260511220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Rachel Maddow Show</title>
    <desc>With honesty and rigor, Rachel Maddow uniquely connects dots to advance stories on her show The Rachel Maddow Show. By exposing the layers of complex issues, she reveals their significance to viewers. In her irreverent style, Maddow transcends the narrative and provides unique perspective.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511210000 -0400" stop="20260511220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511210000 -0400" stop="20260511213000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511213000 -0400" stop="20260511224500 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Top Chef</title>
    <desc>Top Chef is a competition show in which chefs competing against each other in various culinary challenges, judged by the team of professional chefs and notable people from food industry.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511220000 -0400" stop="20260511230000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CIA</title>
    <desc>CIA centers on two unlikely partners — a fast-talking, rule-breaking loose cannon CIA case officer, and a by-the-book, seasoned and smart FBI agent who believes in the rule of law. When this odd couple are assigned to work out of CIA's New York Station, they must learn to work together to investigate cases and criminals posing threats on U.S. soil, finding that their differences may actually be their strength.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511220000 -0400" stop="20260511233000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Independent Lens</title>
    <desc>Independent Lens is an anthology of independent documentary films.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511220000 -0400" stop="20260511230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511220000 -0400" stop="20260511230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511220300 -0400" stop="20260511230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>History's Greatest Warriors</title>
    <desc>History's Greatest Warriors explores the step-by-step process to produce some of history's most infamous and lethal warriors. Each episode introduces viewers to a legendary fighter - from Samurai, Spartans, Delta Force, Navy SEALS, Vikings, and more - and breaks down the selection, training, weaponry, and combat expertise specifically used.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511230000 -0400" stop="20260512000000 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511230000 -0400" stop="20260512000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511230000 -0400" stop="20260512000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511230000 -0400" stop="20260512000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511233500 -0400" stop="20260512003500 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Late Show with Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert brings his signature satire and comedy to The Late Show with Stephen Colbert, the #1 show in late-night. Featuring bandleader Jon Batiste with his band Stay Human, the Emmy Award-nominated show broadcasts from the historic Ed Sullivan Theater. He talks with an eclectic mix of guests about what is new and relevant in the worlds of politics, entertainment, business, music, technology, and more. Stephen Colbert took over as host, executive producer, and writer of The Late Show on Sept. 8, 2015. Colbert is best known for his work as a television host, writer, actor, and producer, and lest known for his charity work teaching English as a second language on Tunisian date farms. Before joining the CBS family -- and being officially adopted by network president Les Moonves -- Colbert helmed The Colbert Report, which aired nearly 1,500 episodes and required Stephen to wear nearly 1,500 different neckties. The program received two Peabody Awards, two Grammy Awards, and several unwelcome shoulder massages. It won two Emmys for Outstanding Variety Series in 2013 and 2014, both of which appear to have been lost in the move. Colbert is pronounced koʊlˈbɛər, according to Wikipedia. His understudy is William Cavanaugh, who will be hosting The Late Show approximately one-third of the time. Good luck, Bill!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511000000 -0400" stop="20260511020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511000000 -0400" stop="20260511020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512050000 -0400" stop="20260512060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512060000 -0400" stop="20260512100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512060000 -0400" stop="20260512070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512070000 -0400" stop="20260512100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512070000 -0400" stop="20260512090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512070000 -0400" stop="20260512090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512070000 -0400" stop="20260512090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512080000 -0400" stop="20260512100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512090000 -0400" stop="20260512100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512090000 -0400" stop="20260512100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512090000 -0400" stop="20260512110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512100000 -0400" stop="20260512120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512100000 -0400" stop="20260512120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512100000 -0400" stop="20260512110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512100000 -0400" stop="20260512120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512110000 -0400" stop="20260512120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512120000 -0400" stop="20260512130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512120000 -0400" stop="20260512140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512123000 -0400" stop="20260512133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512130000 -0400" stop="20260512160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512130000 -0400" stop="20260512140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512130000 -0400" stop="20260512150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512140000 -0400" stop="20260512150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512140000 -0400" stop="20260512160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512140000 -0400" stop="20260512150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512140000 -0400" stop="20260512160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512160000 -0400" stop="20260512180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512160000 -0400" stop="20260512170000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>NFL Live</title>
    <desc>NFL Live is a National Football League studio show, currently airing Monday through Friday at 7:00 p.m ET on ESPN2. Formerly known as NFL 2Night, the program is one of the only NFL-related studio programs to air during the week along with NFL Insiders. As such, NFL Live is not a highlight show, as Sunday and Monday game highlights are handled by the various other NFL studio shows, including NFL Primetime during the season. Unlike shows for other sports, NFL Live even runs throughout the entire off season.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512160000 -0400" stop="20260512170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512170000 -0400" stop="20260512190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512173000 -0400" stop="20260512180000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Pardon the Interruption is a sports television show that airs weekdays on various ESPN TV channels, TSN, ESPN America, XM, and Sirius satellite radio services, and as a downloadable podcast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512180000 -0400" stop="20260512190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512183000 -0400" stop="20260512190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512183000 -0400" stop="20260512190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512183000 -0400" stop="20260512190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512190000 -0400" stop="20260512200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512190000 -0400" stop="20260512200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Celebrity Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>Celebrity Jeopardy! welcomes celebrity contestants to compete against each other by answering trivia questions in the form of a question for a chance to win money for a charity of their choice.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>NCIS (Naval Criminal Investigative Service) is more than just an action drama. With liberal doses of humor, it's a show that focuses on the sometimes complex and always amusing dynamics of a team forced to work together in high-stress situations. Leroy Jethro Gibbs, a former Marine gunnery sergeant, whose skills as an investigator are unmatched, leads this troupe of colorful personalities. Rounding out the team are Anthony DiNozzo, an ex-homicide detective whose instincts in the field are unparalleled and whose quick wit and humorous take on life make him a team favorite; the youthful and energetic forensic specialist Abby Sciuto, a talented scientist whose sharp mind matches her Goth style and eclectic tastes; Caitlin Todd, an ex-Secret Service Agent; and Timothy McGee, an MIT graduate whose brilliance with computers far overshadows his insecurities in the field; Assisting the team is medical examiner Dr. Donald "Ducky" Mallard, who knows it all because he's seen it all, and he's not afraid to let you know. From murder and espionage to terrorism and stolen submarines, these special agents travel the globe to investigate all crimes with Navy or Marine Corps ties.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>WWE NXT</title>
    <desc>Each Wednesday at 8:00 p.m. ET, WWE Superstars and Divas of tomorrow face off on WWE NXT, a one-hour weekly show that features the brightest and best of WWE's rising stars. WWE NXT showcases the Superstars and Divas from WWE's Performance Center as well as appearances from WWE Superstars and Legends in an intimate setting. WWE NXT broadcasts from the state-of-the-art Full Sail LIVE venue on the Full Sail University in campus in Orlando, Florida.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Summer House</title>
    <desc>When a group of beautiful and successful New Yorkers leaves the comforts of the Big Apple behind to party the summer away in their home away from home, nothing is off limits. Bravo's new series Summer House takes the beach town of Montauk, New York by storm, while following a group of nine friends who make the exclusive enclave their go-to party spot between Memorial Day and Labor Day — that is, when they're not hustling at their day jobs. You could say they work hard and party way harder.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512220100 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Homestead Rescue</title>
    <desc>In the last decade, two million Americans have attempted to leave behind civilization in favor of life off-the-grid – but most have failed. For the hundreds of families who decide to become homesteaders, the learning curve is a steep one. Now comes Homestead Rescue. Struggling homesteaders across the country are turning expert homesteader Marty Raney--along with his daughter Misty Raney, a farmer, and son Matt Raney, a hunter and fisherman--to teach them the necessary skills to survive the wilderness. The stakes are high, but the Raney family is determined to prepare these families for nature's worst and set them up for success. Each family faces the ultimate decision: will they tough out their first year or pack up and return to civilization?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Farmer Wants a Wife</title>
    <desc>Four farmers from across the country embark on an adventure of a lifetime in the hopes of finding their future spouse. Women will leave behind the dating apps and pursuit of love in "the big city" in favor of classic American courtship. The farmers will take their group of daters to their farm and show them what it is really like to live as ranchers do.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>U.S. Againt the World: Four Years with the Men's National Soccer Team</title>
    <desc>U.S. Againt the World: Four Years with the Men's National Soccer Team exclusively chronicles the United States Men's National Soccer Team (USMNT) in the leadup to the 2026 FIFA World Cup in North America this June. Filmed over the course of four years, the series follows Christian Pulisic, Tyler Adams, Tim Weah, Weston McKennie, and an array of U.S. players on their personal and collective journeys toward their sport's signature global event.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>With a record number of Americans trading city life for homes in the suburbs, relationships between neighbors are being put to the test. Neighborhood Wars takes viewers into the homes and backyards of neighbors across the country with some of the most unexpected and emotionally charged events caught on camera. Featuring footage from cell phones, drones, home security cameras and more, the series showcases the kindness and conflict between real-life neighbors throughout the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Bear Grylls Is Running Wild</title>
    <desc>Bear Grylls Is Running Wild follows legendary adventurer Bear Grylls as he takes some of the most famous people on the planet into the wild for a 48-hour journey of a lifetime. With thrilling action and revealing conversations, Bear takes his guests on unforgettable adventures in breath-taking wilderness and reveals a side of some of your favorite people like you've never seen before. This season, Bear Grylls leads cast members on a globe-spanning adventure through some of the planet's most unforgiving landscapes — from Norway's glacial wilderness to the legendary mountains of Eryri in Wales. The journeys cut through Arctic rainforest, vast canyonlands, and brutal desert terrain, pushing participants to their limits with glacier crossings, canyon descents, high-risk extractions, and an adrenaline-charged freefall from 11,000 feet, into an adventure along the Irish Sea.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512213000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512213000 -0400" stop="20260512220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>With a record number of Americans trading city life for homes in the suburbs, relationships between neighbors are being put to the test. Neighborhood Wars takes viewers into the homes and backyards of neighbors across the country with some of the most unexpected and emotionally charged events caught on camera. Featuring footage from cell phones, drones, home security cameras and more, the series showcases the kindness and conflict between real-life neighbors throughout the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512220000 -0400" stop="20260512230000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Frontline</title>
    <desc>Since it began in 1983, Frontline has been airing public-affairs documentaries that explore a wide scope of the complex human experience. Frontline's goal is to extend the impact of the documentary beyond its initial broadcast by serving as a catalyst for change..</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512220000 -0400" stop="20260512230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512220000 -0400" stop="20260512230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512220100 -0400" stop="20260512223200 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Squatters</title>
    <desc>Squatters are taking over homes across the country and Flash Shelton is the man who gets them out. With bold tactics and street smarts, Flash and his team face tense and sometimes dangerous situations to help families reclaim their property. Each episode reveals the emotional and high-stakes battles where the fight for justice can quickly escalate, putting everyone involved at risk. This is the struggle to take back what rightfully belongs to them.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512220300 -0400" stop="20260512230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Secrets Declassified with David Duchovny</title>
    <desc>Secrets Declassified tells the incredible stories of government secrets that have only recently come to light. This series proves that secrets can be uncovered, and mysteries can still be unraveled." Each episode will find Duchovny focusing on a different topic, speaking with different experts. Subjects include the real-life story behind Argo and the mystery of the Area 51 conspiracy. Mulder would approve.From black ops and bizarre experiments to deadly cover-ups and nefarious gadgets, David Duchovny pulls the curtain back on all the government secrets in modern history we always suspected, but were never given the answers to. Through the strange and shocking things countries the world over ? and those who work for them ? have done in the name of national interest, we?ll investigate the explosive evidence from newly declassified files that will finally shine a new light on what?s really going on deep in the shadows.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512223200 -0400" stop="20260512230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Squatters</title>
    <desc>Squatters are taking over homes across the country and Flash Shelton is the man who gets them out. With bold tactics and street smarts, Flash and his team face tense and sometimes dangerous situations to help families reclaim their property. Each episode reveals the emotional and high-stakes battles where the fight for justice can quickly escalate, putting everyone involved at risk. This is the struggle to take back what rightfully belongs to them.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512230000 -0400" stop="20260512233500 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512230000 -0400" stop="20260513000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512230000 -0400" stop="20260513000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512230000 -0400" stop="20260513000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512233500 -0400" stop="20260513003500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Emmy Award and Grammy Award winner Jimmy Fallon brought NBC's "The Tonight Show" back to its New York origins when he launched The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from Rockefeller Center. Fallon puts his own stamp on the storied NBC late-night franchise with his unique comedic wit, on-point pop culture awareness, welcoming style and impeccable taste in music with the award-winning house band, The Roots.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512233500 -0400" stop="20260513003500 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Late Show with Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert brings his signature satire and comedy to The Late Show with Stephen Colbert, the #1 show in late-night. Featuring bandleader Jon Batiste with his band Stay Human, the Emmy Award-nominated show broadcasts from the historic Ed Sullivan Theater. He talks with an eclectic mix of guests about what is new and relevant in the worlds of politics, entertainment, business, music, technology, and more. Stephen Colbert took over as host, executive producer, and writer of The Late Show on Sept. 8, 2015. Colbert is best known for his work as a television host, writer, actor, and producer, and lest known for his charity work teaching English as a second language on Tunisian date farms. Before joining the CBS family -- and being officially adopted by network president Les Moonves -- Colbert helmed The Colbert Report, which aired nearly 1,500 episodes and required Stephen to wear nearly 1,500 different neckties. The program received two Peabody Awards, two Grammy Awards, and several unwelcome shoulder massages. It won two Emmys for Outstanding Variety Series in 2013 and 2014, both of which appear to have been lost in the move. Colbert is pronounced koʊlˈbɛər, according to Wikipedia. His understudy is William Cavanaugh, who will be hosting The Late Show approximately one-third of the time. Good luck, Bill!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512000000 -0400" stop="20260512020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512000000 -0400" stop="20260512020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512003500 -0400" stop="20260512013500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Late Night with Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Seth Meyers, who is Saturday Night Live's longest serving anchor on the show's wildly popular "Weekend Update," takes over as host of NBC's Late Night — home to A-list celebrity guests, memorable comedy and the best in musical talent.As the Emmy Award-winning head writer for "SNL," Meyers has established a reputation for sharp wit and perfectly timed comedy, and has gained fame for his spot-on jokes and satire. Meyers takes his departure from "SNL" to his new post at "Late Night," as Jimmy Fallon moves to The Tonight Show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513050000 -0400" stop="20260513060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513060000 -0400" stop="20260513100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513060000 -0400" stop="20260513070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513070000 -0400" stop="20260513100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513070000 -0400" stop="20260513090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513070000 -0400" stop="20260513090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513070000 -0400" stop="20260513090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513080000 -0400" stop="20260513100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513090000 -0400" stop="20260513100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513090000 -0400" stop="20260513100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513090000 -0400" stop="20260513110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513100000 -0400" stop="20260513120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513100000 -0400" stop="20260513120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513100000 -0400" stop="20260513110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513100000 -0400" stop="20260513120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513110000 -0400" stop="20260513120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513120000 -0400" stop="20260513130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513120000 -0400" stop="20260513140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513123000 -0400" stop="20260513133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513130000 -0400" stop="20260513160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513130000 -0400" stop="20260513140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513130000 -0400" stop="20260513150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513140000 -0400" stop="20260513150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513140000 -0400" stop="20260513160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513140000 -0400" stop="20260513150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513140000 -0400" stop="20260513160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513160000 -0400" stop="20260513180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513160000 -0400" stop="20260513170000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>NFL Live</title>
    <desc>NFL Live is a National Football League studio show, currently airing Monday through Friday at 7:00 p.m ET on ESPN2. Formerly known as NFL 2Night, the program is one of the only NFL-related studio programs to air during the week along with NFL Insiders. As such, NFL Live is not a highlight show, as Sunday and Monday game highlights are handled by the various other NFL studio shows, including NFL Primetime during the season. Unlike shows for other sports, NFL Live even runs throughout the entire off season.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513160000 -0400" stop="20260513170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513170000 -0400" stop="20260513190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513173000 -0400" stop="20260513180000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>Pardon the Interruption</title>
    <desc>Pardon the Interruption is a sports television show that airs weekdays on various ESPN TV channels, TSN, ESPN America, XM, and Sirius satellite radio services, and as a downloadable podcast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513180000 -0400" stop="20260513190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513183000 -0400" stop="20260513190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513183000 -0400" stop="20260513190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513183000 -0400" stop="20260513190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513190000 -0400" stop="20260513200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513190000 -0400" stop="20260513200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513213000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Survivor</title>
    <desc>Eighteen to twenty castaways will compete against each other on Survivor. All castaways will compete to outwit, outplay, outlast and ultimately be crowned Sole Survivor.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Celebrity Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>Celebrity Jeopardy! welcomes celebrity contestants to compete against each other by answering trivia questions in the form of a question for a chance to win money for a charity of their choice.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>An emotional thrill ride through the day-to-day chaos of the city's newest state-of-the-art trauma center and into the lives of the courageous doctors, nurses and staff who hold it all together. This is one of those days.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Valley</title>
    <desc>The Valley follows a group of close friends as they trade bottle service in West Hollywood for baby bottles in the Valley all while they navigate bustling businesses, rocky relationships and feisty friendships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>MasterChef</title>
    <desc>Three celebrated food experts put the latest group of contestants through a series of challenging elimination rounds and turn one home cook into a culinary master.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>Police 24/7</title>
    <desc>Fearless men and women in law enforcement agencies across eight U.S. cities demonstrate what it takes to keep the streets safe from crime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>No job is more stressful, dangerous or exhilarating than those of the Firefighters, Rescue Squad and Paramedics of Chicago Firehouse 51. These are the courageous men and women who forge headfirst into danger when everyone else is running the other way and whose actions make the difference between life and death. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>K9 PD with Jim Belushi</title>
    <desc>K9 PD with Jim Belushi showcases intense moments caught on camera of officers and their K9 partners facing high-stakes calls, told through gripping footage from surveillance cameras, body and dash cams, drones and more. Actor and lifelong K9 advocate Jim Belushi returns to the world of heroic K9s—only this time, it's for real—serving as host of the series, which captures the courage, precision, and raw instinct behind one of law enforcement's most formidable partnerships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>The Floor</title>
    <desc>The Floor is a physical quiz show that sees 81 contestants face off in quiz duels on a giant LED floor divided into a 9×9 grid of squares, each representing its own field of knowledge.The first challenger, selected at random, must choose one of his or her neighboring opponents to go head-to-head in an epic quiz duel in the opponent's category. The winner takes over the loser's square, gaining valuable ground as they expand their territory, while the loser exits the game. The winner must then choose – do they continue on and attempt to secure another square? Or do they let The Floor choose a new challenger? The last contestant standing who gains full control over The Floor takes home a life-changing $250,000 cash prize.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Expedition Files</title>
    <desc>In the all-new series Expedition Files, adventurer Josh Gates travels through history on a search to uncover new evidence and answers to the world's most captivating and unexplained mysteries.  Each episode of Expedition Files explores compelling true stories that defy explanation, offering stunning revelations and surprising new insights.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Southern Hospitality</title>
    <desc>The series follows "Southern Charm" resident boss-lady Leva Bonaparte as she manages Charleston's very own "it" crowd, otherwise known as her larger-than-life staff at Republic Garden &amp;amp; Lounge. Leva and husband Lamar own four restaurants along the city's famous King Street, but Republic is the crown jewel of their kingdom. The hottest nightclub and backdrop for Charleston's lively party scene, Republic is the place to go for pleasure, business or both.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513213000 -0400" stop="20260513230000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>America's Culinary Cup</title>
    <desc>America's Culinary Cup will feature a cast of the nation's most decorated chefs as they compete in the kitchen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513213000 -0400" stop="20260513220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>K9 PD with Jim Belushi</title>
    <desc>K9 PD with Jim Belushi showcases intense moments caught on camera of officers and their K9 partners facing high-stakes calls, told through gripping footage from surveillance cameras, body and dash cams, drones and more. Actor and lifelong K9 advocate Jim Belushi returns to the world of heroic K9s—only this time, it's for real—serving as host of the series, which captures the courage, precision, and raw instinct behind one of law enforcement's most formidable partnerships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513220000 -0400" stop="20260513230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>District 21 of the Chicago Police Department is made up of two distinctly different groups. There are the uniformed cops who patrol the beat and go head to head with the city's street crimes. And there's the Intelligence Unit, the team that combats the city's major offenses - organized crime, drug trafficking, high profile murders and beyond. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513220000 -0400" stop="20260513230000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Southern Law</title>
    <desc>Southern Law follows law enforcement officers across the South as they respond to calls, protect their communities, and face the realities of policing in one of the country's most dynamic regions.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513220000 -0400" stop="20260513230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513220000 -0400" stop="20260513230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513220100 -0400" stop="20260513230100 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Conspiracies &amp; Coverups</title>
    <desc>Driven by a relentless hunt for the truth, Bustamante pulls back the curtain on modern-day mysteries that blur the line between fact and fiction. Using his unique perspective and insider techniques, he investigates, pressure-tests, and challenges prevailing narratives to reveal the hidden forces behind these events and the motives used to manipulate the truth.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513221500 -0400" stop="20260513224500 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513230000 -0400" stop="20260513233500 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513230000 -0400" stop="20260514000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513230000 -0400" stop="20260514000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513230000 -0400" stop="20260514000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513233000 -0400" stop="20260514003000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>Inside the NBA</title>
    <desc>Inside the NBA is the postgame show for NBA on TNT broadcasts. The program features host Ernie Johnson with analysts Charles Barkley, Kenny Smith and Shaquille O'Neal. Occasionally, Johnson, Smith, Barkley, and O'Neal are joined by analysts Chris Webber and Grant Hill. The show has won nine Emmy Awards, Ernie has won three as a studio host and Charles Barkley has won two as a studio analyst.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513233500 -0400" stop="20260514003500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Emmy Award and Grammy Award winner Jimmy Fallon brought NBC's "The Tonight Show" back to its New York origins when he launched The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from Rockefeller Center. Fallon puts his own stamp on the storied NBC late-night franchise with his unique comedic wit, on-point pop culture awareness, welcoming style and impeccable taste in music with the award-winning house band, The Roots.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513233500 -0400" stop="20260514003500 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Late Show with Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert brings his signature satire and comedy to The Late Show with Stephen Colbert, the #1 show in late-night. Featuring bandleader Jon Batiste with his band Stay Human, the Emmy Award-nominated show broadcasts from the historic Ed Sullivan Theater. He talks with an eclectic mix of guests about what is new and relevant in the worlds of politics, entertainment, business, music, technology, and more. Stephen Colbert took over as host, executive producer, and writer of The Late Show on Sept. 8, 2015. Colbert is best known for his work as a television host, writer, actor, and producer, and lest known for his charity work teaching English as a second language on Tunisian date farms. Before joining the CBS family -- and being officially adopted by network president Les Moonves -- Colbert helmed The Colbert Report, which aired nearly 1,500 episodes and required Stephen to wear nearly 1,500 different neckties. The program received two Peabody Awards, two Grammy Awards, and several unwelcome shoulder massages. It won two Emmys for Outstanding Variety Series in 2013 and 2014, both of which appear to have been lost in the move. Colbert is pronounced koʊlˈbɛər, according to Wikipedia. His understudy is William Cavanaugh, who will be hosting The Late Show approximately one-third of the time. Good luck, Bill!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513000000 -0400" stop="20260513020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513000000 -0400" stop="20260513020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514050000 -0400" stop="20260514060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514060000 -0400" stop="20260514100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514060000 -0400" stop="20260514070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514070000 -0400" stop="20260514100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514070000 -0400" stop="20260514090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514070000 -0400" stop="20260514090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514070000 -0400" stop="20260514090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514080000 -0400" stop="20260514100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514090000 -0400" stop="20260514100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514090000 -0400" stop="20260514100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514090000 -0400" stop="20260514110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514100000 -0400" stop="20260514120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514100000 -0400" stop="20260514120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514100000 -0400" stop="20260514110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514100000 -0400" stop="20260514120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514110000 -0400" stop="20260514120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514120000 -0400" stop="20260514130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514120000 -0400" stop="20260514140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514123000 -0400" stop="20260514133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514130000 -0400" stop="20260514160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514130000 -0400" stop="20260514140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514130000 -0400" stop="20260514150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514140000 -0400" stop="20260514150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514140000 -0400" stop="20260514160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514140000 -0400" stop="20260514150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514140000 -0400" stop="20260514160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514160000 -0400" stop="20260514180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514160000 -0400" stop="20260514170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514170000 -0400" stop="20260514190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514180000 -0400" stop="20260514190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514183000 -0400" stop="20260514190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514183000 -0400" stop="20260514190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514183000 -0400" stop="20260514190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514190000 -0400" stop="20260514200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514190000 -0400" stop="20260514200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514190000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>Ring of Honor Wrestling</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting pro-wrestling action from the stars of ROH.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514203000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>This Old House</title>
    <desc>The mission of This Old House is to demystify the home improvement process and to celebrate the fusion of old world craftsmanship and modern technology. Each season features two renovation projects. Project One traditionally consists of eighteen or so episodes and is filmed in Massachusetts. Project Two is generally taped in a different region of the country to highlight the variety of American architectural styles and renovation issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210200 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>Chef Gordon Ramsay scours the country for the very best line cooks, home chefs, social media stars, food truck owners and everything in between, all competing against one another with the goal of finding the food world's newest superstar. Joined by two elite names in the food world, chefs Nyesha Arrington and Richard Blais, Ramsay and his co-mentors leave no stone unturned, as they each recruit a group of talented chefs and take them under their wings. Ramsay and his friends attempt to bring out the very best in their cooks, as they all try to find "the one." Ramsay firmly believes that as long as a chef has the drive, talent and perseverance, he or she can make that climb to the top. Creativity, consistency and cunning are the recipe for success to make it to the next level, as the competitors adapt to the challenges waiting for them. Chefs compete for a life-changing $250,000 grand prize and the title of "Next Level Chef."</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Celebrity Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>Celebrity Jeopardy! welcomes celebrity contestants to compete against each other by answering trivia questions in the form of a question for a chance to win money for a charity of their choice.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514203000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Georgie &amp; Mandy's First Marriage</title>
    <desc>Georgie &amp;amp; Mandy's First Marriage follows Georgie and Mandy as they raise their young family in Texas while navigating the challenges of adulthood, parenting and marriage.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>In the criminal justice system, the people are represented by two separate, yet equally important, groups: the police, who investigate crime; and the district attorneys, who prosecute the offenders. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>Scrabble</title>
    <desc>Scrabble is a captivating, fast-paced take on the global board-game phenomenon. In each episode, wordsmiths battle it out playing a series of addictive, word-based games to win points and add words to a giant SCRABBLE board in the center of the set.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>After the First 48</title>
    <desc>After the First 48 revisits some of the most powerful cases originally featured on the First 48 and features exclusive interviews with detectives, prosecutors, defense attorneys, and families of victims. After the First 48 takes viewers through the dramatic and emotional inside story; from the investigation, to the murder trial itself, the verdict and beyond.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514203000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Ask This Old House</title>
    <desc>The crew at This Old House take on some pretty big projects, which means they can only work on one or two houses a year. But homeowners have a virtual truckload of questions on smaller projects, and the TOH crew is ready to answer. Ask This Old House solves the steady stream of home improvement problems faced by viewers - and the crew even makes house calls!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514203000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Ghosts</title>
    <desc>Samantha and Jay throw caution to the wind when they convert their recently inherited country estate into a bed-and-breakfast. Call it mislaid plans. Not only is the place falling apart, but it's also inhabited by spirits of previous residents -- whom only Samantha can see and hear. Ghosts spins the funny, heartfelt story about a newfound dream that reveals connection and self-discovery aren't just for the living.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Elsbeth</title>
    <desc>Elsbeth follows Elsbeth Tascioni, an astute but unconventional attorney who utilizes her singular point of view to make unique observations and corner brilliant criminals alongside the NYPD. After leaving her successful legal career in Chicago to tackle a new investigative role in New York City, Elsbeth finds herself jockeying with the toast of the NYPD, Captain C.W. Wagner, a charismatic and revered leader. Working alongside Elsbeth is Officer Kaya Blanke, a stoic and ethical officer who quickly develops an appreciation for Elsbeth's insightful and offbeat ways.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>In the criminal justice system, sexually-based offenses are considered especially heinous. In New York City, the dedicated detectives who investigate these vicious felonies are members of an elite squad known as the Special Victims Unit. These are their stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>Trivial Pursuit</title>
    <desc>The all-time classic trivia game Trivial Pursuit is reimagined in a question-packed entertainment format. Gameplay takes place on a giant version of the iconic Trivial Pursuit game board, as contestants battle it out over a range of play-along question categories to win wedges and beat each other to the center. The victor then takes on a dramatic finale against the clock to claim the big money jackpot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="National Geographic.US">
    <title>Mysteries of Ancient Medicine</title>
    <desc>Strange, ingenious, and terrifying healing traditions from the ancient world; combining archaeology, forensics, and stylized reconstructions, it explores topics like toxic remedies, pirate cures, early acupuncture, and Roman battlefield surgeries.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514213000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Interrogation Raw</title>
    <desc>Interrogation Raw tells the stories of dramatic murders and other serious crimes through the prism of the gripping interrogations of the accused.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210200 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Fear Factor: House of Fear</title>
    <desc>Fear Factor: House of Fear is coming back bigger, bolder and more daring. Dropped into an unforgiving, remote location, a group of strangers will live together under one roof, and face mind-blowing stunts, harrowing challenges and a twisted game of social strategy where trust is fleeting - and fear is a weapon.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514220000 -0400" stop="20260514230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514220000 -0400" stop="20260514230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514230000 -0400" stop="20260514233500 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514230000 -0400" stop="20260515000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514230000 -0400" stop="20260515000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514230000 -0400" stop="20260515000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514233500 -0400" stop="20260515003500 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Late Show with Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert brings his signature satire and comedy to The Late Show with Stephen Colbert, the #1 show in late-night. Featuring bandleader Jon Batiste with his band Stay Human, the Emmy Award-nominated show broadcasts from the historic Ed Sullivan Theater. He talks with an eclectic mix of guests about what is new and relevant in the worlds of politics, entertainment, business, music, technology, and more. Stephen Colbert took over as host, executive producer, and writer of The Late Show on Sept. 8, 2015. Colbert is best known for his work as a television host, writer, actor, and producer, and lest known for his charity work teaching English as a second language on Tunisian date farms. Before joining the CBS family -- and being officially adopted by network president Les Moonves -- Colbert helmed The Colbert Report, which aired nearly 1,500 episodes and required Stephen to wear nearly 1,500 different neckties. The program received two Peabody Awards, two Grammy Awards, and several unwelcome shoulder massages. It won two Emmys for Outstanding Variety Series in 2013 and 2014, both of which appear to have been lost in the move. Colbert is pronounced koʊlˈbɛər, according to Wikipedia. His understudy is William Cavanaugh, who will be hosting The Late Show approximately one-third of the time. Good luck, Bill!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514000000 -0400" stop="20260514020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514000000 -0400" stop="20260514020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515050000 -0400" stop="20260515060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515060000 -0400" stop="20260515100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515060000 -0400" stop="20260515070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515070000 -0400" stop="20260515100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515070000 -0400" stop="20260515090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515070000 -0400" stop="20260515090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515070000 -0400" stop="20260515090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515080000 -0400" stop="20260515100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515090000 -0400" stop="20260515100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515090000 -0400" stop="20260515100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515090000 -0400" stop="20260515110000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America's Newsroom</title>
    <desc>Watch 'America's Newsroom' on Fox News Channel - follow Bill Hemmer and Dana Perino Weekdays 9 a.m. - 11 a.m. ET as they bring you the news that matters to you.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515100000 -0400" stop="20260515120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515100000 -0400" stop="20260515120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515100000 -0400" stop="20260515110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515100000 -0400" stop="20260515120000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Ana Cabrera Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515110000 -0400" stop="20260515120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515120000 -0400" stop="20260515130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515120000 -0400" stop="20260515140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Chris Jansing Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and coverage of the day's important stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515123000 -0400" stop="20260515133000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>The Young and the Restless revolves around the rivalries, romances, hopes and fears of the residents of the fictional Midwestern metropolis, Genoa City. The lives and loves of a wide variety of characters mingle through the generations, dominated by the Newman, Abbott, Chancellor, Baldwin and Winters families. ­ When The Young and the Restless premiered in 1973, it revolutionized the daytime drama. It continues to set the standard with strong characters, socially conscious storylines, romance and sensuality.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515130000 -0400" stop="20260515160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515130000 -0400" stop="20260515140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515130000 -0400" stop="20260515150000 -0400" channel="Fox News Channel.US">
    <title>America Reports</title>
    <desc>A look at the latest news and headlines with Sandra Smith and John Roberts</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515140000 -0400" stop="20260515150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515140000 -0400" stop="20260515160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Katy Tur Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515140000 -0400" stop="20260515150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515140000 -0400" stop="20260515160000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>American Agenda</title>
    <desc>American Agenda with hosts Bob Brooks &amp;amp; Katrina Szish is a live, fast-paced look at national news and international events. The program brings viewers the latest from Washington, with insightful analysis from lawmakers and experts, and media reports from New York and around the globe.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515160000 -0400" stop="20260515180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515160000 -0400" stop="20260515170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515170000 -0400" stop="20260515190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515180000 -0400" stop="20260515190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515183000 -0400" stop="20260515190000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>NBC Nightly News</title>
    <desc>NBC Nightly News is the most-watched evening newscast in America, providing the very latest on the day's top stories and going beyond the headlines to add context and analysis to the most pressing issues of our time, both at home and abroad. We go to the heart of breaking news stories, introduce you to everyday people caught up in extraordinary events, offer in-depth reporting on health and medicine, cover international news as it unfolds and we profile those who inspire us to do better in our popular Making A Difference reports. The award-winning broadcast carries a legacy that spans more than six decades, beginning in 1948 - when NBC started broadcasting television's first-ever regularly scheduled network evening newscast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515183000 -0400" stop="20260515190000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Tonight with David Muir</title>
    <desc>With unparalleled resources, World News Tonight with David Muir provides the latest information and analysis of major events from around the country and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515183000 -0400" stop="20260515190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515190000 -0400" stop="20260515200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515190000 -0400" stop="20260515200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="STARZ.US">
    <title>Outlander</title>
    <desc>Outlander follows the story of Claire Randall, a married combat nurse from 1945 who is mysteriously swept back in time to 1743, where she is immediately thrown into an unknown world where her life is threatened. When she is forced to marry Jamie, a chivalrous and romantic young Scottish warrior, a passionate affair is ignited that tears Claire's heart between two vastly different men in two irreconcilable lives.The Outlander series, adapted from Diana Gabaldon's international best-selling books, spans the genres of romance, science fiction, history and adventure into one epic tale.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Sheriff Country</title>
    <desc>Sheriff Country focuses on straight-shooting sheriff Mickey Fox, the stepsister of Cal Fire's division chief Sharon Leone, who investigates criminal activity as she patrols the streets of small-town Edgewater while contending with her ex-con father, Wes, who is an off-the-grid marijuana grower, and a mysterious incident involving her wayward daughter.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515203000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Washington Week with The Atlantic</title>
    <desc>On Washington Week (formerly Washington Week with Gwen Ifill) guest journalists weigh in on issues of the week in this venerable roundtable, the first program ever fed by PBS (previously it had aired on WETA-TV in Washington, D.C., and other East Coast public stations). Though its format is panel discussion, there have been occasional one-on-one interviews, a notable example being host Paul Duke's 1994 White House visit with President Bill Clinton. The series won a DuPont-Columbia University Award in 1974.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Celebrity Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>Celebrity Jeopardy! welcomes celebrity contestants to compete against each other by answering trivia questions in the form of a question for a chance to win money for a charity of their choice.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210100 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Deadliest Catch</title>
    <desc>It's the deadliest job on earth: crab fishing off the Alaskan coast on the icy Bering Sea. These adventurers will battle Arctic weather, brutal waves, and a ticking clock for big money in this modern-day gold rush from which they may never return.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515203000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Firing Line with Margaret Hoover</title>
    <desc>Firing Line with Margaret Hoover maintains the character of the original, providing a platform that is diligent in its commitment to civility and the rigorous exchange of opinion. Interviews and debates will highlight leading lights from the left and right, complemented by archival footage from the original Firing Line to remind viewers of longstanding conservative and liberal arguments, where they've been disproved or reinforced over time.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Fire Country</title>
    <desc>In Fire Country, seeking redemption and a shortened prison sentence, young convict Bode Donovan joins a firefighting program that returns him to his small Northern California hometown, where he and other inmates work alongside elite firefighters to extinguish massive blazes across the region.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The UnBelievable with Dan Aykroyd</title>
    <desc>Did you know that a brown bear became a war hero for the Allies during WWII? Or that a flying lawnmower once killed a spectator at a football game? What about the story of the 19th century doctor who ate vomit to understand how yellow fever is transmitted?If you haven't, then brace yourself for The UnBelievable with Dan Aykroyd.Each hour-long episode will open up our cabinet of curiosities to reveal the strangest-but-true stories in human history, brought to life through dynamic recreation, compelling graphics, and arresting archival. These seemingly tall tales all actually happened, and our cast of experts dives into the historical record to tell you how and why.It's a bizarro barrage of people, places and events that prove just how weird our world can be.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515220000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Great Performances</title>
    <desc>Great Performances is a television series devoted to the performing arts, has been telecast on PBS since 1972. The show is produced by WNET in New York City. It is one of the longest running performing arts anthologies on television, second only to Hallmark Hall of Fame. Great Performances presents concerts, ballet, opera, an occasional documentary, and plays. The series has also won many television awards, including an Emmy Award, a Peabody Award, and an Image Award, with nods from the Directors Guild of America and the Cinema Audio Society.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210100 -0400" stop="20260515220300 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>The Last Woodsmen</title>
    <desc>The Last Woodsmen takes us deep into the secluded wilderness with these courageous and highly skilled loggers as they literally risk their lives. It's a rarely explored, dangerous business which translates to incredibly engrossing television.On a floating barge hundreds of miles from civilization, veteran logger Jared Douglas puts everything on the line to harvest the largest timber in the world. One misstep in this high-risk industry could cost tens of thousands of dollars, or even a life. Joining him at the edge of the world is a tight-knit crew of lumbermen who, with only axes and hand-held power saws, take down massive, highly valuable trees that can be worth up to $70K each.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515220000 -0400" stop="20260515230000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Boston Blue</title>
    <desc>In Boston Blue, NYPD Detective Danny Reagan takes a position with Boston PD. Once in Boston, he is paired with Detective Lena Silver, the eldest daughter of a prominent law enforcement family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515220000 -0400" stop="20260515230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515220000 -0400" stop="20260515230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515230000 -0400" stop="20260516000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>On The 11th Hour with Stephanie Ruhle, Stephanie looks at the major political stories of the day and breaking campaign news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515230000 -0400" stop="20260516000000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Amanpour &amp; Co.</title>
    <desc>Featuring conversations with global leaders and decision makers on the issues affecting the world today, Amanpour and Company adds to the long tradition of public affairs programming that has been a hallmark of public media for decades.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515230000 -0400" stop="20260516000000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Laura Coates Live</title>
    <desc>In Laura Coates Live, Laura goes inside the story with a relentless pursuit of the facts. She is CNN's chief legal analyst, playing a central role in the network's extensive legal programming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515000000 -0400" stop="20260515020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515000000 -0400" stop="20260515020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516070000 -0400" stop="20260516100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516070000 -0400" stop="20260516080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516070000 -0400" stop="20260516090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Saturday Morning</title>
    <desc>Hosts Jeff Glor, Dana Jacobson and Michelle Miller provide original reporting, breaking news, and profiles of leading figures in culture and the arts from the Times Square studio on the Saturday edition of the CBS morning news family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516090000 -0400" stop="20260516100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Smerconish</title>
    <desc>After serving as an MSNBC contributor and guest-host on the network for four years, TV and radio personality Michael Smerconish believed he was ready to head a show of his own. CNN agreed, and thus was born Smerconish, an hour long Saturday morning program that takes after its host's independent views. Using a topical, conversational format, he aims for the TV show to be an extension of his weekday radio broadcast, with free-flowing topics and the ability to discuss issues that strike a chord with the audience. Along the same lines, he thinks it's important to present the content in an engaging manner, free of my-way-or-the-highway ideology. Smerconish, who has a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania, is also a New York Times' best-selling author.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516090000 -0400" stop="20260516093000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Lucky Dog</title>
    <desc>On Lucky Dog, animal trainer Brandon McMillan's second home is the neighborhood animal shelter where he is determined to rescue hard-to-love, out-of control, untrained and unadoptable dogs. Then, back at Brandon's training facility known as the Lucky Dog Ranch, he embarks on the seemingly impossible task of turning the frightened pooches into perfect pets. In the end, a lucky family will adopt an even luckier dog, making each episode an adoption story that warms the heart.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516090000 -0400" stop="20260516110000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>America Right Now</title>
    <desc>Tom Basile tackles the week's biggest stories with top talkers from politics, Hollywood, and across America.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516100000 -0400" stop="20260516130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Velshi</title>
    <desc>MSNBC anchor Ali Velshi brings his sharp analysis and point-of-view to weekend mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516110000 -0400" stop="20260516120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Amanpour Hour</title>
    <desc>Christiane Amanpour, CNN's chief international anchor, brings valuable insight to the biggest global and domestic news stories of the week.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516130000 -0400" stop="20260516160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516143000 -0400" stop="20260516150000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>America's Test Kitchen</title>
    <desc>America's Test Kitchen is filmed in a real, working test kitchen located just outside of Boston. It is the home of Cook's Illustrated magazine and the Monday-to-Friday destination for more than three dozen test cooks, editors, food scientists, tasters, and cookware specialists.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516153000 -0400" stop="20260516160000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Cook's Country from America's Test Kitchen</title>
    <desc>"Cook's Country from America's Test Kitchen" is a half-hour cooking show distributed to public television stations (reruns airing on Create) in the United States, which are also available in most Canadian markets. The show's hosts are Julia Collin Davison &amp;amp; Bridget Lancaster; the show and the magazine are affiliated, and the magazine's test kitchen facility in Brookline, Massachusetts, is used as a set for the show. Cook's Illustrated's parent company, Boston Common Press, while retaining its corporate name, has marketed its publishing and media activities under the America's Test Kitchen brand beginning in 2004.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516160000 -0400" stop="20260516194000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Preakness Stakes</title>
    <desc>The Preakness Stakes is an American thoroughbred horse race held on the third Saturday in May each year at Pimlico Race Course in Baltimore, Maryland. It is a Grade I race run over a distance of 9.5 furlongs (1+3⁄16 miles (1,900 m)) on dirt. Colts and geldings carry 126 pounds (57 kg); fillies 121 pounds (55 kg). It is the second jewel of the Triple Crown, held two weeks after the Kentucky Derby and three weeks before the Belmont Stakes.First run in 1873, the Preakness Stakes was named by a former Maryland governor after the colt who won the first Dinner Party Stakes at Pimlico. The race has been termed "The Run for the Black-Eyed Susans" because a blanket of Maryland's state flower is placed across the withers of the winning colt or filly. Attendance at the Preakness Stakes ranks second in North America among equestrian events, surpassed only by the Kentucky Derby.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516170000 -0400" stop="20260516173000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Cyberchase</title>
    <desc>Cyberchase chronicles the adventures of three extraordinary kids, collectively called the CyberSquad: Matt, the leader Jackie the CyberSquad's resident fashion guru, and Inez,with a lot of questions in her mind (and she hates being called Nezzie). At the beginning of the series, Matt, Jackie and Inez, through a set of extraordinary circumstances, get warped into "Cyberspace" via a library computer in the "Real World." Now all three are involved in a power struggle between the beauteous and wise Motherboard, protectress of all Cyberspace, and the dastardly Hacker, who wishes to become its overlord. With the help of Dr. Marbles and Digit, Motherboard's faithful aides, the kids must save the Internet from Hacker's evil plans using logic and (The most hated subject in the entire history of education) mathematics instead of weapons and dramatics to defeat any obstacles in their way!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516170000 -0400" stop="20260516173000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Cyberchase</title>
    <desc>Cyberchase chronicles the adventures of three extraordinary kids, collectively called the CyberSquad: Matt, the leader Jackie the CyberSquad's resident fashion guru, and Inez,with a lot of questions in her mind (and she hates being called Nezzie). At the beginning of the series, Matt, Jackie and Inez, through a set of extraordinary circumstances, get warped into "Cyberspace" via a library computer in the "Real World." Now all three are involved in a power struggle between the beauteous and wise Motherboard, protectress of all Cyberspace, and the dastardly Hacker, who wishes to become its overlord. With the help of Dr. Marbles and Digit, Motherboard's faithful aides, the kids must save the Internet from Hacker's evil plans using logic and (The most hated subject in the entire history of education) mathematics instead of weapons and dramatics to defeat any obstacles in their way!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516170000 -0400" stop="20260516180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516180000 -0400" stop="20260516210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend Primetime</title>
    <desc>A diverse panel of journalists navigates the week's biggest stories and sets the agenda for the week ahead, offering context, analysis, and civil debate in a three-hour Saturday and Sunday evening format.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516210000 -0400" stop="20260516220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Kara Swisher Wants to Live Forever</title>
    <desc>Produced by EverWonder Studio, Kara Swisher Wants to Live Forever follows journalist Kara Swisher as she embarks on a deeply personal and sharply reported journey into the rapidly expanding world of longevity science and humanity's enduring quest to cheat death."When my father died of an aneurysm at 34 years old, I was only five years old. Since then, I've thought a lot about death and how it impacts us all, for better or worse," said Swisher.  "When I started covering Silicon Valley in the early 1990s, I spent a lot of time reporting on how innovation and tech leaders could help some people while hurting others. As titans who have profoundly impacted our world, they've become interested in applying their vast fortunes and often god-like know-how to longevity, dreaming they might even be able to hack death itself. Can they? Is that a good thing? What is actual breakthrough science and what is the same old snake oil? Will that effort help all of humanity or just themselves? My goal is the same as it always has been: To find out."Inspired by her own experiences confronting mortality, Swisher investigates the promises and pitfalls of the booming longevity industry. Across the series, Swisher examines everything from anti-aging treatments and biotech breakthroughs to the role of artificial intelligence, the influence of Silicon Valley, and the growing cultural obsession with extending life. Along the way, she explores how wealth, access to healthcare, and social connection shape who benefits from these innovations, and whether humanity's pursuit of longer lives is changing how we think about death itself.Throughout the series, Swisher sits down with a range of voices at the center of the longevity conversation, including OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, entrepreneur Bryan Johnson, CRISPR pioneer and Nobel Prize winner Jennifer Doudna, entrepreneur and professor Scott Galloway, and Reed Jobs, whose work is shaped by his family's personal encounter with cancer. The series takes Swisher from exclusive concierge medical clinics to cutting-edge biotech labs and international healthcare systems, including a visit to South Korea to examine how preventative care and innovation have contributed to the country's high life expectancy.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516220000 -0400" stop="20260516230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Kara Swisher Wants to Live Forever</title>
    <desc>Produced by EverWonder Studio, Kara Swisher Wants to Live Forever follows journalist Kara Swisher as she embarks on a deeply personal and sharply reported journey into the rapidly expanding world of longevity science and humanity's enduring quest to cheat death."When my father died of an aneurysm at 34 years old, I was only five years old. Since then, I've thought a lot about death and how it impacts us all, for better or worse," said Swisher.  "When I started covering Silicon Valley in the early 1990s, I spent a lot of time reporting on how innovation and tech leaders could help some people while hurting others. As titans who have profoundly impacted our world, they've become interested in applying their vast fortunes and often god-like know-how to longevity, dreaming they might even be able to hack death itself. Can they? Is that a good thing? What is actual breakthrough science and what is the same old snake oil? Will that effort help all of humanity or just themselves? My goal is the same as it always has been: To find out."Inspired by her own experiences confronting mortality, Swisher investigates the promises and pitfalls of the booming longevity industry. Across the series, Swisher examines everything from anti-aging treatments and biotech breakthroughs to the role of artificial intelligence, the influence of Silicon Valley, and the growing cultural obsession with extending life. Along the way, she explores how wealth, access to healthcare, and social connection shape who benefits from these innovations, and whether humanity's pursuit of longer lives is changing how we think about death itself.Throughout the series, Swisher sits down with a range of voices at the center of the longevity conversation, including OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, entrepreneur Bryan Johnson, CRISPR pioneer and Nobel Prize winner Jennifer Doudna, entrepreneur and professor Scott Galloway, and Reed Jobs, whose work is shaped by his family's personal encounter with cancer. The series takes Swisher from exclusive concierge medical clinics to cutting-edge biotech labs and international healthcare systems, including a visit to South Korea to examine how preventative care and innovation have contributed to the country's high life expectancy.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516220000 -0400" stop="20260516230000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>48 Hours</title>
    <desc>48 Hours is a CBS news magazine that investigates intriguing crime and justice cases that touch on all aspects of the human experience. Over its long run, the show has helped exonerate wrongly convicted people, driven the reopening -- and resolution -- of cold cases, and changed numerous lives. CBS News correspondents offer an in-depth look into each story, with the emphasis on solving the mystery at its heart. The program and its team have earned critical acclaim, including 20 Emmys and three Peabody Awards.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516232900 -0400" stop="20260517010200 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Saturday Night Live</title>
    <desc>Saturday Night Live is an Emmy Award-winning late-night comedy showcase.Since its inception in 1975, "SNL" has launched the careers of many of the brightest comedy performers of their generation. As The New York Times noted on the occasion of the show's Emmy-winning 25th Anniversary special in 1999, "in defiance of both time and show business convention, 'SNL' is still the most pervasive influence on the art of comedy in contemporary culture." At the close of the century, "Saturday Night Live" placed seventh on Entertainment Weekly's list of the Top 100 Entertainers of the past fifty years.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516000000 -0400" stop="20260516010000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>WOW - Women of Wrestling</title>
    <desc>The series will feature 35 wrestlers, including third generation wrestling superstar Tessa Blanchard, returning superheroes The Beast, Stephy Slays, Jungle Grrrl, Beverly Hills Babe and talented newcomers to WOW such as Faith the Lioness and Princess Aussie.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516000000 -0400" stop="20260516010000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>WOW - Women of Wrestling</title>
    <desc>The series will feature 35 wrestlers, including third generation wrestling superstar Tessa Blanchard, returning superheroes The Beast, Stephy Slays, Jungle Grrrl, Beverly Hills Babe and talented newcomers to WOW such as Faith the Lioness and Princess Aussie.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517070000 -0400" stop="20260517100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517070000 -0400" stop="20260517080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517080000 -0400" stop="20260517090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist</title>
    <desc>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist delivers morning news, videos, and photos about current events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517090000 -0400" stop="20260517100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Meet the Press</title>
    <desc>For almost as long as there has been television, there's been Meet the Press. The hourlong Sunday morning public affairs program has featured interviews with countless U.S. and world leaders, and has reviewed, analyzed and discussed the news of the week -- all while looking toward the week ahead.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517090000 -0400" stop="20260517103000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS News Sunday Morning</title>
    <desc>CBS News Sunday Morning is a early morning news and magazine program that airs on Sunday's on CBS.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517090000 -0400" stop="20260517100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>State of the Union with Jake Tapper and Dana Bash</title>
    <desc>Jake Tapper and Dana Bash bring together major newsmakers, analysts and experts to tackle pressing domestic issues and diplomacy on the global stage.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517100000 -0400" stop="20260517110000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Fareed Zakaria GPS</title>
    <desc>Fareed Zakaria GPS is a weekly public affairs show hosted by journalist and author Fareed Zakaria. As of November 2011, the show airs Sundays at 10 am Eastern Time and 1 pm Eastern Time on CNN. The show also airs Sundays at 1200 and 1900 GMT on CNN International. The "GPS" in the show's title stands for "Global Public Square," a reference to the show's focus on international issues and foreign affairs. On August 10, 2012, CNN suspended the program pending their investigation of suspected plagiarism. One week later, the New York Times reported, "Time and CNN said they had completed their reviews, found no evidence of plagiarism, and restored Mr. Zakaria to his demanding schedule." Each installment features Zakaria leading a panel discussion and conducting an extended one-on-one interview.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517100000 -0400" stop="20260517130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Velshi</title>
    <desc>MSNBC anchor Ali Velshi brings his sharp analysis and point-of-view to weekend mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517100000 -0400" stop="20260517110000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>This Week</title>
    <desc>This Week  is hosted by former Clinton White House staffer and current co-anchor of ABC's weekday morning news show "Good Morning America", George Stephanopoulos offers a look at current events with a focus on the politics of the day. Each week's show includes interviews with top newsmakers (including some of the nation's top political leaders) as well as a roundtable discussion, usually featuring journalists from ABC and other news organizations, of the week's happenings. Since 2008, the program has broadcast from a studio at the Newseum in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517103000 -0400" stop="20260517113000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Face the Nation</title>
    <desc>Face the Nation is a news interview program which airs every Sunday morning, live from the CBS studio in Washington D.C. It is dedicated to interviewing newsmakers on the latest issues. Guests include government leaders, politicians, and international figures in the news. CBS News… More correspondents engage the guests in a lively roundtable discussion focusing on current topics. The show started on November 7th, 1954, and was originally broadcast on both CBS Television and Radio Networks. After close to two decades, the program was taken off CBS radio.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517130000 -0400" stop="20260517160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517170000 -0400" stop="20260517180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517180000 -0400" stop="20260517210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend Primetime</title>
    <desc>A diverse panel of journalists navigates the week's biggest stories and sets the agenda for the week ahead, offering context, analysis, and civil debate in a three-hour Saturday and Sunday evening format.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517190000 -0400" stop="20260517200000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>ABC's longest-running primetime entertainment show, America's Funniest Home Videos, returns for season 36 this fall with the same mission -- giving families something genuinely funny to enjoy together on Sunday nights."AFV," the longest-running primetime entertainment show in ABC history, returns for season 36 with the same mission - to provide viewers with hysterical moments that fly by at a dizzying pace.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Marshals</title>
    <desc>Marshals stars Luke Grimes reprising his role as Kayce Dutton. With the Yellowstone Ranch behind him, Dutton joins an elite unit of U.S. Marshals, combining his skills as a cowboy and Navy SEAL to bring range justice to Montana. Kayce and his teammates - Pete Calvin, Belle Skinner, Andrea Cruz and Miles Kittle - must balance the high psychological cost of serving as the last line of defense in the region's war on violence with their duty to their families, which for Kayce includes his son Tate and his confidants Thomas Rainwater and Mo from the Broken Rock reservation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517220200 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Naked and Afraid: Global Showdown</title>
    <desc>Survivalists from all over the world - including Brazil, Australia, Mexico, and the United States - represent their homelands in a grueling 40-day primitive bushcraft competition. Paired with a partner, their skills, toughness and teamwork will be tested as they compete for national pride and the largest cash prize in franchise history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Biography: WWE Legends</title>
    <desc>A&amp;amp;E Network and WWE Studios are giving fans an exclusive look behind the curtain in an all-new Sunday night programming partnership. With unprecedented access to WWE's archive, the ten-week programming block features eight original two-hour documentaries under the award-winning "Biography" banner showcasing the stories behind some of the most memorable WWE Superstars of all time including "Stone Cold" Steve Austin®, "Macho Man" Randy Savage®, "Rowdy" Roddy Piper™, Booker T®, Shawn Michaels®, Bret Hart, Mick Foley and Ultimate Warrior. The new "Biography" specials are helmed by some of the industry's top directors and storytellers to chronicle the success of these WWE Legends and their lasting mark on both sports entertainment and popular culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Atlanta</title>
    <desc>An up-close and personal look at life in Hotlanta, The Real Housewives of Atlanta follows five glamorous southern belles as they balance motherhood, demanding careers and a fast-paced social calendar, and shows what life is like in the most exclusive areas of Atlanta. These driven and ambitious women prove that they're not just "housewives," but entrepreneurs, doting mothers and classy southern women. These ladies show the world what it takes to live large in some of the hottest zip codes in the south.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517203000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Family Guy follows Peter Griffin the endearingly ignorant dad, and his hilariously offbeat family of middle-class New Englanders in Quahog, RI. Lois is Peter's wife, a stay-at-home mom with no patience for her family's antics. Then there are their kids: 18-year-old Meg is an outcast at school and the Griffin family punching bag; 13-year-old Chris is a socially awkward teen who doesn't have a clue about the opposite sex; and one-year-old Stewie is a diabolically clever baby whose burgeoning sexuality is very much a work in progress. Rounding out the Griffin household is Brian the family dog and a ladies' man who is one step away from AA.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517203000 -0400" stop="20260517210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>The series follows Bob who runs Bob's Burgers, with the help of his wife and their three kids. Bob has big ideas about burgers, but the rest of the clan falls short on service. Despite the greasy counters and lousy location, the Belchers are determined to make every "Grand Re-Re-Re-opening" a success. Bob's wife, Linda, stands by her man and often does so by bursting into song. Their eldest daughter, 13-year-old Tina has a slight obsession with boys and zombies. Middle child Gene is an aspiring musician with a thirst for life. Louise is the bunny ears-wearing youngest daughter with an off-kilter sense of humor that makes her somewhat of a liability in the kitchen – and with the public.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517220000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>Euphoria</title>
    <desc>Euphoria follows a group of high school students as they navigate love and friendships in a world of drugs, sex, trauma, and social media.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Disaster: The Chernobyl Meltdown</title>
    <desc>Marking the 40th anniversary of the unprecedented tragedy, Disaster: The Chernobyl Meltdown tells the powerful story of the world's worst nuclear disaster in four gripping episodes. Spanning the scope of the catastrophic collapse of the reactor, the Soviets' calculated cover-up, and the present-day fallout now intersecting with the war in Ukraine, the series reveals a tragedy still reverberating across history. Featuring revealing interviews with survivors speaking publicly for the first time, alongside rare insight into the CIA and Soviet responses, the series exposes a web of secrecy, miscalculation, and human cost. Astonishing new footage from inside the nuclear exclusion zone reveals how this scarred landscape is once again under siege as war encroaches on one of the most dangerous places on Earth.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517220000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Tracker</title>
    <desc>Tracker features lone-wolf survivalist Colter Shaw, who roams the country as a "reward seeker," using his expert tracking skills to help private citizens and law enforcement to solve all manner of mysteries while contending with his own fractured family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Hazardous History with Henry Winkler</title>
    <desc>The eight-episode fast-paced, nostalgia-fueled series will take viewers on a thrilling ride through America's past.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Rhode Island</title>
    <desc>They may live in the smallest state in the country, but their drama? Extra large. Bravo is expanding the distinguished franchise with The Real Housewives of Rhode Island, spotlighting a fresh, charismatic group of women whose lives intertwine across the storied coastline of New England luxury.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517213000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>American Dad!</title>
    <desc>In American Dad!, Stan Smith leads the all-American family in this animated sitcom filled with wild and crazy extremes. Everyday life is taken to the limit as Stan applies the same drastic measures used in his job at the CIA to his home life. Driven by machismo and the American dream, he often is blind to how horribly he fails at his attempts. This father might not know best, but he never stops trying.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517213000 -0400" stop="20260517220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>The series follows Bob who runs Bob's Burgers, with the help of his wife and their three kids. Bob has big ideas about burgers, but the rest of the clan falls short on service. Despite the greasy counters and lousy location, the Belchers are determined to make every "Grand Re-Re-Re-opening" a success. Bob's wife, Linda, stands by her man and often does so by bursting into song. Their eldest daughter, 13-year-old Tina has a slight obsession with boys and zombies. Middle child Gene is an aspiring musician with a thirst for life. Louise is the bunny ears-wearing youngest daughter with an off-kilter sense of humor that makes her somewhat of a liability in the kitchen – and with the public.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517220000 -0400" stop="20260517230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Disaster: The Chernobyl Meltdown</title>
    <desc>Marking the 40th anniversary of the unprecedented tragedy, Disaster: The Chernobyl Meltdown tells the powerful story of the world's worst nuclear disaster in four gripping episodes. Spanning the scope of the catastrophic collapse of the reactor, the Soviets' calculated cover-up, and the present-day fallout now intersecting with the war in Ukraine, the series reveals a tragedy still reverberating across history. Featuring revealing interviews with survivors speaking publicly for the first time, alongside rare insight into the CIA and Soviet responses, the series exposes a web of secrecy, miscalculation, and human cost. Astonishing new footage from inside the nuclear exclusion zone reveals how this scarred landscape is once again under siege as war encroaches on one of the most dangerous places on Earth.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517220000 -0400" stop="20260517230000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Betrayal: Secrets &amp; Lies</title>
    <desc>The series follows lives undone by unthinkable betrayals and the courage it takes to survive scandalous confessions, secret lives, terrifying acts of violence, financial ruin and more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517220100 -0400" stop="20260517230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE LFG</title>
    <desc>WWE LFG (Legends &amp;amp; Future Greats) will offer viewers an inside look at the rigorous training process, featuring iconic WWE Legends such as Paul "Triple H" Levesque and Shawn Michaels and weekly regular coaches Undertaker, Booker T, Mickie James and Bubba Ray Dudley as they mentor a new generation in weekly matches on their quest to become the next WWE Superstars.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517220200 -0400" stop="20260517230400 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>In the Eye of the Storm: Chasers</title>
    <desc>In the Eye of the Storm: Chasers, a heart-pounding ride into nature at its most extreme. The series follows twelve teams of certified weather spotters and professional storm chasers as they self-shoot their close encounters with dangerous tornadoes. With no producers or camera crews, each team ventures into America's Tornado Alley, risking everything to spot tornados, warn people in harm's way, and help save lives when disaster strikes.The series captures raw, harrowing encounters as storm chasers, outfitted with their own camera rigs and advanced weather tech, race into the American Midwest during one of the most active tornado seasons in decades. These men and women risk their lives while redefining storm chasing for a new generation.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517220300 -0400" stop="20260517230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Food That Built America</title>
    <desc>For generations of Americans, food titans like Henry Heinz, Milton Hershey, John and Will Kellogg, C.W. Post and the McDonald brothers have literally been household names, but you don't know their stories. Before they were brand names, they were brilliant, sometimes ruthless, visionaries who revolutionized food and changed the landscape of America forever. This miniseries event will tell the fascinating stories of the people behind the food that built America – those who used brains, muscle, blood, sweat and tears to get to America's heart through its stomach, and along the way built cities, invented new technologies and helped win wars.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517230000 -0400" stop="20260517233000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>Last Week Tonight with John Oliver</title>
    <desc>On Last Week Tonight with John Oliver, John Oliver presents a satirical look at the week in news, politics and current events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517230400 -0400" stop="20260517233400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE's Greatest Moments</title>
    <desc>WWE's Greatest Moments will feature legendary play-by-play announcer Michael Cole hosting half-hour episodes with various WWE Superstars &amp;amp; Legends, including "Stone Cold" Steve Austin, Hulk Hogan, Kevin Owens and others, to share vivid recollections and perspectives on the most remarkable moments in wrestling history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517233400 -0400" stop="20260518000300 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE's Greatest Moments</title>
    <desc>WWE's Greatest Moments will feature legendary play-by-play announcer Michael Cole hosting half-hour episodes with various WWE Superstars &amp;amp; Legends, including "Stone Cold" Steve Austin, Hulk Hogan, Kevin Owens and others, to share vivid recollections and perspectives on the most remarkable moments in wrestling history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511070000 -0400" stop="20260511072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511124500 -0400" stop="20260511125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511141000 -0400" stop="20260511150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511150000 -0400" stop="20260511154500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>A series which helps prospective buyers find their dream home in the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511160000 -0400" stop="20260511170000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Escape to Florida</title>
    <desc>The fun-filled lives of the growing number of British and Irish expats who are turning their backs on grey skies and rising living costs at home and seeking a fresh start in America's Sunshine State.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511163000 -0400" stop="20260511171500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Bridge of Lies</title>
    <desc>Ross Kemp has turned his hand to quiz show hosting for the very first time, and will preside over teams of contestants as they compete for cash by crossing the Bridge – a collection of stepping stones featuring various truths and lies based on general knowledge categories.Each player must try to safely step on the truths and avoid the lies, or risk falling off and out of the game. Once they've conquered the Bridge on their own, successful contestants will join forces to face the dramatic final crossing for a chance to take home some cash.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511170000 -0400" stop="20260511180000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Château DIY</title>
    <desc>Adventurous British families buy and renovate beautiful chateaux in France.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511170000 -0400" stop="20260511180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511180000 -0400" stop="20260511190000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses</title>
    <desc>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses is a series that follows two British families who have set up shop in Spain selling property to Brits seeking fun in the sun.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511185500 -0400" stop="20260511190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511193000 -0400" stop="20260511200000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>How to Clean Up for Cash</title>
    <desc>Josie Gibson presents as families have a loved one's clutter cleared and valued in secret by antiques expert Dan Hatfield and declutterer Jacqueline McLeod.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511195500 -0400" stop="20260511200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511210000 -0400" channel="National Geographic.GB">
    <title>Construction Fails</title>
    <desc>Construction Fails happen every day, but sometimes the damage is catastrophic. This factual, fast-paced show investigates the most spectacular mishaps, what went wrong, and how the disaster could have been averted. Combining live footage with CGI animation, this show examines well-known disasters, such as the Notre Dame fire, and the collapse of the Georgia Dome, but also more minor incidents. Presented in a light-hearted and accessible manner, Construction Fails shows what happens when things go drastically wrong.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Police Interceptors</title>
    <desc>Follow the action-packed lives of the high-speed police interception unit. Led by specially trained officers and equipped with the fastest vehicles in the force, the team tackles the most difficult-to-catch criminals on a daily basis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511210000 -0400" stop="20260511220000 -0400" channel="Quest.GB">
    <title>Shed &amp; Buried: Classic Cars</title>
    <desc>Shed &amp;amp; Buried: Classic Cars sees Henry team-up with Fuzz Townshend once again. The duo will be doing what they do best: digging in the nation's sheds, barns and outbuildings, this time to (hopefully) find a tidy profit in some vintage motors.Henry's love of motorbikes and tractors is well-known, but he still has a soft spot for classic cars. Fuzz - who has an encyclopaedic knowledge of all things automotive - is the perfect partner to help him unearth some classic four-wheelers and turn them into nice little earners.That's only half the battle - once their finds are back in the shed, restorer extraordinaire Guy Willison and engineering genius Allen Millyard will be put to the test, turning the rusty wrecks the lads have unearthed into right royal runners.As always, Henry will need to keep Fuzz focused, to make sure he doesn't buy an obscure vintage bus or lorry. Fuzz will have to keep an eye on Henry too, as he's usually done a deal before Fuzz can even lift the bonnet.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511210000 -0400" stop="20260511223000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Major Crimes Unit</title>
    <desc>Seconds is all it takes for the most brutal of crimes to be committed and lives to be shattered forever. When the worst happens, one team steps forward, and the brave men and women of the West Midland's Major Crime Unit take control - specialist detectives highly trained to piece together the smallest of clues and pick up the faintest of trails. Every lead matters and every second counts.With unprecedented access to this elite crime-fighting unit, the series follows investigators as they race against time to track suspects, uncover the truth, and deliver justice for victims and their families. No stone unturned, no suspect safe - this is law enforcement at its most relentless.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511212500 -0400" stop="20260511223000 -0400" channel="E4.GB">
    <title>Celebs Go Dating</title>
    <desc>Single celebrities join an exclusive dating agency in a bid to find true love. Matchmakers pair them with non-celebrity partners and the cameras capture every romantic and cringe-filled moment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511220000 -0400" stop="20260511230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Donal MacIntyre's UK Killer Evidence</title>
    <desc>Renowned investigative journalist and criminologist Donal MacIntyre returns to host Donal MacIntyre's Killer Evidence to demonstrate through 10 UK and US cases, that forensics will always uncover the ‘killer evidence' which brings murderers to justice.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511223500 -0400" stop="20260511234000 -0400" channel="E4.GB">
    <title>Made in Chelsea</title>
    <desc>A look at the lifestyles of a group of 20-something residents of the exclusive postcode in London, Chelsea, SW3.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512070000 -0400" stop="20260512072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512124500 -0400" stop="20260512125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512141000 -0400" stop="20260512150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512150000 -0400" stop="20260512154500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>A series which helps prospective buyers find their dream home in the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512160000 -0400" stop="20260512170000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Escape to Florida</title>
    <desc>The fun-filled lives of the growing number of British and Irish expats who are turning their backs on grey skies and rising living costs at home and seeking a fresh start in America's Sunshine State.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512163000 -0400" stop="20260512171500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Bridge of Lies</title>
    <desc>Ross Kemp has turned his hand to quiz show hosting for the very first time, and will preside over teams of contestants as they compete for cash by crossing the Bridge – a collection of stepping stones featuring various truths and lies based on general knowledge categories.Each player must try to safely step on the truths and avoid the lies, or risk falling off and out of the game. Once they've conquered the Bridge on their own, successful contestants will join forces to face the dramatic final crossing for a chance to take home some cash.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512170000 -0400" stop="20260512180000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Château DIY</title>
    <desc>Adventurous British families buy and renovate beautiful chateaux in France.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512170000 -0400" stop="20260512180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512180000 -0400" stop="20260512190000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses</title>
    <desc>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses is a series that follows two British families who have set up shop in Spain selling property to Brits seeking fun in the sun.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512185500 -0400" stop="20260512190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512195500 -0400" stop="20260512200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Reuben: Life in the Dales</title>
    <desc>Hill shepherds' son 19-year-old Reuben Owen from Channel 5's Our Yorkshire Farm is back, attempting to grow his new heavy plant machinery business with his best friends Tommy and Sarah in the remote Yorkshire Dales.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Interior Design Masters with Alan Carr</title>
    <desc>Interior Design Masters takes ten fledgling designers and launches them into the world of interior design. With eight weeks and eight different challenges to tackle, in each episode the designers will be confronted with a new space to transform in an attempt to win the grand prize offer of a life changing design contract.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Jamie's Ultimate BBQ</title>
    <desc>Fresh air, good vibes, and woodsmoked wonders! Jamie Oliver shows us how to get outside, get cooking and get those flavours and textures that the kitchen just can't match.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="Quest.GB">
    <title>Francis Bourgeois &amp; Chris Harris: We Saved A Train</title>
    <desc>Trainspotting star Francis Bourgeois teams up with petrolhead Chris Harris to restore a wrecked locomotive, built in 1961.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Critical Condition</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following the work of a major hospital trauma unit.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512210000 -0400" stop="20260512220000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>True Crime Presents</title>
    <desc>A collection of true crime documentaries that cover a range of real-life offences and notorious offenders.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512212000 -0400" stop="20260512222500 -0400" channel="E4.GB">
    <title>Celebs Go Dating</title>
    <desc>Single celebrities join an exclusive dating agency in a bid to find true love. Matchmakers pair them with non-celebrity partners and the cameras capture every romantic and cringe-filled moment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512220000 -0400" stop="20260512230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Killers: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>Killers: Caught on Camera is a brand-new true crime series with unique access to the video footage that leads to the conviction of killers around the world.Each case is pieced together like a jigsaw as we link the CCTV, home surveillance, police body camera, and mobile phone footage that builds the evidence to catch the killer.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513070000 -0400" stop="20260513072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513124500 -0400" stop="20260513125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513141000 -0400" stop="20260513150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513160000 -0400" stop="20260513170000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Escape to Florida</title>
    <desc>The fun-filled lives of the growing number of British and Irish expats who are turning their backs on grey skies and rising living costs at home and seeking a fresh start in America's Sunshine State.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513163000 -0400" stop="20260513171500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Bridge of Lies</title>
    <desc>Ross Kemp has turned his hand to quiz show hosting for the very first time, and will preside over teams of contestants as they compete for cash by crossing the Bridge – a collection of stepping stones featuring various truths and lies based on general knowledge categories.Each player must try to safely step on the truths and avoid the lies, or risk falling off and out of the game. Once they've conquered the Bridge on their own, successful contestants will join forces to face the dramatic final crossing for a chance to take home some cash.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513170000 -0400" stop="20260513180000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Château DIY</title>
    <desc>Adventurous British families buy and renovate beautiful chateaux in France.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513170000 -0400" stop="20260513180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513180000 -0400" stop="20260513190000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses</title>
    <desc>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses is a series that follows two British families who have set up shop in Spain selling property to Brits seeking fun in the sun.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513185500 -0400" stop="20260513190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513193000 -0400" stop="20260513200000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>For the Love of Dogs</title>
    <desc>Alison Hammond is preparing to dish out the dog treats and set tails wagging as she is announced as the new presenter of the award-winning ITV series, For the Love of Dogs.Alison will be heading to Battersea Dogs &amp;amp; Cats Home to help the animals in their care look for a new place to live, following the sad passing of much-loved presenter Paul O'Grady last spring.With more abandoned and stray dogs in need of care than ever, the six-part series will tell the stories of some of the latest arrivals at Battersea, as Alison rolls up her sleeves and helps Battersea's expert staff and volunteers to take care of the animals and get them ready for their potential new owners.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513195500 -0400" stop="20260513200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <desc>Race Across the World will pit pairs of travellers against each other in a race to reach the Far East without taking a single flight, with no smartphone in sight. Each contestant will only have the cash equivalent of an air fare to their destination to pay for their overland travel. If they run out, they'll need to earn more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Location, Location, Location</title>
    <desc>No floorboard is left unturned as dynamic property experts Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help house hunters find the perfect home in the perfect location.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Warship: Life in the Royal Navy</title>
    <desc>JJ Chalmers and Kate Humble are given unprecedented access to the Royal Navy, both at sea and across many of their establishments back home. Our cameras are on board as a British warship hunts down a Russian submarine; Kate gets special clearance to go behind the scenes at Britian's secretive submarine base at Faslane in Scotland and JJ reveals what it takes to be an elite Royal Marine Commando as he journeys back to the beginning of his military career.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Salisbury Poisonings: The Untold Story</title>
    <desc>Salisbury Poisonings: The Untold Story tells the story of the 2018 poisoning of ex-Russian spy Sergei Skripal and his daughter Yulia in the quiet city of Salisbury, an incident that sent shockwaves across the globe. Just months later, British mother of three Dawn Sturgess died accidentally after coming into contact with Novichok, the nerve agent used in the original attack.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513220000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Surgeons: At the Edge of Life</title>
    <desc>Transforming patients' lives, at the cutting edge of medicine. Meet the world-leading surgeons pushing science - and the human body - to its limits.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210000 -0400" stop="20260513223000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>A Killer Makes a Call</title>
    <desc>A 999 call comes into the emergency services reporting a murder. Is it a traumatised witness who survived? A distressed loved one who finds the aftermath? Or is it the chilling voice of the killer?In this series we focus on shocking murder cases where the person who makes the call is actually the murderer. In each episode we unravel the sequence of events that lead up to the call and then the investigation that follows to determine the identity of the murderer and how they were caught. In every case the call is a key piece of evidence as the police piece together the case and get justice for the victim.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513210500 -0400" stop="20260513221000 -0400" channel="E4.GB">
    <title>Celebs Go Dating</title>
    <desc>Single celebrities join an exclusive dating agency in a bid to find true love. Matchmakers pair them with non-celebrity partners and the cameras capture every romantic and cringe-filled moment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513220000 -0400" stop="20260513230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Fatal Fraud</title>
    <desc>Fatal Fraud delves into cases where financial schemes spiral into betrayal, violence and murder, exposing the deadly cost of lies fueled by greed.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514070000 -0400" stop="20260514072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514124500 -0400" stop="20260514125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514141000 -0400" stop="20260514150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514160000 -0400" stop="20260514170000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Escape to Florida</title>
    <desc>The fun-filled lives of the growing number of British and Irish expats who are turning their backs on grey skies and rising living costs at home and seeking a fresh start in America's Sunshine State.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514163000 -0400" stop="20260514171500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Bridge of Lies</title>
    <desc>Ross Kemp has turned his hand to quiz show hosting for the very first time, and will preside over teams of contestants as they compete for cash by crossing the Bridge – a collection of stepping stones featuring various truths and lies based on general knowledge categories.Each player must try to safely step on the truths and avoid the lies, or risk falling off and out of the game. Once they've conquered the Bridge on their own, successful contestants will join forces to face the dramatic final crossing for a chance to take home some cash.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514170000 -0400" stop="20260514180000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Château DIY</title>
    <desc>Adventurous British families buy and renovate beautiful chateaux in France.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514170000 -0400" stop="20260514180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514180000 -0400" stop="20260514190000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses</title>
    <desc>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses is a series that follows two British families who have set up shop in Spain selling property to Brits seeking fun in the sun.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514185500 -0400" stop="20260514190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514195500 -0400" stop="20260514200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="Sky Arts.GB">
    <title>Classic Movies: The Story of...</title>
    <desc>Classic Movies: The Story of... goes in search of the cinematically sublime. Those films that have transcended their era to enter the pantheon of greats.With each episode devoted to a single film, their story will be told with detail, affection, looking for the truth behind the myth, all the trials and triumphs that went into forging a classic. But this isn't simply history, the standard making of, it's about identifying those ingredients immortal scenes, performances, themes, luxuriant cinematography, art direction, special effects, music, even the power of a single line – that elevate a film to a new level.Hosted by Ian Nathan, guide us through the story from inception to legacy, supplemented with regular input along with special guest, with unique insight, historians who have devoted entire books, and visit to special location, where they shot or that served as  a key inspiration, bringing each of these films to life with a dynamic presentation. We are on a journey to find out not what makes a film good, but what makes it classic.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Paul Merton: Driving Amazing Trains</title>
    <desc>Paul Merton climbs into the driver's cab to take charge of some of the world's most iconic locomotives, learning what it takes to keep them running and meeting the people who keep the railways running.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>The Yorkshire Vet</title>
    <desc>The Yorkshire Vet is a documentary series about Yorkshire vet Julian Norton, his business partner Peter Wright and their team as they administer modern-day medical and surgical aid to creatures great and small. From bulldogs to bullocks, there are no creatures too large or too small for these vets.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514200000 -0400" stop="20260514203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Taskmaster</title>
    <desc>Greg Davies is the Taskmaster who, with the help of his right-hand man, Alex, sets out to test the wiles, wit and wisdom of five hyper competitive comedians through a series of ingenious challenges. With the chance to be crowned show champion, rivalry amongst the comedians is encouraged, dodgy tactics rewarded and bribes accepted.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>The Hardacres</title>
    <desc>The Hardacres chronicles the sweeping rags to riches story of a working class family in 1890s Yorkshire. A sprawling family saga, the series follows the lives, loves and fortunes of the Hardacre family as they move from a grimy fish dock to a vast country estate. When an accident at work on the docks lands Sam and Mary Hardacre – along with their three kids Joe, Liza and Harry, and Mary's inimitable mother Ma – unemployed and destitute, they have to think fast. In a bid to avoid the workhouse, the driven and determined Hardacres put their last penny into a radical business venture they hope will free them from their harsh existence on the quays of the North Yorkshire coast.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514210000 -0400" stop="20260514220500 -0400" channel="E4.GB">
    <title>Celebs Go Dating</title>
    <desc>Single celebrities join an exclusive dating agency in a bid to find true love. Matchmakers pair them with non-celebrity partners and the cameras capture every romantic and cringe-filled moment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514220000 -0400" stop="20260514230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Britain's Countryside Killers</title>
    <desc>This British series examines notorious murders that have had a lasting impact on rural communities in the UK. Each episode revisits a case that shocked once-peaceful towns and villages, highlighting how these seemingly idyllic settings were forever changed by violent crime. The series includes contributions from retired police detectives, forensic psychologists, and local journalists who provide detailed analysis of the investigative process behind each case.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515070000 -0400" stop="20260515072200 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Emmerdale is a British soap focusing on the lives of several families and locals living around an estate, a farm and the nearby village in the Yorkshire Dales. It is the second longest British soap in television history since airing its first episode on ITV in 1972, as 'Emmerdale Farm', the show was renamed in 1989.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515124500 -0400" stop="20260515125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515141000 -0400" stop="20260515150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515160000 -0400" stop="20260515170000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Escape to Florida</title>
    <desc>The fun-filled lives of the growing number of British and Irish expats who are turning their backs on grey skies and rising living costs at home and seeking a fresh start in America's Sunshine State.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515170000 -0400" stop="20260515180000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Château DIY</title>
    <desc>Adventurous British families buy and renovate beautiful chateaux in France.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515170000 -0400" stop="20260515180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515180000 -0400" stop="20260515190000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses</title>
    <desc>Sun, Sea and Selling Houses is a series that follows two British families who have set up shop in Spain selling property to Brits seeking fun in the sun.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515185500 -0400" stop="20260515190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515193000 -0400" stop="20260515200000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Bradley Walsh &amp; Son: Breaking Dad</title>
    <desc>Bradley and Barney Walsh return for more adrenaline-fuelled adventures. Like father, like son? Perhaps not.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515193000 -0400" stop="20260515200000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Unreported World</title>
    <desc>Unreported World is a foreign affairs programme produced by Quicksilver Media Productions and broadcast by Channel 4 in the United Kingdom. Over the course of its twenty-six series, reporters have travelled to dangerous locations all over the world in an attempt to uncover stories usually ignored by the world media.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515195500 -0400" stop="20260515200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Gardeners' World</title>
    <desc>Gardening show packed with good ideas, tips, advice from experts and timely reminders to get the most out of your garden, whatever its size or type.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Traffic Cops</title>
    <desc>The documentary giving an insight into the working life of officers patrolling Britain's roads transfers to Channel 5, following Yorkshire police forces tackling an ever-more sophisticated criminal fraternity from the cities to the Dales.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515200000 -0400" stop="20260515203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515220500 -0400" channel="E4.GB">
    <title>Celebs Go Dating</title>
    <desc>Single celebrities join an exclusive dating agency in a bid to find true love. Matchmakers pair them with non-celebrity partners and the cameras capture every romantic and cringe-filled moment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515213000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Have I Got News for You</title>
    <desc>Based on the week's news, Have I Got News for You is fronted by guest hosts and features two regular team captains, Paul Merton and Ian Hislop. Each week the show invites two guests to cast a jaundiced eye over the week's news, resulting in a fast flow of anarchic, spontaneous and hugely entertaining wit and humour. Guests typically represent the world of politics, comedy, show-business and journalism, and are often themselves particularly newsworthy participants. The final touches of Have I Got News for You are put together only hours before recording, allowing guests to comment on the late-breaking news stories of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515210000 -0400" stop="20260515220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>Gogglebox is a British observational documentary television show which has aired on Channel 4 since 2013. The show focuses on families, friends and couples from around the country in their living rooms watching the last week's of British television.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515220000 -0400" stop="20260515230000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>First Dates</title>
    <desc>The First Dates restaurant throws open its doors to single people looking for love.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516120000 -0400" stop="20260516124500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Football Focus</title>
    <desc>A preview of all the top footballing action with detailed analysis from an expert panel of guests.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516140000 -0400" stop="20260516150000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Dermot's Taste of Ireland</title>
    <desc>From traditional Irish stew to soda bread, fresh seafood, and boxty potato pancakes - Dermot will taste his way across the island, meeting the chefs and locals that champion and celebrate Ireland's gastronomic heritage. Having opened two of his own fish-themed restaurants and sharing some of his favourite home recipes on ITV's This Morning, he is now taking his passion on the road whilst exploring Ireland's ancient landscapes, diverse cities and stunning coastlines. From Michelin Star restaurants in the ‘Gourmet Capital of Ireland' Kinsale; to fishing for oysters by the sea in Cork; sitting down for some home-grown comfort food in Wexford; and exploring the buzz of the Dublin food scene; before venturing across to Northern Ireland and the bustling city of Belfast and beyond - Dermot's Taste of Ireland promises to be a foodie delight, full of surprises.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516175500 -0400" stop="20260516184000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Bridge of Lies Celebrity Specials</title>
    <desc>Teams of celebrities take on the nail-biting quiz hosted by Ross Kemp.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516180000 -0400" stop="20260516200000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Britain's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>Britain's Got Talent brings together the very best variety acts from across the nation as they compete to win a life changing £250,000 and a coveted spot on The Royal Variety Performance.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516192500 -0400" stop="20260516193000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News Weekend</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516200000 -0400" stop="20260516210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Angela Rippon's River Cruises</title>
    <desc>This series showcases the majesty, culture and beauty of the world's most iconic rivers. Presented by journalist and national treasure Angela Rippon, each episode transports viewers along a mighty river through bustling towns, breathtaking vistas and a fascinating journey through history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260516200000 -0400" stop="20260516203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517192500 -0400" stop="20260517193000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News Weekend</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Cruising to the Ends of the Earth</title>
    <desc>Cruising to the Ends of the Earth follows three wildly different voyages to share the diverse and breathtaking landscape of our planet. Filmed on board Princess Cruises ships, the series will journey to the frozen peaks of Alaska, the dazzling coastlines of South Korea and Japan, as well as travelling through ancient history via the Mediterranean.Along the way, viewers will meet guests and crew on board the ships for the extraordinary trips. The series will follow them on sea and on land as they embark on bucket-list experiences and explore terrains like volcanic basins, archaeological sites, and cities with fascinating cuisine and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517203000 -0400" channel="BBC Alba.GB">
    <title>An Là</title>
    <desc>National, international and local news from the BBC Alba team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517223000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Trading Places</title>
    <desc>Trading Places is an energetic, entertainingly provocative ‘fish-out-of-water' series that takes a group of three young people and plunges them into an immersive week-long 24/7 experience inside one of four extraordinary worlds whose way of life is very different from their own.Will it be fireworks or friendship when a generation raised online and on-demand come face to face with regimes built on no-nonsense rules, unshakable principles and loyalty to a strict set of values. How will the young visitors react to the rituals and regulations of their new surroundings? And as the experience transforms both them and their hosts, will either side ever be the same again?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517210000 -0400" stop="20260517220500 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Your Song</title>
    <desc>Your Song is about everyday people, who, driven by their love and connection to a particular song, will step up to the stage and share their story with the world. Whether their track helped them through heartbreak, became their anthem of triumph, or reminds them who they are, Your Song is exactly that…. Your's.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512200000 -0400" stop="20260512210000 -0400" channel="Citytv.CA">
    <title>The Price is Right Tonight</title>
    <desc>Hosted by legendary comedian and television personality Howie Mandel, The Price Is Right Tonight is a new Canadian series that brings the iconic game show's joyful wins and classic format to a primetime audience.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514220000 -0400" stop="20260514230000 -0400" channel="Citytv.CA">
    <title>Law &amp; Order Toronto: Criminal Intent</title>
    <desc>In Toronto's war on crime, the worst offenders are pursued by the detectives of the specialized criminal investigations unit. These are their stories.As a psychological thriller wrapped in a criminal investigation, Law &amp;amp; Order Toronto: Criminal Intent follows an elite squad of detectives who investigate high-profile crime and corruption in metro Toronto.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517200000 -0400" stop="20260517210000 -0400" channel="CTV.CA">
    <title>Sullivan's Crossing</title>
    <desc>After Neurosurgeon Maggie Sullivan's personal and professional life are thrown into turmoil she returns home to Sullivan's Crossing. While there, Maggie is forced to navigate her complicated present while confronting the painful past she has chosen to ignore for years.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511060000 -0400" stop="20260511090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511120000 -0400" stop="20260511130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511193000 -0400" stop="20260511200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511200000 -0400" stop="20260511203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Australian Story</title>
    <desc>These are the stories of who we are. Australian Story presents unique tales that provide an insight into Australian life with all its complexities and challenges.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511203000 -0400" stop="20260511211500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Four Corners</title>
    <desc>Four Corners is Australia's premier television current affairs program. It has been part of the national story since August 1961, exposing scandals, triggering inquiries, firing debate, confronting taboos and interpreting fads, trends and sub-cultures. Its consistently high standards of journalism and film-making have earned international recognition and an array of Walkleys, Logies and other national awards.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511212000 -0400" stop="20260511213500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Media Watch</title>
    <desc>Media Watch is Australia's leading forum for media analysis and comment.Conflicts of interest, bank backflips, deceit, misrepresentation, manipulation, plagiarism, abuse of power, technical lies and straight out fraud: Media Watch has built an unrivalled record of exposing media shenanigans since it first went to air in 1989.The media provides the information we need to make decisions about our lives, but how reliable are the media reports that shape our views of the world?Media Watch turns the spotlight onto those who literally 'make the news': the reporters, editors, sub-editors, producers, camera operators, sound recordists and photographers who claim to deliver the world to our doorsteps, radios, computers and living rooms. We also keep an eye on those who try to manipulate the media: the PR consultants, spin-doctors, lobbyists and "news makers" who set the agenda.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511213500 -0400" stop="20260511220500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Planet America</title>
    <desc>Chas Licciardello and John Barron set out to discover the real America - its politics and its people - with analysis from US and Australian experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260511230000 -0400" stop="20260511233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512060000 -0400" stop="20260512090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512120000 -0400" stop="20260512130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512193000 -0400" stop="20260512200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260512230000 -0400" stop="20260512233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513060000 -0400" stop="20260513090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513120000 -0400" stop="20260513130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513193000 -0400" stop="20260513200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513200000 -0400" stop="20260513203500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Gruen</title>
    <desc>The Gruen Transfer is about advertising, how it works, and how it works on us. It decodes and defuses the commercial messages that swirl through our lives, with the help of a panel of ad industry experts. From Season 5 the show was renamed "Gruen Planet" and expanded the topics covered to include political and commercial "spin" as well as advertising. In 2015 it is re-named as Gruen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513203500 -0400" stop="20260513212500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Guy Montgomery's Guy Mont Spelling Bee</title>
    <desc>Get ready to laugh-out-loud as Guy Montgomery and his loyal assistant Aaron Chen are joined by some of Australia's favourite personalities, testing their spelling prowess with wildly inventive spelling challenges designed to befuddle, bamboozle, and bedazzle them all.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260513230000 -0400" stop="20260513233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514060000 -0400" stop="20260514090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514120000 -0400" stop="20260514130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514193000 -0400" stop="20260514200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260514230000 -0400" stop="20260514233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515060000 -0400" stop="20260515090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515120000 -0400" stop="20260515130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260515230000 -0400" stop="20260515233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517090000 -0400" stop="20260517100000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Insiders</title>
    <desc>Australia's must-watch political program continues to be a platform for the country's best political analysts and commentators, taking you to the heart of the action every Sunday morning.Insiders entered a very crowded Sunday morning political market in 2001. But our approach was to provide coverage with so many more elements, and to do it in a way that is informative but irreverent. And of course have a few laughs along the way. If you took politics too seriously you'd go mad," said founding host Barrie Cassidy.Insiders is the most watched morning show on Australian TV any day of the week. So start your week with the program the politicians rely on to find out what's going on.Insiders is broadcast on Sundays from 9am to 10am (AEST) on ABC TV and the ABC News channel.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517123000 -0400" stop="20260517133000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Landline</title>
    <desc>Pip Courtney &amp;amp; a team of Landline reporters around the country bring you up to date with the issues affecting rural &amp;amp; regional Australia. From farming, agriculture, food, economics, innovation, climate, infrastructure &amp;amp; more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260517201500 -0400" stop="20260517204000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Bad Company</title>
    <desc>Set within the crumbling walls of The Argyle, a venerable iconic theatre company on the brink of bankruptcy, Bad Company follows Margie, the Argyle's volatile artistic director, whose unchecked whims have sent the company spiraling, and Julia a high-flying corporate executive brought in to clean up Margie's mess.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
</tv>