<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv generator-info-name="TVMaze EPG Generator" generator-info-url="https://www.tvmaze.com/api">
  <channel id="CNN.US">
    <display-name>CNN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.US">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CBS.US">
    <display-name>CBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="MS NOW.US">
    <display-name>MS NOW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Newsmax.US">
    <display-name>Newsmax</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="A&amp;E.US">
    <display-name>A&amp;E</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NBC.US">
    <display-name>NBC</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery.US">
    <display-name>Discovery</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ESPN.US">
    <display-name>ESPN</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Bravo.US">
    <display-name>Bravo</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="HBO.US">
    <display-name>HBO</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="History.US">
    <display-name>History</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="NFL Network.US">
    <display-name>NFL Network</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Syndication.US">
    <display-name>Syndication</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="The CW.US">
    <display-name>The CW</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="FOX.US">
    <display-name>FOX</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="PBS.US">
    <display-name>PBS</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Comedy Central.US">
    <display-name>Comedy Central</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="STARZ.US">
    <display-name>STARZ</display-name>
    <country>US</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="5.GB">
    <display-name>5</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC One.GB">
    <display-name>BBC One</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Channel 4.GB">
    <display-name>Channel 4</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ITV1.GB">
    <display-name>ITV1</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="BBC Two.GB">
    <display-name>BBC Two</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <display-name>TRUE CRIME</display-name>
    <country>GB</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="CTV.CA">
    <display-name>CTV</display-name>
    <country>CA</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="ABC.AU">
    <display-name>ABC</display-name>
    <country>AU</country>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Discovery.AU">
    <display-name>Discovery</display-name>
    <country>AU</country>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260710000000 -0400" stop="20260710020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260710020000 -0400" stop="20260710030000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Now</title>
    <desc>ABC World News Now gives viewers up-to-date information on current events and news from around the world, airing in the overnight hours. Its tone is somewhat lighter than a regular news broadcast, though reports are filed from the usual ABC News correspondents. Weather and pop culture stories round out the reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711070000 -0400" stop="20260711080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711070000 -0400" stop="20260711090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Saturday Morning</title>
    <desc>Hosts Jeff Glor, Dana Jacobson and Michelle Miller provide original reporting, breaking news, and profiles of leading figures in culture and the arts from the Times Square studio on the Saturday edition of the CBS morning news family.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711070000 -0400" stop="20260711100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711090000 -0400" stop="20260711110000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>America Right Now</title>
    <desc>Tom Basile tackles the week's biggest stories with top talkers from politics, Hollywood, and across America.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711090000 -0400" stop="20260711093000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Lucky Dog</title>
    <desc>On Lucky Dog, animal trainer Brandon McMillan's second home is the neighborhood animal shelter where he is determined to rescue hard-to-love, out-of control, untrained and unadoptable dogs. Then, back at Brandon's training facility known as the Lucky Dog Ranch, he embarks on the seemingly impossible task of turning the frightened pooches into perfect pets. In the end, a lucky family will adopt an even luckier dog, making each episode an adoption story that warms the heart.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711100000 -0400" stop="20260711110000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>When a house has been left for dead, the Zombie House Flippers bring it back to life and into beautifully remade shape for top dollar. These flippers show the inner workings of this high-stakes world full of unexpected disasters, hidden costs, and quirky personalities. With tight budgets and short timelines, it's a mad scramble to finish these flips and make bank for the team.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711100000 -0400" stop="20260711130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Connect with Jacob Soboroff</title>
    <desc>Connect with Jacob Soboroffwill be the network's first Los Angeles-based program. Built around the connection Soboroff has forged with the MS NOW audience for more than a decade, Connect will bring viewers closer to the stories shaping the country. Connect will also bring Soboroff's storied reporting from the ground in Los Angeles and beyond to help connect the dots between what's happening in local communities throughout the country and larger national conversations driving politics, culture, and daily life.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711110000 -0400" stop="20260711130000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Saturday Report</title>
    <desc>Rita Cosby and Jon Glasgow tackles the big headlines with smart analysis from top experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711110000 -0400" stop="20260711120000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Zombie House Flipping: Family Business</title>
    <desc>In Columbus, Ohio, power flipper Tommy Harr and his family have built a business on seeing opportunity where others see disaster. Their edge comes from within the family — two generations of elite home inspectors, a fearless construction crew led by his middle brother, and a mom who doubles as both designer and real estate agent. Together, they take on the city's worst "zombie" houses, transforming rundown properties into stunning dream homes.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711130000 -0400" stop="20260711150000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>Saturday Agenda</title>
    <desc>Rob Astorino reveals Washington's inner workings and the fight for core values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711130000 -0400" stop="20260711160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711150000 -0400" stop="20260711153000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>WNBA Tip-Off</title>
    <desc>WNBA Tip-Off serves as the pre-game telecast on CBS. It features a less-scripted format, highlighted by a lively round-table discussion and debate of the top story lines around the league.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711170000 -0400" stop="20260711190000 -0400" channel="Newsmax.US">
    <title>The Count</title>
    <desc>Newsmax counts up the top stories of the week, while offering analysis by lawmakers, newsmakers, and policy experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711170000 -0400" stop="20260711180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711200000 -0400" stop="20260711210000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Storage Wars: Back to the Locker</title>
    <desc>Storage Wars: Back to the Locker refers to a series of episodes within the larger "Storage Wars" series, where the focus is on the competitive bidding and treasure hunting within abandoned storage units. These episodes continue the main show's premise of professional buyers vying to acquire the contents of storage lockers, often with the hope of finding valuable items among the discarded belongings. The "Back to the Locker" part emphasizes the return to the core concept of exploring what lies behind the doors of these storage units.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711210000 -0400" stop="20260711220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Storage Wars follows professional buyers and their teams as they scour repossessed storage units in search of hidden treasure. Part gamblers, part detectives, these auction pros have found everything from coffins to the world's most valuable comic book collection, paying as little as ten dollars for items valued in the millions.Each episode of Storage Wars follows a group of bidders as they get a quick peek inside the units, aided only by the beam of a flashlight. They then must assess on the spot if the unit is worth a bid and how high they will actually go to grasp the gold. The high-stakes fun begins as we see if the resulting buy is full of mostly trash... or true treasure.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712070000 -0400" stop="20260712080000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America: Weekend Edition</title>
    <desc>GMA Weekend expanded to seven days a week in September 2004, providing up-to-the-minute news, weather and topical features from the familiar set of the weekday program located at the crossroads of the world, Times Square. The show's increased focus on lifestyle, leisure and family-oriented topics are suited for the relaxed pace of the weekend, attracting engaged and loyal GMA viewers as they start their days.Co-anchors Dan Harris and Paula Faris bring great energy and vitality to the morning show. In his 11 years at ABC News, Dan has traveled the globe, reporting from Haiti, Pakistan, Afghanistan, Iraq, Ground Zero, South Korea, Israel and the West Bank. His interests range from international affairs and politics to technology and indie music. Former anchor of ABC's World News Now and America This Morning, Paula delivered unforgettable and colorful accounts from the World Cup. Her popular Real Money reports have shown American families how to save thousands of dollars. As the audience on the weekend continues to grow, GMA is now the #1 morning newscast on Saturdays and regularly beats NBC's Today on Sunday mornings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712070000 -0400" stop="20260712100000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weekend</title>
    <desc>Fresh analysis of the week's biggest events and a rotating crew of major D.C. newsmakers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712080000 -0400" stop="20260712090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist</title>
    <desc>Sunday TODAY with Willie Geist delivers morning news, videos, and photos about current events.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712083000 -0400" stop="20260712090000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>RV There Yet?</title>
    <desc>Explore America's national parks and check out the fun detours along the way! Featuring hacks to common RV challenges, cooking tips, best routs, must-have equipment, RV care and more!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712090000 -0400" stop="20260712100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Meet the Press</title>
    <desc>For almost as long as there has been television, there's been Meet the Press. The hourlong Sunday morning public affairs program has featured interviews with countless U.S. and world leaders, and has reviewed, analyzed and discussed the news of the week -- all while looking toward the week ahead.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712090000 -0400" stop="20260712100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>State of the Union with Jake Tapper and Dana Bash</title>
    <desc>Jake Tapper and Dana Bash bring together major newsmakers, analysts and experts to tackle pressing domestic issues and diplomacy on the global stage.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712090000 -0400" stop="20260712103000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS News Sunday Morning</title>
    <desc>CBS News Sunday Morning is a early morning news and magazine program that airs on Sunday's on CBS.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712100000 -0400" stop="20260712110000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Fareed Zakaria GPS</title>
    <desc>Fareed Zakaria GPS is a weekly public affairs show hosted by journalist and author Fareed Zakaria. As of November 2011, the show airs Sundays at 10 am Eastern Time and 1 pm Eastern Time on CNN. The show also airs Sundays at 1200 and 1900 GMT on CNN International. The "GPS" in the show's title stands for "Global Public Square," a reference to the show's focus on international issues and foreign affairs. On August 10, 2012, CNN suspended the program pending their investigation of suspected plagiarism. One week later, the New York Times reported, "Time and CNN said they had completed their reviews, found no evidence of plagiarism, and restored Mr. Zakaria to his demanding schedule." Each installment features Zakaria leading a panel discussion and conducting an extended one-on-one interview.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712100000 -0400" stop="20260712110000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>This Week</title>
    <desc>This Week  is hosted by former Clinton White House staffer and current co-anchor of ABC's weekday morning news show "Good Morning America", George Stephanopoulos offers a look at current events with a focus on the politics of the day. Each week's show includes interviews with top newsmakers (including some of the nation's top political leaders) as well as a roundtable discussion, usually featuring journalists from ABC and other news organizations, of the week's happenings. Since 2008, the program has broadcast from a studio at the Newseum in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712100000 -0400" stop="20260712130000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Connect with Jacob Soboroff</title>
    <desc>Connect with Jacob Soboroffwill be the network's first Los Angeles-based program. Built around the connection Soboroff has forged with the MS NOW audience for more than a decade, Connect will bring viewers closer to the stories shaping the country. Connect will also bring Soboroff's storied reporting from the ground in Los Angeles and beyond to help connect the dots between what's happening in local communities throughout the country and larger national conversations driving politics, culture, and daily life.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712103000 -0400" stop="20260712113000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Face the Nation</title>
    <desc>Face the Nation is a news interview program which airs every Sunday morning, live from the CBS studio in Washington D.C. It is dedicated to interviewing newsmakers on the latest issues. Guests include government leaders, politicians, and international figures in the news. CBS News… More correspondents engage the guests in a lively roundtable discussion focusing on current topics. The show started on November 7th, 1954, and was originally broadcast on both CBS Television and Radio Networks. After close to two decades, the program was taken off CBS radio.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712120000 -0400" stop="20260712150000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>MLB All-Star Futures Game</title>
    <desc>The MLB All-Star Futures Game is an annual baseball exhibition game hosted by Major League Baseball. Started in 1999, a team of minor league baseball prospects from the United States and a team of prospects from other countries in the World compete against each other. It is played as part of the festivities of the Major League Baseball All-Star Game.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712130000 -0400" stop="20260712160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Alex Witt Reports</title>
    <desc>The latest breaking news, reporting and live coverage of the day's important stories; hosted by trusted NBC News journalists, these dynamic hours offer discussions with newsmakers, journalists and politicians.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712170000 -0400" stop="20260712180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>PoliticsNation</title>
    <desc>Rev. Al Sharpton highlights important political stories and issues that require a national platform.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712183000 -0400" stop="20260712190000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>WNBA Countdown</title>
    <desc>WNBA Countdown serves as the primer for game telecasts on both ESPN2 and ESPN. It features a less-scripted format, highlighted by a lively round-table discussion and debate of the top story lines around the league.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712200000 -0400" stop="20260712213000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Big Brother</title>
    <desc>Big Brother follows a group of people living together in a house outfitted with dozens of high-definition cameras and microphones recording their every move, 24 hours a day. Each week, the Houseguests will vote someone out of the house. At the end, the last remaining Houseguest will receive the grand prize of $500,000.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712200000 -0400" stop="20260712210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Atlanta</title>
    <desc>An up-close and personal look at life in Hotlanta, The Real Housewives of Atlanta follows five glamorous southern belles as they balance motherhood, demanding careers and a fast-paced social calendar, and shows what life is like in the most exclusive areas of Atlanta. These driven and ambitious women prove that they're not just "housewives," but entrepreneurs, doting mothers and classy southern women. These ladies show the world what it takes to live large in some of the hottest zip codes in the south.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712200000 -0400" stop="20260712220100 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Naked and Afraid: Global Showdown</title>
    <desc>Survivalists from all over the world - including Brazil, Australia, Mexico, and the United States - represent their homelands in a grueling 40-day primitive bushcraft competition. Paired with a partner, their skills, toughness and teamwork will be tested as they compete for national pride and the largest cash prize in franchise history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712210000 -0400" stop="20260712220000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>Set 200 years before the events of Game of Thrones, House of the Dragon tells the history of House Targaryen as they fight through a civil war.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712210000 -0400" stop="20260712220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Hazardous History with Henry Winkler</title>
    <desc>The eight-episode fast-paced, nostalgia-fueled series will take viewers on a thrilling ride through America's past.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712210000 -0400" stop="20260712213000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712220000 -0400" stop="20260712230000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>In the Eye of the Storm</title>
    <desc>In the Eye of the Storm Megastorms like 2021's Hurricane Ida and the 2023 Maui Wildfires were captured by onlookers who found themselves in the wrong place at the right time and boldly held up their camera phones to document their experiences.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712220100 -0400" stop="20260712230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE LFG</title>
    <desc>WWE LFG (Legends &amp;amp; Future Greats) will offer viewers an inside look at the rigorous training process, featuring iconic WWE Legends such as Paul "Triple H" Levesque and Shawn Michaels and weekly regular coaches Undertaker, Booker T, Mickie James and Bubba Ray Dudley as they mentor a new generation in weekly matches on their quest to become the next WWE Superstars.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712220300 -0400" stop="20260712230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Food That Built America</title>
    <desc>For generations of Americans, food titans like Henry Heinz, Milton Hershey, John and Will Kellogg, C.W. Post and the McDonald brothers have literally been household names, but you don't know their stories. Before they were brand names, they were brilliant, sometimes ruthless, visionaries who revolutionized food and changed the landscape of America forever. This miniseries event will tell the fascinating stories of the people behind the food that built America – those who used brains, muscle, blood, sweat and tears to get to America's heart through its stomach, and along the way built cities, invented new technologies and helped win wars.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712230400 -0400" stop="20260712233400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE's Greatest Moments</title>
    <desc>WWE's Greatest Moments will feature legendary play-by-play announcer Michael Cole hosting half-hour episodes with various WWE Superstars &amp;amp; Legends, including "Stone Cold" Steve Austin, Hulk Hogan, Kevin Owens and others, to share vivid recollections and perspectives on the most remarkable moments in wrestling history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712233400 -0400" stop="20260713000300 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>WWE's Greatest Moments</title>
    <desc>WWE's Greatest Moments will feature legendary play-by-play announcer Michael Cole hosting half-hour episodes with various WWE Superstars &amp;amp; Legends, including "Stone Cold" Steve Austin, Hulk Hogan, Kevin Owens and others, to share vivid recollections and perspectives on the most remarkable moments in wrestling history.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713050000 -0400" stop="20260713060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713060000 -0400" stop="20260713090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713060000 -0400" stop="20260713070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713070000 -0400" stop="20260713100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713070000 -0400" stop="20260713090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713070000 -0400" stop="20260713090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713070000 -0400" stop="20260713090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713080000 -0400" stop="20260713100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713090000 -0400" stop="20260713100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713090000 -0400" stop="20260713110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713090000 -0400" stop="20260713100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713100000 -0400" stop="20260713120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713100000 -0400" stop="20260713120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713100000 -0400" stop="20260713110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713110000 -0400" stop="20260713120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713120000 -0400" stop="20260713130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713120000 -0400" stop="20260713140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713130000 -0400" stop="20260713160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713130000 -0400" stop="20260713140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713140000 -0400" stop="20260713150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713140000 -0400" stop="20260713150000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>General Hospital</title>
    <desc>General Hospital, which celebrated its golden anniversary on April 1, 2013, continues its tradition of passion, intrigue and adventure that takes place in the fictional town of Port Charles in upstate New York. The glamour and excitement of those who have come to find their destinies in this familiar seaport town intertwine with the lives, loves and fortunes of beloved, well-known faces. As always, love, danger and mind blowing plot twists continue to abound on General Hospital with contemporary storylines and unforgettable characters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713140000 -0400" stop="20260713160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713160000 -0400" stop="20260713180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713160000 -0400" stop="20260713170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713170000 -0400" stop="20260713190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713180000 -0400" stop="20260713190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713183000 -0400" stop="20260713190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713190000 -0400" stop="20260713200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713190000 -0400" stop="20260713200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>All American</title>
    <desc>When a rising high school football player from South Central L.A. is recruited to play for Beverly Hills High, the wins, losses and struggles of two families from vastly different worlds — Compton and Beverly Hills — begin to collide. Inspired by the life of pro football player Spencer Paysinger.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210100 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Dancing with the Stars: The Next Pro</title>
    <desc>Dancing with the Stars: The Next Pro will feature up-and-coming professional dancers who will live in a house together and compete in a grueling audition process. The winner will land a coveted spot as a pro dancer on the next season of "Dancing With the Stars."</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>The 1% Club is a unique, compelling and funny entertainment show that tests the nation's intelligence, based on a scientific survey. It's a chance to test how your brain works through a series of questions that all have a right answer but can also lead to a series of entertaining wrong answers along the way. Whether you're a contestant vying for the cash prize or a viewer playing with your friends and family on the app, answer enough questions correctly, and you could earn yourself a place in the 1% Club: an elite group of people who can honestly say they've outwitted 99% of the population.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>World War II with Tom Hanks</title>
    <desc>For eighty years, the Second World War has remained the most devastating and defining conflict in human history. World War II with Tom Hanks is a landmark documentary event that reexamines the war through the lens of a new century. Told over twenty hours and guided by Tom Hanks, whose lifelong passion for this history has shaped some of the most profound screen portrayals of the era, the series captures the full arc of the war — from the rise of fascism in Europe to the fall of Berlin, from Pearl Harbor to Hiroshima, and the uneasy peace that follows. Each episode uncovers new dimensions of the conflict: the decisions that shaped the battlefield, the unseen networks that sustained the war effort, and the aftershocks that still shape our world today. "World War II with Tom Hanks" is the definitive retelling of that story for a new generation: a sweeping, deeply human portrait of how the modern world was forged in the fires of global war.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Anderson Cooper 360°</title>
    <desc>Anderson Cooper 360° (commonly shortened to either AC-360 or 360) is a television news show on CNN, hosted by the American journalist Anderson Cooper. The program covers a number of news stories of the day, usually through live or taped reports from the network's correspondents. The coverage can also include analysis from experts on the issues, commonly featured in or after the taped reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Below Deck Mediterranean</title>
    <desc>With a new boat, new location, and new faces, the excitement, drama, and adventure of life aboard a private luxury yacht is taken to another level in the Mediterranean. Providing unparalleled service to wealthy and uncompromising guests is made even more difficult as the team faces everything from love triangles to seeing fellow crew members shockingly cross the line with guests. Voyaging from Santorini, Mykonos, and many of the Greek islands, each episode features a new group of elite clientele who present a new set of challenges, all while offering the crew a glamorous lifestyle and exotic perks that most people only dream of experiencing. For these young, attractive, and adventurous yachties, the "work hard, play harder" nature of the job combined with the pressure of working in the most exclusive yachting scene in the world pushes the team close to the breaking point on Below Deck Mediterranean.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Contraband: Seized at the Border</title>
    <desc>The border between the USA and Mexico is the busiest in the world. This series follows the work of America's Customs and Border Protection agency, whose job is to defend the border and stop terrorists, drugs and illegal weapons from entering the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>The Quiz with Balls</title>
    <desc>The Quiz with Balls pits brains against balls combining a high-stakes quiz show with a large-scale physical competition. Each episode features two families competing for $100,000 in a "battle of the balls".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>All American</title>
    <desc>When a rising high school football player from South Central L.A. is recruited to play for Beverly Hills High, the wins, losses and struggles of two families from vastly different worlds — Compton and Beverly Hills — begin to collide. Inspired by the life of pro football player Spencer Paysinger.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>World War II with Tom Hanks</title>
    <desc>For eighty years, the Second World War has remained the most devastating and defining conflict in human history. World War II with Tom Hanks is a landmark documentary event that reexamines the war through the lens of a new century. Told over twenty hours and guided by Tom Hanks, whose lifelong passion for this history has shaped some of the most profound screen portrayals of the era, the series captures the full arc of the war — from the rise of fascism in Europe to the fall of Berlin, from Pearl Harbor to Hiroshima, and the uneasy peace that follows. Each episode uncovers new dimensions of the conflict: the decisions that shaped the battlefield, the unseen networks that sustained the war effort, and the aftershocks that still shape our world today. "World War II with Tom Hanks" is the definitive retelling of that story for a new generation: a sweeping, deeply human portrait of how the modern world was forged in the fires of global war.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The McBee Dynasty: Real American Cowboys</title>
    <desc>The McBee Dynasty: Real American Cowboys follows patriarch Steve McBee, the hard-working founder of the family business, and his four sons: Steven Jr. the business-minded heir apparent, Cole the underdog who works hard in the field, Jesse the quiet cowboy, and Brayden who has the least interest in farming.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>American Ninja Warrior</title>
    <desc>American Ninja Warrior is an action-packed series that follows competitors as they tackle a series of challenging obstacle courses in both qualifying and finals rounds across the country. Those that successfully complete a course in their designated region move on to the national finals round in Las Vegas, where they face a stunning four-stage course modeled after the famed Mt. Midoriyama in Japan.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713220000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Source with Kaitlan Collins</title>
    <desc>The Source with Kaitlan Collins - Kaitlan Collins chases the facts, asks the tough questions, and connects with her sources in primetime.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713220000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>120 Hours Behind Bars</title>
    <desc>Over five intense days, 120 Hours Behind Bars delivers an unfiltered look inside America's toughest jails, where officers are outnumbered, cellblocks are overcrowded, and violence erupts without warning.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713220000 -0400" stop="20260713233000 -0400" channel="PBS.US">
    <title>Independent Lens</title>
    <desc>Independent Lens is an anthology of independent documentary films.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713220000 -0400" stop="20260713230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713220000 -0400" stop="20260713230000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Late Night Law</title>
    <desc>Ride along as officers face the dangers and decisions that define the night shift.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713220000 -0400" stop="20260713230000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip</title>
    <desc>In CNN NewsNight with Abby Phillip, she delivers a thoughtful, sharp approach to the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713220000 -0400" stop="20260713223000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713220300 -0400" stop="20260713230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>History's Greatest Machines with Dolph Lundgren</title>
    <desc>Machines can rewrite history – and no one knows that better than action legend and chemical engineer graduate Dolph Lundgren. Join him as he uncovers the stories behind history's most groundbreaking machines: witness secret stealth helicopters, spy planes outrunning missiles, espionage tech that won wars, to the rocket that took humanity to the moon. Guided by Dolph's keen insight and charisma, this is a thrilling ride through the gears, guts, and genius behind the machines that reshaped our world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713230000 -0400" stop="20260714000000 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713230000 -0400" stop="20260714000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713233500 -0400" stop="20260714003500 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Jimmy Kimmel Live</title>
    <desc>Jimmy Kimmel Live features a diverse lineup of guests that include celebrities, athletes, musical acts, comedians and human-interest subjects, along with comedy bits and a house band.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713233500 -0400" stop="20260714003500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Emmy Award and Grammy Award winner Jimmy Fallon brought NBC's "The Tonight Show" back to its New York origins when he launched The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from Rockefeller Center. Fallon puts his own stamp on the storied NBC late-night franchise with his unique comedic wit, on-point pop culture awareness, welcoming style and impeccable taste in music with the award-winning house band, The Roots.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713000000 -0400" stop="20260713020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713000000 -0400" stop="20260713020000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Story Is with Elex Michaelson</title>
    <desc>The Story Is will feature live nightly panels and debates on set featuring a range of voices including attorneys Gloria Allred and Areva Martin, conservative talk radio hosts Larry Elder and Jennifer Horn, progressive podcast host Brian Tyler Cohen, former California GOP chair Jessica Millan Patterson and journalists Peter Hamby from Puck and POLITICO's Melanie Mason.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713003500 -0400" stop="20260713013500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Late Night with Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Seth Meyers, who is Saturday Night Live's longest serving anchor on the show's wildly popular "Weekend Update," takes over as host of NBC's Late Night — home to A-list celebrity guests, memorable comedy and the best in musical talent.As the Emmy Award-winning head writer for "SNL," Meyers has established a reputation for sharp wit and perfectly timed comedy, and has gained fame for his spot-on jokes and satire. Meyers takes his departure from "SNL" to his new post at "Late Night," as Jimmy Fallon moves to The Tonight Show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713020000 -0400" stop="20260713030000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Now</title>
    <desc>ABC World News Now gives viewers up-to-date information on current events and news from around the world, airing in the overnight hours. Its tone is somewhat lighter than a regular news broadcast, though reports are filed from the usual ABC News correspondents. Weather and pop culture stories round out the reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714050000 -0400" stop="20260714060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714060000 -0400" stop="20260714090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714060000 -0400" stop="20260714070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714070000 -0400" stop="20260714100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714070000 -0400" stop="20260714090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714070000 -0400" stop="20260714090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714070000 -0400" stop="20260714090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714080000 -0400" stop="20260714100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714090000 -0400" stop="20260714100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714090000 -0400" stop="20260714110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714090000 -0400" stop="20260714100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714100000 -0400" stop="20260714120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714100000 -0400" stop="20260714120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714100000 -0400" stop="20260714110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714110000 -0400" stop="20260714120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714120000 -0400" stop="20260714130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714120000 -0400" stop="20260714140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714130000 -0400" stop="20260714160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714130000 -0400" stop="20260714140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714140000 -0400" stop="20260714150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714140000 -0400" stop="20260714160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714160000 -0400" stop="20260714180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714160000 -0400" stop="20260714170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714170000 -0400" stop="20260714190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714180000 -0400" stop="20260714190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714183000 -0400" stop="20260714190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714190000 -0400" stop="20260714200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714190000 -0400" stop="20260714200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714220000 -0400" channel="The CW.US">
    <title>WWE NXT</title>
    <desc>Each Wednesday at 8:00 p.m. ET, WWE Superstars and Divas of tomorrow face off on WWE NXT, a one-hour weekly show that features the brightest and best of WWE's rising stars. WWE NXT showcases the Superstars and Divas from WWE's Performance Center as well as appearances from WWE Superstars and Legends in an intimate setting. WWE NXT broadcasts from the state-of-the-art Full Sail LIVE venue on the Full Sail University in campus in Orlando, Florida.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714233000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>MLB All-Star Game</title>
    <desc>The MLB All-Star Game is an annual professional baseball game sanctioned by Major League Baseball (MLB) contested between the All-Stars from the American League (AL) and National League (NL), currently selected by fans for starting fielders, by managers for pitchers, and by managers and players for reserves. The game usually occurs on either the second or third Tuesday in July, and is meant to mark a symbolic halfway-point in the MLB season (though not the mathematical halfway-point which, for most seasons, is usually found within the previous calendar week). Both of the major leagues share an All-Star break, with no regular-season games scheduled on the day before or two days after the All-Star Game itself. Some additional events and festivities associated with the game take place each year close to and during this break in the regular season.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714220000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>With the talent search open to acts of all ages, America's Got Talent has brought the variety format back to the forefront of American culture by showcasing performers from across the country. The series is a true celebration of the American spirit, featuring a colorful array of singers, dancers, comedians, contortionists, impressionists, jugglers, magicians, ventriloquists and hopeful stars, all vying for their chance to win America's hearts and the $1 million prize.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714220000 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Homestead Rescue: Intervention</title>
    <desc>Wilderness experts confront people living on the edge of survival to make them choose between a professional rescue and continuing to live under dangerous conditions.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>In the City</title>
    <desc>In the city that never sleeps, a group of New Yorkers navigates the biggest transitions of their lives — marriage, parenthood, reinvention, and the reality of growing up without growing apart. Can they have it all, or will they need to choose between the lives they've built and the futures they never saw coming?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714210000 -0400" stop="20260714220000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch</title>
    <desc>Gaining full and unprecedented access to one of the most infamous and secretive hotspots of paranormal and UFO-related activities on earth, The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch will feature a team of scientists and experts who will conduct a thorough search of this infamous 512-acre property located in Utah's Uinta Basin. They will attempt to find out the truth behind more than 200 years of mysteries - involving everything from UFO sightings and paranormal activities to animal mutilations and Native American legends of a shape-shifting creature known simply as The Skinwalker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714210000 -0400" stop="20260714213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>With a record number of Americans trading city life for homes in the suburbs, relationships between neighbors are being put to the test. Neighborhood Wars takes viewers into the homes and backyards of neighbors across the country with some of the most unexpected and emotionally charged events caught on camera. Featuring footage from cell phones, drones, home security cameras and more, the series showcases the kindness and conflict between real-life neighbors throughout the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714210000 -0400" stop="20260714220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714210000 -0400" stop="20260714213000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714213000 -0400" stop="20260714220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>With a record number of Americans trading city life for homes in the suburbs, relationships between neighbors are being put to the test. Neighborhood Wars takes viewers into the homes and backyards of neighbors across the country with some of the most unexpected and emotionally charged events caught on camera. Featuring footage from cell phones, drones, home security cameras and more, the series showcases the kindness and conflict between real-life neighbors throughout the US.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714220000 -0400" stop="20260714223000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Password</title>
    <desc>Password is a reboot of the 1960s game show in which two teams, composed of a celebrity player and a contestant, attempt to convey mystery words to each other using only single-word clues in order to win a cash prize.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714220000 -0400" stop="20260714223000 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch: Behind the Gates</title>
    <desc>The Secret of Skinwalker Ranch: Behind the Gates offers a more in-depth look at the mysteries surrounding the ranch and the team's investigations, often featuring interviews with team members and experts.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714220000 -0400" stop="20260714230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714220100 -0400" stop="20260714223200 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Squatters</title>
    <desc>Squatters are taking over homes across the country and Flash Shelton is the man who gets them out. With bold tactics and street smarts, Flash and his team face tense and sometimes dangerous situations to help families reclaim their property. Each episode reveals the emotional and high-stakes battles where the fight for justice can quickly escalate, putting everyone involved at risk. This is the struggle to take back what rightfully belongs to them.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714223000 -0400" stop="20260714230000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Password</title>
    <desc>Password is a reboot of the 1960s game show in which two teams, composed of a celebrity player and a contestant, attempt to convey mystery words to each other using only single-word clues in order to win a cash prize.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714223200 -0400" stop="20260714233300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The Proof Is Out There: Unexplained Edition</title>
    <desc>In this special edition series of The Proof Is Out There, journalist Tony Harris explores some of the most astonishing phenomena ever captured on camera. From UFOs and cryptids to eerie encounters and unexplained forces, Tony and a team of experts analyze the evidence and deliver their verdict.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714223200 -0400" stop="20260714230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Squatters</title>
    <desc>Squatters are taking over homes across the country and Flash Shelton is the man who gets them out. With bold tactics and street smarts, Flash and his team face tense and sometimes dangerous situations to help families reclaim their property. Each episode reveals the emotional and high-stakes battles where the fight for justice can quickly escalate, putting everyone involved at risk. This is the struggle to take back what rightfully belongs to them.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714230000 -0400" stop="20260714233500 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714230000 -0400" stop="20260715000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714233500 -0400" stop="20260715003500 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Jimmy Kimmel Live</title>
    <desc>Jimmy Kimmel Live features a diverse lineup of guests that include celebrities, athletes, musical acts, comedians and human-interest subjects, along with comedy bits and a house band.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714233500 -0400" stop="20260715003500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Emmy Award and Grammy Award winner Jimmy Fallon brought NBC's "The Tonight Show" back to its New York origins when he launched The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from Rockefeller Center. Fallon puts his own stamp on the storied NBC late-night franchise with his unique comedic wit, on-point pop culture awareness, welcoming style and impeccable taste in music with the award-winning house band, The Roots.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714003500 -0400" stop="20260714013500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Late Night with Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Seth Meyers, who is Saturday Night Live's longest serving anchor on the show's wildly popular "Weekend Update," takes over as host of NBC's Late Night — home to A-list celebrity guests, memorable comedy and the best in musical talent.As the Emmy Award-winning head writer for "SNL," Meyers has established a reputation for sharp wit and perfectly timed comedy, and has gained fame for his spot-on jokes and satire. Meyers takes his departure from "SNL" to his new post at "Late Night," as Jimmy Fallon moves to The Tonight Show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714020000 -0400" stop="20260714030000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Now</title>
    <desc>ABC World News Now gives viewers up-to-date information on current events and news from around the world, airing in the overnight hours. Its tone is somewhat lighter than a regular news broadcast, though reports are filed from the usual ABC News correspondents. Weather and pop culture stories round out the reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715050000 -0400" stop="20260715060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715060000 -0400" stop="20260715090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715060000 -0400" stop="20260715070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715070000 -0400" stop="20260715100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715070000 -0400" stop="20260715090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715070000 -0400" stop="20260715090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715070000 -0400" stop="20260715090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715080000 -0400" stop="20260715100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715090000 -0400" stop="20260715100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715090000 -0400" stop="20260715110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715090000 -0400" stop="20260715100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715100000 -0400" stop="20260715120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715100000 -0400" stop="20260715120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715100000 -0400" stop="20260715110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715110000 -0400" stop="20260715120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715120000 -0400" stop="20260715130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715120000 -0400" stop="20260715140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715130000 -0400" stop="20260715160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715130000 -0400" stop="20260715140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715140000 -0400" stop="20260715150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715140000 -0400" stop="20260715160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715160000 -0400" stop="20260715180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715160000 -0400" stop="20260715170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715170000 -0400" stop="20260715190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715180000 -0400" stop="20260715190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715183000 -0400" stop="20260715190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715190000 -0400" stop="20260715200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715190000 -0400" stop="20260715200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715200000 -0400" stop="20260715230000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The ESPYS</title>
    <desc>The ESPYS is an awards show that airs annually an ESPY Award (short for Excellence in Sports Performance Yearly Award) is an accolade presented by the American cable television network ESPN to recognize individual and team athletic achievement and other sports-related performance during the calendar year preceding a given annual ceremony. The first ESPYS were awarded in 1993. Because of the ceremony's rescheduling prior to the 2002 iteration thereof, awards presented in 2002 were for achievement and performances during the seventeen-plus previous months. As the similarly styled Grammy (for music), Emmy (for television), Academy Award (for film), and Tony (for theatre), the ESPYS are hosted by a contemporary celebrity; the style, though, is more relaxed, light, and self-referential than that of many other awards shows, with comedic sketches usually included.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715200000 -0400" stop="20260715213000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Big Brother</title>
    <desc>Big Brother follows a group of people living together in a house outfitted with dozens of high-definition cameras and microphones recording their every move, 24 hours a day. Each week, the Houseguests will vote someone out of the house. At the end, the last remaining Houseguest will receive the grand prize of $500,000.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715200000 -0400" stop="20260715210000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>MasterChef</title>
    <desc>Three celebrated food experts put the latest group of contestants through a series of challenging elimination rounds and turn one home cook into a culinary master.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715200000 -0400" stop="20260715210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Valley</title>
    <desc>The Valley follows a group of close friends as they trade bottle service in West Hollywood for baby bottles in the Valley all while they navigate bustling businesses, rocky relationships and feisty friendships.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715200000 -0400" stop="20260715210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715210000 -0400" stop="20260715220000 -0400" channel="FOX.US">
    <title>Nation's Dumbest</title>
    <desc>Nation's Dumbest is the first television show where the loser is the winner. Celebrities fight it out to be eliminated from the competition as quickly as possible to avoid being crowned the nation's dumbest. From influencers to wrestlers, comedians to politicians, the contestants are put to the test in a series of physical and mental rounds about all the things you really should know.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715210000 -0400" stop="20260715223400 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Alone</title>
    <desc>Alone places ten hardcore survivalists alone in the wilderness - no camera crew, no teams, no producers - on a single mission to stay alive. At stake is $500,000 awarded to the person who can last the longest. They will face extreme isolation and psychological distress as they plunge into the unknown, self-documenting their experience.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715210000 -0400" stop="20260715213000 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>My Strange Arrest</title>
    <desc>An in-depth look at the people who were arrested for allegedly committing some of the weirdest, wildest and most bizarre crimes ever. We dig beyond the headlines and the viral videos to look at the incidents and their consequences, hearing the stories from the accused, the arresting officers and eyewitnesses. These are bizarre crimes with real-life ramifications.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715210000 -0400" stop="20260715220000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Next Gen NYC</title>
    <desc>Next Gen NYC follows a tangled web of friends raised in the spotlight — or at least close enough for good lighting — as they stumble into adulthood one brunch, breakup and spontaneous decision at a time. Whether stepping out of their parents' shadows or creating their own legacies from scratch, these twentysomethings are determined to conquer Manhattan — if they can figure out how to adult first. Together, they'll navigate friendships, careers and romance, proving that trouble runs on espresso martinis and questionable decisions.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715210000 -0400" stop="20260715220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715210000 -0400" stop="20260715214200 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Expedition Unknown</title>
    <desc>In the hit series Expedition Unknown, Travel Channel's witty explorer Josh Gates seeks answers to some of the world's most captivating unsolved stories and legends. Gates is on a mission to find the truth behind each iconic legend, digging through years of historical evidence, facts and myths. Leaving no stone unturned, his adventures take him around the globe as he immerses himself in the core locales linked to each tale. From excavating ruins in search of the real Robin Hood to sailing the high seas investigating Christopher Columbus and exploring Nepal's "sky caves" for Shangri La, Gates' archaeological background and ubiquitous sense of humor generate a new take on age-old stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715213000 -0400" stop="20260715220100 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>My Strange Arrest</title>
    <desc>An in-depth look at the people who were arrested for allegedly committing some of the weirdest, wildest and most bizarre crimes ever. We dig beyond the headlines and the viral videos to look at the incidents and their consequences, hearing the stories from the accused, the arresting officers and eyewitnesses. These are bizarre crimes with real-life ramifications.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715220000 -0400" stop="20260715230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715220000 -0400" stop="20260715223000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715220100 -0400" stop="20260715230100 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Mystery at Blind Frog Ranch</title>
    <desc>There are some places on earth where the land just seems different, and Blind Frog Ranch in eastern Utah is one of those places. Locals say the land is cursed. That it's trying to hold on to something. From Aztec treasure to caverns of gold and silver to lost Mormon mines, legends surround Duane Ollinger's 160-acre ranch in Utah's Uintah Basin. But Duane isn't concerned with the lore. After discovering a system of seven underground caves that run through his property, he is singularly focused on finding what's hidden in them - no matter what the cost.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715220100 -0400" stop="20260715223200 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Swamp Patrol</title>
    <desc>SWAMP PATROL pulls viewers into the unpredictable world of law enforcement operating in America's most unforgiving swamps. From the tangled bayous of Louisiana to the coastal inlets of Florida, Swamp Patrol follows officers in real time through bodycam footage as they respond to a wide range of threats, including armed suspects, drug busts, missing persons, stolen boats, 11-foot gators, and deadly snakes. Every call comes with its own dangers, and in the depths of the swamp, there is no backup. The series offers a captivating look at the chaos and courage required to hold the line in places most people never step.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715223200 -0400" stop="20260715230400 -0400" channel="A&amp;E.US">
    <title>Swamp Patrol</title>
    <desc>SWAMP PATROL pulls viewers into the unpredictable world of law enforcement operating in America's most unforgiving swamps. From the tangled bayous of Louisiana to the coastal inlets of Florida, Swamp Patrol follows officers in real time through bodycam footage as they respond to a wide range of threats, including armed suspects, drug busts, missing persons, stolen boats, 11-foot gators, and deadly snakes. Every call comes with its own dangers, and in the depths of the swamp, there is no backup. The series offers a captivating look at the chaos and courage required to hold the line in places most people never step.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715223400 -0400" stop="20260715233400 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Forged in Fire</title>
    <desc>Forged in Fire features world-class bladesmiths competing against each other to create some of the most iconic edged weapons from history. In each episode, four of the best bladesmiths in the country will come together to put both their skills and reputations on the line. Whether they are making a Japanese katana, a medieval broadsword, or an ancient throwing blade like the chakram, the weapons they forge will be fully functional and lethal works of art and war. The unique histories contained within each weapon will be creatively told during the forging process and the final weapons themselves will be assessed and ruthlessly tested by our panel of expert judges. These dynamic and explosive tests will be individually designed to push the weapons to their absolute limit. One by one, the bladesmiths will be eliminated until only one remains to be crowned the champion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715230000 -0400" stop="20260715233500 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715230000 -0400" stop="20260716000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715233500 -0400" stop="20260716003500 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Jimmy Kimmel Live</title>
    <desc>Jimmy Kimmel Live features a diverse lineup of guests that include celebrities, athletes, musical acts, comedians and human-interest subjects, along with comedy bits and a house band.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715233500 -0400" stop="20260716003500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Emmy Award and Grammy Award winner Jimmy Fallon brought NBC's "The Tonight Show" back to its New York origins when he launched The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from Rockefeller Center. Fallon puts his own stamp on the storied NBC late-night franchise with his unique comedic wit, on-point pop culture awareness, welcoming style and impeccable taste in music with the award-winning house band, The Roots.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715003500 -0400" stop="20260715013500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Late Night with Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Seth Meyers, who is Saturday Night Live's longest serving anchor on the show's wildly popular "Weekend Update," takes over as host of NBC's Late Night — home to A-list celebrity guests, memorable comedy and the best in musical talent.As the Emmy Award-winning head writer for "SNL," Meyers has established a reputation for sharp wit and perfectly timed comedy, and has gained fame for his spot-on jokes and satire. Meyers takes his departure from "SNL" to his new post at "Late Night," as Jimmy Fallon moves to The Tonight Show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715020000 -0400" stop="20260715030000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Now</title>
    <desc>ABC World News Now gives viewers up-to-date information on current events and news from around the world, airing in the overnight hours. Its tone is somewhat lighter than a regular news broadcast, though reports are filed from the usual ABC News correspondents. Weather and pop culture stories round out the reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716050000 -0400" stop="20260716060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716060000 -0400" stop="20260716090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716060000 -0400" stop="20260716070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716070000 -0400" stop="20260716100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716070000 -0400" stop="20260716090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716070000 -0400" stop="20260716090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716070000 -0400" stop="20260716090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716080000 -0400" stop="20260716100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716090000 -0400" stop="20260716100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716090000 -0400" stop="20260716110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716090000 -0400" stop="20260716100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716100000 -0400" stop="20260716120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716100000 -0400" stop="20260716120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716100000 -0400" stop="20260716110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716110000 -0400" stop="20260716120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716120000 -0400" stop="20260716130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716120000 -0400" stop="20260716140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716130000 -0400" stop="20260716160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716130000 -0400" stop="20260716140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716140000 -0400" stop="20260716150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716140000 -0400" stop="20260716160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716160000 -0400" stop="20260716180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716160000 -0400" stop="20260716170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716170000 -0400" stop="20260716190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716180000 -0400" stop="20260716190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716183000 -0400" stop="20260716190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716190000 -0400" stop="20260716200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716190000 -0400" stop="20260716200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716200000 -0400" stop="20260716210000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Surviving Earth</title>
    <desc>Surviving Earth will take an incredible journey into prehistory to learn the lessons from past mass extinctions.Adopting cutting-edge digital technology, each episode transports the viewer back to meet the bizarre and amazing creatures and breathtaking landscapes of a vibrant lost world. Audiences will witness how life finds a way to survive on a planet where meteors fall, super volcanoes erupt, seas boil and the land moves. From the creators of "Walking with Dinosaurs" and "Primeval," these are the stories of the survivors, fighters and lucky ones that shaped the world we live in.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716200000 -0400" stop="20260716210000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Big Brother</title>
    <desc>Big Brother follows a group of people living together in a house outfitted with dozens of high-definition cameras and microphones recording their every move, 24 hours a day. Each week, the Houseguests will vote someone out of the house. At the end, the last remaining Houseguest will receive the grand prize of $500,000.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716200000 -0400" stop="20260716210000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Celebrity Family Feud</title>
    <desc>Teams of celebrities and their families face off to name the top responses to questions posed to 100 people.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716200000 -0400" stop="20260716210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716200000 -0400" stop="20260716210000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>The Real Housewives of Orange County</title>
    <desc>These ladies show no signs of slowing down and although they may be enjoying the sunny SoCal lifestyle, replete with plastic surgery and frequent shopping sprees, real life still manages to find them, even in the land of excess and indulgence on The Real Housewives of Orange County.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716210000 -0400" stop="20260716220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Secrets Declassified with David Duchovny</title>
    <desc>Secrets Declassified tells the incredible stories of government secrets that have only recently come to light. This series proves that secrets can be uncovered, and mysteries can still be unraveled." Each episode will find Duchovny focusing on a different topic, speaking with different experts. Subjects include the real-life story behind Argo and the mystery of the Area 51 conspiracy. Mulder would approve.From black ops and bizarre experiments to deadly cover-ups and nefarious gadgets, David Duchovny pulls the curtain back on all the government secrets in modern history we always suspected, but were never given the answers to. Through the strange and shocking things countries the world over ? and those who work for them ? have done in the name of national interest, we?ll investigate the explosive evidence from newly declassified files that will finally shine a new light on what?s really going on deep in the shadows.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716210000 -0400" stop="20260716220000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Since its beginning in 1986, Burning Man has grown from its anarchic counterculture roots in San Francisco to a globally recognized spectacle. Each year, 80,000 self-styled "Burners" congregate in the Nevada desert to create music, art, and connection, raise temples, join a spiritual movement centered on community, and take part in a modern American cultural experiment. Following the organization through several years of unprecedented turmoil, The Man Will Burn follows a movement pushed to its limits as it strives to stay operational while staying true to its core values.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716210000 -0400" stop="20260716220000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Press Your Luck</title>
    <desc>A game of wits, strategy and high stakes as contestants try to avoid the iconic WHAMMY for a chance at life-changing cash and prizes.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716210000 -0400" stop="20260716220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716210000 -0400" stop="20260716213000 -0400" channel="Bravo.US">
    <title>Watch What Happens Live</title>
    <desc>Watch What Happens Live is an interactive series hosted by Bravo programming executive Andy Cohen, Bravo's Senior Vice President of Original Programming and Development, is best known to viewers as the host of the network's often explosive Watch What Happens reunion specials. Watch What Happens originally debuted as a live online show on www.bravotv.com. Watch What Happens welcomes guests from some of the cable network's most popular series, as well as other entertainment stars, to chat about pop culture and celebrities in the news!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716220000 -0400" stop="20260716230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716220500 -0400" stop="20260716230500 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>Ancient Aliens</title>
    <desc>Ancient Aliens explores the controversial theory that extraterrestrials have visited Earth for millions of years. From the age of the dinosaurs to ancient Egypt, from early cave drawings to continued mass sightings in the US, each episode in this hit History series gives historic depth to the questions, speculations, provocative controversies, first-hand accounts and grounded theories surrounding this age old debate. Did intelligent beings from outer space visit Earth thousands of years ago?</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716230000 -0400" stop="20260716233500 -0400" channel="Comedy Central.US">
    <title>The Daily Show</title>
    <desc>Hosted by a rotating cast of comedy greats, The Daily Show remains the go-to source for provocative satire, insightful interviews and an award-winning team of correspondents and contributors.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716230000 -0400" stop="20260717000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716233500 -0400" stop="20260717003500 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Jimmy Kimmel Live</title>
    <desc>Jimmy Kimmel Live features a diverse lineup of guests that include celebrities, athletes, musical acts, comedians and human-interest subjects, along with comedy bits and a house band.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716233500 -0400" stop="20260717003500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Emmy Award and Grammy Award winner Jimmy Fallon brought NBC's "The Tonight Show" back to its New York origins when he launched The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon from Rockefeller Center. Fallon puts his own stamp on the storied NBC late-night franchise with his unique comedic wit, on-point pop culture awareness, welcoming style and impeccable taste in music with the award-winning house band, The Roots.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716003500 -0400" stop="20260716013500 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Late Night with Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Seth Meyers, who is Saturday Night Live's longest serving anchor on the show's wildly popular "Weekend Update," takes over as host of NBC's Late Night — home to A-list celebrity guests, memorable comedy and the best in musical talent.As the Emmy Award-winning head writer for "SNL," Meyers has established a reputation for sharp wit and perfectly timed comedy, and has gained fame for his spot-on jokes and satire. Meyers takes his departure from "SNL" to his new post at "Late Night," as Jimmy Fallon moves to The Tonight Show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716020000 -0400" stop="20260716030000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>ABC World News Now</title>
    <desc>ABC World News Now gives viewers up-to-date information on current events and news from around the world, airing in the overnight hours. Its tone is somewhat lighter than a regular news broadcast, though reports are filed from the usual ABC News correspondents. Weather and pop culture stories round out the reports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717050000 -0400" stop="20260717060000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Way Too Early</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced program brings viewers everything they need to know to start their days--from news and politics to sports and pop culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717060000 -0400" stop="20260717090000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Morning Joe</title>
    <desc>On Morning Joe, the hosts Joe Scarborough, Mika Brzezinski, and Willie Geist engage in dynamic discussion about political news and issues important to all Americans. Morning Joe attracts a variety of guests, including top newsmakers, politicians and cultural influencers.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717060000 -0400" stop="20260717070000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN This Morning</title>
    <desc>Start your day with Audie Cornish bringing you the latest headlines and analysis.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717070000 -0400" stop="20260717100000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central</title>
    <desc>Anchored by John Berman, Kate Bolduan and Sara Sidner, CNN News Central is the core hub of the network's best-in-class newsgathering operation during the day, bringing stories to viewers in real time, while offering perspective and context to key issues. Modeled after CNN's special election programming, CNN News Central uses similar technology and storytelling tools, and applies them to news well beyond politics. The immersive approach will showcase what CNN does best – breaking news, visual storytelling, and factual, impactful reporting.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717070000 -0400" stop="20260717090000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>Good Morning America</title>
    <desc>Good Morning America is a two-hour, live program anchored by Robin Roberts, George Stephanopoulos and Michael Strahan. Lara Spencer is the entertainmnt anchor, and Ginger Zee is the chief meteorologist.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717070000 -0400" stop="20260717090000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today</title>
    <desc>Today is an American news and talk morning television show that airs on NBC. The program debuted on January 14, 1952. It was the first of its genre on American television and in the world, and is the fifth-longest-running American television series.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717070000 -0400" stop="20260717090000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Mornings</title>
    <desc>CBS Mornings offers a thoughtful, substantive and insightful source of news and information to a daily audience of 3 million viewers. The Emmy Award-winning broadcast presents a mix of daily news, coverage of developing stories of national and global significance, and interviews with leading figures in politics, business and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717080000 -0400" stop="20260717100000 -0400" channel="NFL Network.US">
    <title>Good Morning Football</title>
    <desc>Prior to the start of the 2016 NFL regular season, NFL Network has announced a new daily morning show, Good Morning Football, premiering Monday, August 1. Hosted by Kay Adams, Nate Burleson, Peter Schrager and Kyle Brandt, and Executive Produced by Michael Davies, Good Morning Football airs live Monday–Friday at 7:00 a.m. ET on NFL Network from CBS Broadcast Center in New York City. The three-hour live show is NFL Network's first show to originate from New York City in the network's nearly 13 year history. Good Morning Football will re-air Monday–Friday starting at 10:00 a.m. ET.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717090000 -0400" stop="20260717100000 -0400" channel="Syndication.US">
    <title>The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>The 700 Club is a talk show featuring guests, news and spiritual stories from a Christian perspective. News stories are often related to Bible passages. Fundamentalist preacher and one-time presidential candidate Pat Robertson hosts this long-running religious show.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717090000 -0400" stop="20260717110000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle</title>
    <desc>Money, Power, Politics with Stephanie Ruhle, utilizing her extensive Wall Street background to analyze the high-stakes intersection of money, power, and politics, Stephanie Ruhle delivers original reporting and hard-hitting interviews on the stories that directly affect Americans' lives. The program focuses on business and political news, featuring the "Nightcap" roundtable segment from her previous show, The 11th Hour</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717090000 -0400" stop="20260717100000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>A news program intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning. Each daily live broadcast provides current domestic and international news, weather reports, and interviews with newsmakers from the worlds of politics, business, media, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717100000 -0400" stop="20260717120000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Situation Room</title>
    <desc>The Situation Room with Wolf Blitzer and Pamela Brown: The command center for breaking news, politics and extraordinary reports from around the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717100000 -0400" stop="20260717120000 -0400" channel="ESPN.US">
    <title>First Take</title>
    <desc>First Take (aka: ESPN First Take) is a weekday sports talk show co-hosted by Stephen A. Smith, Max Kellerman and Molly Qerim who are joined by regular contributors and special guests. The show includes daily sports news, interviews with sports journalists, athletes and personalities, spirited debates, and an assortment of other topics. The show debuted 7 May 2007 as "Cold Pizza".</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717100000 -0400" stop="20260717110000 -0400" channel="NBC.US">
    <title>TODAY with Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>America's feel-good morning show with big stars and sweet surprises; Jenna Bush Hager and Sheinelle Jones host an hour of heartfelt connection, inspirational stories, fun and laughs.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717110000 -0400" stop="20260717120000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>The View</title>
    <desc>The View is a live, one-hour daily talk show from ABC co-hosted by Whoopi Goldberg, Joy Behar, Sunny Hostin, Sara Haines, and Meghan McCain. It is the original forum in which real women discuss everyday issues, share their opinions and engage in colorful conversations.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717120000 -0400" stop="20260717130000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Inside Politics</title>
    <desc>Dana Bash features the top political stories, sourced by the best reporters.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717120000 -0400" stop="20260717140000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>On the Line with Alicia Menendez</title>
    <desc>On the Line with Alicia Menendez moves beyond the headlines to examine the stories shaping the nation, featuring one-on-one conversations with newsmakers and a focus on voices often left out of the political discourse</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717130000 -0400" stop="20260717160000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>CNN News Central (PM)</title>
    <desc>News from around the world with Brianna Keilar and Boris Sanchez.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717130000 -0400" stop="20260717140000 -0400" channel="ABC.US">
    <title>GMA3</title>
    <desc>GMA3 is a news, health, lifestyle and shopping program.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717140000 -0400" stop="20260717150000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>Beyond the Gates</title>
    <desc>Beyond the Gates is set in a leafy Maryland suburb just outside of Washington D.C., and in one the most affluent African American counties in the United States. Here you'll find a posh gated community with winding tree-lined streets and luxurious mansions to call home. At the center of this community are the Duprees, a powerful and prestigious multi-generational family that is the very definition of Black royalty. But behind these pristine walls and lush, manicured gardens are juicy secrets and scandals waiting to be uncovered. And those that live outside these gates are watching closely. These are the places where our characters live, love, work and play. Those who have "made it" and those who haven't are all trying to navigate life … and some with more grace than others.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717140000 -0400" stop="20260717160000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Moment with Katy Tur</title>
    <desc>The Moment with Katy Tur is designed to move beyond the immediate headlines to provide deeper context and understanding of the political and national stories shaping the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717160000 -0400" stop="20260717180000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>Deadline: White House</title>
    <desc>Hosted by Nicolle Wallace, this program provides in-depth reporting and dynamic discussions on the political stories driving the news cycle. Nicolle Wallace brings viewers the latest political developments of the day, in addition to interviews with leading newsmakers and influential politicians. Drawing on her years of experience as communications chief for President George W. Bush and senior advisor for the McCain-Palin campaign, Wallace provides political insight and clarity on where key decision-makers stand on complex issues.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717160000 -0400" stop="20260717170000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Arena with Kasie Hunt</title>
    <desc>Kasie Hunt brings key players into the arena for sharp analysis and panel discussion on the latest news in politics and culture.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717170000 -0400" stop="20260717190000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>The Lead with Jake Tapper</title>
    <desc>CNN's chief Washington correspondent, Jake Tapper, hosts this hourlong weekday afternoon program, which mixes Tapper's interests with headlines from around the country and the world, headlines that span politics, money, sports and popular culture. The Lead with Jake Tapper also concentrates on bringing stories that aren't found on front pages -- buried leads -- to the forefront. Tapper came to CNN from ABC News, where he most recently served as senior White House correspondent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717180000 -0400" stop="20260717190000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Beat with Ari Melber</title>
    <desc>The Beat with Ari Melber delivers the biggest political and news stories of the day, with interviews and original reporting from around the nation. An Emmy-winning journalist, attorney and former Senate staffer, Melber cuts through the spin and the noise to tell you what's really happening. Real news, every night.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717183000 -0400" stop="20260717190000 -0400" channel="CBS.US">
    <title>CBS Evening News</title>
    <desc>The CBS Evening News, a daily evening broadcast featuring news reports, feature stories and interviews by CBS News correspondents and reporters covering events across world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717190000 -0400" stop="20260717200000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Weeknight</title>
    <desc>One-on-one conversations with politicians and newsmakers, and the breaking issues of the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717190000 -0400" stop="20260717200000 -0400" channel="CNN.US">
    <title>Erin Burnett OutFront</title>
    <desc>Erin Burnett OutFront is an hour-long television news program hosted by Erin Burnett on CNN. The show premiered on October 3, 2011 in the 7PM and 11PM time slot to replace John King, USA. CNN said in 2011 they hoped Burnett's expected popularity would provide an "attractive" opening to an evening of "talk shows and news analysis". Erin Burnett, OutFront is broadcast live from CNN's Time Warner Center studios in New York City or on location from the site of a breaking news event, airing from 7:00 pm ET to 8:00 pm ET and also airs via tape-delay on CNN Philippines every Tuesday-Friday at 5:00 pm local time since March 17, 2015. The program covers a number of news stories of the day in a Count-up format, starting at #1 – most important and making it to #7 by the end of the hour. Burnett's program features taped packages from CNN Correspondents along with analysis and panel discussion.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717200000 -0400" stop="20260717210000 -0400" channel="STARZ.US">
    <title>Power Book III: Raising Kanan</title>
    <desc>Power Book III: Raising Kanan is a prequel story that takes viewers back to the '90s and the early years of iconic Power character Kanan Stark.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717200000 -0400" stop="20260717210000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>All In with Chris Hayes</title>
    <desc>On All In with Chris Hayes, Chris Hayes delivers impactful stories that don't always make the front page. Drawing from his background as a reporter, Hayes goes on the road to uncover the truth by knocking on doors, digging deeper and speaking with people representing all points of view.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717200000 -0400" stop="20260717210800 -0400" channel="Discovery.US">
    <title>Deadliest Catch</title>
    <desc>It's the deadliest job on earth: crab fishing off the Alaskan coast on the icy Bering Sea. These adventurers will battle Arctic weather, brutal waves, and a ticking clock for big money in this modern-day gold rush from which they may never return.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717210000 -0400" stop="20260717220000 -0400" channel="HBO.US">
    <title>Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>President and Mrs. Obama wanted to honor America's 250th anniversary and celebrate the unique history of our nation on this special occasion....But then Larry David called.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717210000 -0400" stop="20260717220300 -0400" channel="History.US">
    <title>The UnXplained</title>
    <desc>The UnXplained will tackle subjects that have mystified mankind for centuries, from mysterious structures and cursed ancient cities to extraterrestrial sightings and bizarre rituals. The series will also feature contributions from top scientists, historians, engineers and researchers - each seeking to shed light on how the seemingly impossible can happen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717210000 -0400" stop="20260717220000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Briefing with Jen Psaki</title>
    <desc>Based in Washington, D.C., The Briefing with Jen Psaki will pull from Psaki's decades-long experiences on campaign buses, in the Oval Office, at the State Department, and in the briefing room to dissect the most important stories of the day. Every day the show will aim to help viewers better understand the happenings in Washington and around the country, how it impacts their communities, and what leaders are doing to stand up for the people they represent.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717220000 -0400" stop="20260717230000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell</title>
    <desc>Drawing upon his experience as a former chief of staff on the Senate Finance Committee and as an Emmy-winning executive producer and writer of The West Wing, O'Donnell gives the last word and rewrites the most compelling stories of the day on The Last Word with Lawrence O'Donnell.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717230000 -0400" stop="20260718000000 -0400" channel="MS NOW.US">
    <title>The 11th Hour with Ali Velshi</title>
    <desc>Ali Velshi delivers sharp, data-driven analysis of the day's biggest stories.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711192500 -0400" stop="20260711193000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News Weekend</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711200000 -0400" stop="20260711210000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Alexander Armstrong Across America</title>
    <desc>Alexander Armstrong embarks on a journey across the United States to explore how a nation founded on bold ideals has grown into one of the world's most powerful and complex countries. From historic heartlands to modern extremes, this is a country shaped by its past but constantly reinventing itself.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712190000 -0400" stop="20260712200000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Countryfile</title>
    <desc>The people, places and stories making news in the British countryside.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712192500 -0400" stop="20260712193000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News Weekend</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712210000 -0400" stop="20260712220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>The Piano</title>
    <desc>Claudia Winkleman hosts the search for the UK's best amateur pianists.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713123000 -0400" stop="20260713133000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713124500 -0400" stop="20260713125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713140000 -0400" stop="20260713150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713141000 -0400" stop="20260713150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713150000 -0400" stop="20260713154500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>A series which helps prospective buyers find their dream home in the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713170000 -0400" stop="20260713180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713185500 -0400" stop="20260713190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713190000 -0400" stop="20260713193000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Global Eye</title>
    <desc>Award-winning investigations - revealing secrets, rooting out injustice, and exposing crime, corruption, and abuse. The biggest stories from BBC correspondents all over the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713193000 -0400" stop="20260713200000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Mastermind</title>
    <desc>Mastermind is a British quiz show, well known for its challenging questions, intimidating setting and air of seriousness. It first aired on 11 September 1972 &amp;amp; is still running today. Four contestants brave the black chair as they answer questions on their specialist subjects and test their general knowledge to win the coveted trophy.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713195500 -0400" stop="20260713200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Dover 24/7: Britain's Busiest Port</title>
    <desc>Dover 24/7: Britain's Busiest Port takes viewers inside one of the UK's most critical transport hubs, the Port of Dover.The series takes viewers inside some of the key port control centres to meet frontline staff and shine a light on the teamwork, expertise, operational challenges, and crucial minute-by-minute decisions that impact millions around the UK to reveal some of the huge 24/7 operation that keeps the nation's most important transport hub open for business. From the terminal and port control teams to the Port of Dover Police and the ferry and cruise companies, viewers will get to know the individuals keeping the port moving around the clock.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713203000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>Only Connect</title>
    <desc>Quiz show in which connections must be made between apparently unconnected things, where patience and lateral thinking are as vital as knowledge.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713203000 -0400" stop="20260713210000 -0400" channel="BBC Two.GB">
    <title>University Challenge</title>
    <desc>Academic quiz show where teams of students from UK universities answer questions on all manner of subjects.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713210000 -0400" stop="20260713220000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Cameras film around the clock in some of Britain's busiest A&amp;amp;E departments, where stories of life, love and loss unfold every day</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714124500 -0400" stop="20260714125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714140000 -0400" stop="20260714150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714141000 -0400" stop="20260714150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714150000 -0400" stop="20260714154500 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>A series which helps prospective buyers find their dream home in the country.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714170000 -0400" stop="20260714180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714185500 -0400" stop="20260714190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714195500 -0400" stop="20260714200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714210000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>The Great British Sewing Bee</title>
    <desc>Amateur sewers take on challenges as they compete to be named Britain's best home sewer.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714200000 -0400" stop="20260714210000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Bake Off: The Professionals</title>
    <desc>Twelve professional duos from across the U.K. go head to head in a series of competitive heats judged by celebrated pastry chefs Cherish Finden and Benoit Blin.In each episode the expert pairs are challenged to two rounds that will test their professional ability and allow them to showcase their creative flair. A new presenting line up of Tom Allen and Liam Charles will offer their own comedic take on events in the professional's kitchen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715124500 -0400" stop="20260715125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715140000 -0400" stop="20260715150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715141000 -0400" stop="20260715150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715170000 -0400" stop="20260715180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715185500 -0400" stop="20260715190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715195500 -0400" stop="20260715200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716124500 -0400" stop="20260716125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716140000 -0400" stop="20260716150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716141000 -0400" stop="20260716150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716170000 -0400" stop="20260716180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716185500 -0400" stop="20260716190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716195500 -0400" stop="20260716200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716200000 -0400" stop="20260716210000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Fake or Fortune?</title>
    <desc>Journalist Fiona Bruce teams up with art expert Philip Mould to investigate mysteries behind paintings.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716203000 -0400" stop="20260716210000 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>Tom Kerridge Cooks...</title>
    <desc>Tom Kerridge hits the road in his 1950s food truck to discover wonderful produce, cooking with the ingredients he finds along the way.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716210000 -0400" stop="20260716220500 -0400" channel="ITV1.GB">
    <title>The Chase Around the World</title>
    <desc>The Chase Around the World will take contestants on a global adventure competition. This series sees six pairs of contestants attempt to track down the biggest brains in Britain - all six of The Chasers - in undisclosed locations around the globe. Unravelling puzzles along the way, the winning pair will pit their knowledge against The Chasers in order to win a life-changing prize pot.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716210000 -0400" stop="20260716220000 -0400" channel="BBC One.GB">
    <title>Who Do You Think You Are?</title>
    <desc>Series in which celebrities trace their ancestry, discovering secrets and surprises from their past.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716220000 -0400" stop="20260716230000 -0400" channel="TRUE CRIME.GB">
    <title>Britain's Countryside Killers</title>
    <desc>This British series examines notorious murders that have had a lasting impact on rural communities in the UK. Each episode revisits a case that shocked once-peaceful towns and villages, highlighting how these seemingly idyllic settings were forever changed by violent crime. The series includes contributions from retired police detectives, forensic psychologists, and local journalists who provide detailed analysis of the investigative process behind each case.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717124500 -0400" stop="20260717125000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at Lunchtime</title>
    <desc>The latest national and international news, sport and weather.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717140000 -0400" stop="20260717150000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>Vanessa</title>
    <desc>Raw, unfiltered, authentic and personal, Vanessa Feltz wants you to tell her what's on your mind. Fiery discussions, a good giggle and plenty of afternoon gossip!</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717141000 -0400" stop="20260717150000 -0400" channel="Channel 4.GB">
    <title>Countdown</title>
    <desc>The show in which two contestants engage in a battle of wits, competing against the clock in games of lexical dexterity and numerical agility.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717170000 -0400" stop="20260717180000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717185500 -0400" stop="20260717190000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 18.55</title>
    <desc>National and international news.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717195500 -0400" stop="20260717200000 -0400" channel="5.GB">
    <title>5 News at 19:55</title>
    <desc>National and international news</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714210000 -0400" stop="20260714220000 -0400" channel="CTV.CA">
    <title>The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The Amazing Race Canada will provide a uniquely Canadian take on the original series, with competitors discovering the world within the borders of Canada.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712090000 -0400" stop="20260712100000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Insiders</title>
    <desc>Australia's must-watch political program continues to be a platform for the country's best political analysts and commentators, taking you to the heart of the action every Sunday morning.Insiders entered a very crowded Sunday morning political market in 2001. But our approach was to provide coverage with so many more elements, and to do it in a way that is informative but irreverent. And of course have a few laughs along the way. If you took politics too seriously you'd go mad," said founding host Barrie Cassidy.Insiders is the most watched morning show on Australian TV any day of the week. So start your week with the program the politicians rely on to find out what's going on.Insiders is broadcast on Sundays from 9am to 10am (AEST) on ABC TV and the ABC News channel.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712123000 -0400" stop="20260712133000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Landline</title>
    <desc>Pip Courtney &amp;amp; a team of Landline reporters around the country bring you up to date with the issues affecting rural &amp;amp; regional Australia. From farming, agriculture, food, economics, innovation, climate, infrastructure &amp;amp; more.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712183000 -0400" stop="20260712190000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Compass</title>
    <desc>Compass explores the Australian soul - our beliefs, our ethical dilemmas and the changing face of our spirituality, with new host, popular journalist and broadcaster, Indira Naidoo.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260712193000 -0400" stop="20260712203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Race Around The World</title>
    <desc>In a time defined by fast-paced narratives and global connection, Race Around the World returns both as a homage to its original spirit and a bold reimagining. It celebrates the raw power of authentic, on-the-ground storytelling and the boundless curiosity that fuels it.The revival of the much-loved format is set to deliver fresh perspectives, discover new creative talent and reaffirm the ABC's commitment to original Australian content.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713060000 -0400" stop="20260713090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713120000 -0400" stop="20260713130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713193000 -0400" stop="20260713200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713193000 -0400" stop="20260713203000 -0400" channel="Discovery.AU">
    <title>Aussie Gold Hunters</title>
    <desc>In Aussie Gold Hunters, we join three hard-core crews of gold prospectors as they take the gamble of a lifetime and battle to strike it big, deep in the wild west of outback Australia.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713200000 -0400" stop="20260713203000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Australian Story</title>
    <desc>These are the stories of who we are. Australian Story presents unique tales that provide an insight into Australian life with all its complexities and challenges.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713203000 -0400" stop="20260713211500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Four Corners</title>
    <desc>Four Corners is Australia's premier television current affairs program. It has been part of the national story since August 1961, exposing scandals, triggering inquiries, firing debate, confronting taboos and interpreting fads, trends and sub-cultures. Its consistently high standards of journalism and film-making have earned international recognition and an array of Walkleys, Logies and other national awards.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713212000 -0400" stop="20260713213500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Media Watch</title>
    <desc>Media Watch is Australia's leading forum for media analysis and comment.Conflicts of interest, bank backflips, deceit, misrepresentation, manipulation, plagiarism, abuse of power, technical lies and straight out fraud: Media Watch has built an unrivalled record of exposing media shenanigans since it first went to air in 1989.The media provides the information we need to make decisions about our lives, but how reliable are the media reports that shape our views of the world?Media Watch turns the spotlight onto those who literally 'make the news': the reporters, editors, sub-editors, producers, camera operators, sound recordists and photographers who claim to deliver the world to our doorsteps, radios, computers and living rooms. We also keep an eye on those who try to manipulate the media: the PR consultants, spin-doctors, lobbyists and "news makers" who set the agenda.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260713230000 -0400" stop="20260713233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714060000 -0400" stop="20260714090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714120000 -0400" stop="20260714130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714193000 -0400" stop="20260714200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260714230000 -0400" stop="20260714233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715060000 -0400" stop="20260715090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715120000 -0400" stop="20260715130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715193000 -0400" stop="20260715200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715200000 -0400" stop="20260715203500 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Gruen</title>
    <desc>The Gruen Transfer is about advertising, how it works, and how it works on us. It decodes and defuses the commercial messages that swirl through our lives, with the help of a panel of ad industry experts. From Season 5 the show was renamed "Gruen Planet" and expanded the topics covered to include political and commercial "spin" as well as advertising. In 2015 it is re-named as Gruen.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715203500 -0400" stop="20260715211000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>Spicks and Specks</title>
    <desc>Delve into musical history with Spicks and Specks, ABC TV's weekly comedy game show. Each week, the panel are joined by four guests from the worlds of comedy, music and entertainment.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715230000 -0400" stop="20260715233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716060000 -0400" stop="20260716090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716120000 -0400" stop="20260716130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716193000 -0400" stop="20260716200000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>The best analysis of local, national and international events from an Australian perspective. Hosted by Sarah Ferguson, with political commentary from 7.30 Political Editor Sabra Lane in Canberra.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716230000 -0400" stop="20260716233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717060000 -0400" stop="20260717090000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Be the first to know what's happened overnight. Michael Rowland and Lisa Millar, Paul Kennedy, Georgie Tunny and Nate Byrne bring you breaking news, interviews and all the information you need to get you through the day.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717120000 -0400" stop="20260717130000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Ros Childs presents the latest from ABC News, following today's top stories and coverage of events as they unfold. Plus comprehensive analysis and original reporting from ABC reporters around Australia and the world.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260717230000 -0400" stop="20260717233000 -0400" channel="ABC.AU">
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>More news, more often. Wherever you are stay in touch with ABC News. We've got more reporters in more places, connecting communities and covering the stories and issues that matter to you. Presented by Jade Barker.</desc>
    <category>TV Show</category>
  </programme>
</tv>